Welcome to the night, the cars laid out for show Star shine is so bright, watch the secrets unfold
With a rhythm
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Flow
Hearts in the balance
Every card an open door
Feel the romance
In every arcane world
Hi guys, how are you today? Thank you for being here. Welcome to the show.
Yeah, I'm trying the new thing. I'm trying to like
a different, if you could do a platform. I'm just trying just the Rumble and I find that I did a
Twitch but I can only stream to three things so I'm just trying to kick Rumble and YouTube thing.
There's my link is pinched
Yeah, so last day it was it was okay. I mean is that we had page and God you were here have a nice conversation
I was you know there and then
And I was getting a little tired and oh, you know, who was it? Oh Lord Vader's here. The thing with Lord Vader
That's people from me. Oh, there's someone in the back
Immediately I jump jump up and put them
On stage thinking that I've kept them waiting for a long time
And I just hear I
Hear like a laugh and I was like, I don't sound like Lord Vader
I was like, okay, and then it's like but I was looking at the screen and then I didn't got like a minute later God
He's like that's not Lord Vader and I look you know, it's like a it was the form Bob. It was just 20s thing again
I mean
It's just so it's all lame
So lame. I can't even describe how lame it is. It's just so dumb
I don't mean to I don't bother this person. I don't know this person just came to my show one day
Starts picking on me and starts a
text message it'd be terrible things
It's very just very weird person. So anyway
Can you go ahead and like this? Oh, look who we have here
Are you there do you hear me
Yes, you hear me now Trevor
Trevor do you hear me? Yes? Are you good? Are you good? Hey, yeah? Yeah? Yeah? Yeah
It's okay, I mean as I woke up. Hey everybody in chat. I woke up. I've been like, you know
looking at
You know the adding to my streaming platforms like look I've been in chat GPT talking about my show
Yeah, actually chat GPT is so awesome
You can give chat GPT like a link to any you know any public episode, right?
Yeah, hey, what's the money for 20 any public episode of my show?
I can put it into chat GPT and it will give me a whole analysis of the show like oh, how and I
Analyze how like my territory it does it's so many things
And it's like, it's just so cool, I'm really, I'm really...
I love his cat CPT. I love you use that. You know, what's the worst that I've found is a freaking Google Gemini
I mess around with that. Like I like to mess around and be like
rank
List and rank
bands on their significance and
I'll just say bands and let the AI
The Google Gemini ranks the bands in regards to significance before I know it
like the rolling stones are at the bottom of the list and the fucking spin doctors from the 90s
are like way on top. And I'm like, okay, this isn't right. This isn't right in the slightest.
Yeah, I like to fuck around with the AI to Google Gemini needs to really work on
It's it's not great. Yeah, I know. Well, I know it's like they are
There's their focus is all over the place on over there
You know, so it's like it's better like that your chat CPT focuses just on the AI. I mean, that's all they do
So it's like it's really
You know the Google it's like they just like, you know throw like a little the little money behind it and the department
But it's like I don't really focus everything on it like this. Yeah, so I think chat CPT tried that one
They even do
Is it yours? Oh, happy birthday. Happy birthday.
37. God damn it. God damn it, Sike. How did that happen?
I'm a lot older than you.
Well, I do want to thank you. Yeah
The older you get the more little birthdays and holidays mean like
like really there was
My neighbor, this was a few years ago. He had a friend over sitting on the porch and I was talking to him and my neighbor and
This guy said the most brilliant thing
When you become an older adult
Holidays and birthdays are just an excuse to drink
Yeah
Man
Where have the years gone, my friends?
It seems like just yesterday we were both in our 20s
having the times of our lives and...
I mean, my 20s, I just,
I always felt my 20s slipping away from me, you know?
I just, I always felt like,
and I've always felt like I never like got the use out of them.
I just wasted them away and like, you know.
Me too, me too, I wish.
I mean, I had gone in regards to,
You know when you're young and you're skinny and you're cute like just with
You know, I met up with guys and whatnot
Yeah, I really wish I would have did more with my 20s too because once my 30s hit man, the party was over
The party was over
the part I kind of feel like me too but I feel like you know the part is just getting started
in some senses I think we're alive right now and it's like we have like now we have the
knowledge and stuff like that that we didn't have at that age you know and so you know uh I don't
know hey we got the AI and the chat gbt right the chat gbt so that's fun that's fun that we got that
Uh-oh, what's going on?
Yeah, that Google Gemini, my God.
My God, I'm doing a list of rank bands or musicians
on significance in the fucking spin doctors
from the 90s are ahead of the Rolling Stones.
Like, okay, Google, let's fucking work that out.
Let's let's get that worked out. Psych, are you there? Are you there, sir?
Oh, for fuck's sakes. Oh, my dear boy, Syche. It's always something, is it not?
Man, it is hot. It is a toasty one here in Grand Rapids, Michigan. 89, 89 degrees, not counting the
I think we're going to get a break from the heat. I think it's going to drop down into the 70s for the next
week or so.
Syke, can you hear me?
Syke's wearing a flannel in July.
He must have some good air conditioning.
Hello, can you hear me? Hello, can you hear me?
What's going on, sir?
Oh my god, hold on. Oh, hold on. I need to move my headphones or connect it to the cord and it's very short, hold on.
Oh, oh shit. Here we go. Okay. Yeah
No, I dropped this following
Yeah, so here's the production value guys. Oh gosh, okay
Okay, please say please say please say okay
Yeah
Just go over here. Ah, sorry. Okay
Yeah, I'll just hold this I'll sit over here. Oh my gosh
Okay, that's a little bit better
Oh, hi guys. Let's see lava here arching and metatron is watching and recording back to wow, you know, I guess the
Well, hopefully it's a good thing. Okay. Hey, money. What's up Katrina? What's up everybody?
Yeah, so you've heard I've been doing these AI songs. Yeah, they've been having so much fun doing these
I heard your AI song you played that was uh, that was cute. That was real freaking cute. I heard that
Which one which one did you hear cuz I mean I made a bunch yesterday to like
It's all madness and
There's a madness. Yeah, I think that something like that. It was some song. It was just another day. I heard it.
There's a song called Madness.
I don't know. At least I used the name real quick.
Crazy or
Supposedly
YouTube is gonna
demonetize channels who primarily use
AI as their content like AI generated content. Yeah, they're gonna allow that they're gonna
They're gonna demonetize channels. It's because some people just use AI content. That's what they're talking about. They're talking about like
It's like almost fully produced. It's like completely like just like AI. It's just AI basically this like
What about these youtube shorts where it's just these zoomers the zoomers will just uh, so take somebody else's video
And then they'll narrate it
But they're narrating like it's so obvious like there's
There's no need for narration, but that's their way to get somebody else's video on their channel
and make money from it and they just give an obvious commentary that's not needed at all.
Right. Yeah, that's kind of like the react and that's like a kind of like going on the react reaction content
Where it's just like, you know, and people like ones are content to be used and people want to find content
I mean that's the whole thing. It's like I mean as long as people are watching it
But I think it is very lazy and like, you know, no, it's very pretty sad and obvious, but
It's like, you know, at least they're putting up something, you know, it's like, it's, uh...
Does that, uh, does that reaction, uh, like, I'm talking about, like, when people react to movies on, uh, YouTube,
like, major, major studio films, there's no way in fuck that gets monetized, right? It seems like...
Yeah, they can be monetized. It's called fair use. You can, you're allowed to, like, um,
use clips, and if you talk about it in an educational way, that's, that's...
basically what you choose very much about that.
It seems like the movie studios would have an issue with that.
Yeah, I mean, it's very, it's very used as long as you're not just showing clips of the whole like,
like long, just like long clips, you're just showing short parts of it.
You're allowed to use those, yeah.
It's like, well, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I would say we're able to do any movie reviews, you know?
I mean, it's about my TV.
It's like, it just turned on.
I need to hold on once again.
Man, Psych have must have some good air conditioning. He's wearing a long sleeve flannel or California.
We got.
I am god damn it. I am cooking.
I have my trusty fan here.
Okay, I'm good now.
Can you hear me?
Yes, I hear you now.
I hear you fine.
I have my...
Did you switch...
Yeah.
Did you switch headphones or whatever?
It's charging a little bit.
That one's charging a little bit.
So, I have the other one going.
Yeah.
You must have yourself some good air conditioning along along see along sleeve flannel and July
Yeah, it's like a little bit overcast outside. It's like it's not like hot. It's just like, you know, it's regular. Hey Christine
How are you sweetie?
It's like 90 here, and I am touching you are
The house where I live, it's right outside downtown Grand Rapids.
It's a big old house that was built in the 1890s and it's divided into four different units.
And yeah, this bad boy does not have central air.
I had my trusty fan here, but I turned it off because it comes through on the feed when I'm on other people's fan-als, so I don't have a fan-off.
Yeah.
I want to thank you that the other night you called in and you came on the show and it was kind of like, you know, you kind of defended me a little bit and you're like, I don't know, just felt good.
Yeah
Well, well it was well one I was intoxicated and two
Two can I ask you something about especially with these zoomers who watch these streams?
Yeah, I think you're supposed to know who everybody is
some random streamer that they watch is like Abraham Lincoln to where everybody knows who they are
one streamer I got into it with and listen I don't hold grudges it's whatever I mean all of this is
nonsense to begin with if I get into an argument with somebody you know it's not something I think
about but uh he's like oh you must be with uh what the fuck it's something about Aldi
are you with 1k army are you with 1k army like what in the fuck is 1k army
yeah i know
and then he said aldi and i'm like i know who aldi is but what like these the zoomers they are so
immersed in this nonsense that they think everybody else knows everybody and then there's somebody
screen names, and we bring up somebody, oh, that one guy, I don't even know the person's
name, that one guy really got the best of you on Sykes' panel when he was making fun
of your voice.
And then this person, this Zoomer will repeatedly come on different screen names.
telling me that and I don't have I don't know who the fuck he's referring to
like he said his name before the person's name before but yeah these words they get so into
because they they don't have a mind for themselves like they're not able to have a mind for themselves
so like when I see an older streamer who has some kind of personality or
Whatever not, they get so attached to him and then they automatically think that everybody knows who the fuck they are
And it's like yeah
A lot of people do know people around here like Aldi is like Aldi his name is Aldi 1k
And so like they're basically saying like, you know, they think like, you know, you were for Aldi and stuff
Or you know, can you have a voice?
I know Aldi because he was on the RVs before, but when somebody says without even saying Aldi,
they just say, are you part of 1k army? Like what the fuck is 1k army? Like what are you talking about?
I know, I know. And there's one person who who always tries to get my attention in all the chats.
Gee, and I'm just making this name up because I don't remember I can't remember who he's saying
G dog really uh
Really got you when he was up when you were on slice panel making fun of your voice. He really got you good
I'm like, who the fuck I don't even remember what you're talking about. I know into a few arguments, maybe
I'm uh on your panel, but
But they get so, the Zoomers, man, they are so into this and they are so attached.
And it's literally, they bring up these people like they're George Washington or Abraham Lincoln
or somebody.
That's okay.
I mean, good.
I mean, but it's like, that's the new celebrities, the new celebrities are like these regular
people that they just like are from like, you think about like, if people that watch
my show all the time, they're watching like, you know,
Me more than they watch like Seinfeld or like they watch like, you know, people would watch half hour shows a week
You know, it's like and now it's it's so it's like you have you really develop though like a kind of relationship when you're like you
You're people are you know, there's like so much interaction. It's like so it's like a whole different
You know, it's kind of like it's different than the old media. So it is kind of different
But yeah, did you take it a little bit? It's funny like seeing it play out
No, I mean, I was like, I think that was a pretty classic show, but I mean, there's like a lot.
I like the, you know, Larry David show.
Her beauty hasn't bettered it.
I definitely appreciate it. I mean, I'm not I'm not watching it that often, but I definitely appreciate it now more than I was when I, you know, grown up in the 90s when I was a kid, it was just that stupid show that was on all the time.
Yeah, fucking time Seinfeld and at the time I hated it, but now now that I'm an adult, I can somewhat appreciate it.
Yeah.
Hey, Yumi. Yeah, I know. I like being able to appreciate things that I couldn't understand as an adult.
Yeah, I did like I was I was a tea I was like in high school when Seinfeld was out
My parents would like watch it was like, you know, everyone watched it was like every Sunday was like friends Seinfeld
I know it was like the 90s, you know, and
The 90s man, we just
Whatever was on TV was on TV and you had to watch it. Yeah staying home from school and fucking odd
You were sick and you had to lay in bed and watch reruns of Roseanna
or mash remember that one god damn it that was a long day when when they were showing a non-stop
reruns of fucking mash but uh oh yeah
any other sport they would just have golf on all day on Sundays and it's like oh god damn
god damn it i was all about um let me see i mean it's like i was about you know tgif on
friday out on the hey hey person how are you oh hey hey have you met gaudy hello
Why so glum, Shum?
I'm not glum, I'm smiling like a...
Trevor's kind of glum, look at his face.
Huh? Oh yeah.
Yeah, yeah, people, I don't know.
It's just a random picture I picked out as my icon.
Well, pal, turn that frown upside down.
Let's get the party started.
Fair enough, fair enough.
How are you, good sir?
I'll do a fair test.
Yeah
Sorry the show ended last night Goddy, you know, we got yeah, I like dirt like the gate Lord Vader on I don't think that was him
Yeah, there were two dudes in that picture a black dude and a white dude, I think he was the white dude. Yeah
We're almost neighbors I'm in Chicago almost
Okay. Yeah. Okay. Is it is it hot in there too? It's about 84 right now. Okay. Yeah. We're we're we're at 90 here. Oh, Chicago. Nice. I've been there once or twice.
It's okay. I'm not fond of it myself. I live just outside the city. Oh, you really? Okay. Yeah. Okay.
Then what city are you near, Sike? I know you've said it before.
I'm in Redonda Beach. It's like LA, like South Bay, Los Angeles.
The South Bay of Los Angeles, would be cities.
Oh, okay. All right. Nice.
So two Midwesterners and a West Coast gentleman, if you will.
Yeah. I used to love going to LA. Every time I went up to California, I used to love it.
Fuck you, I loved it.
This was years ago, though. This was over 10 years ago.
Yeah, you live here or do you just visit here?
No, I used to visit all the time. It was great. I
Went to San Francisco LA San Diego. I never hit Northern California, but
Yeah, it is nice and it's expensive to use I lived there for like a play about a year in school
Northern California
Once in my life once in my life
1994 I was six years old. They went to go visit my
My uncle was based in California at the time in the Marines. So we went to go visit my aunt and uncle
1994, it's been over 30 years, and you know what I always think, and this is gonna sound ridiculous?
I'm like, oh my god, I was in California, and Tupac was still alive at that time, but he was still alive.
He didn't pass away until two years later, and I think, oh my god, I was there when he was still in the distance.
Oh, wow, that's your point, I was thinking that, but...
You know where I was when John Denver died? I was in Denver.
What do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you
He would literally drink and flying, he would get in his plane, totally wasted and fly.
That's what happened.
He was wasted flying his freaking airplane and...
He had his last Rocky Mountain High that day.
Yes, indeed.
He did.
Yes, sir.
It was good.
He deserved better.
So it goes, so it goes.
Yeah, so I don't know, guys, I don't know.
Guys, it's just a guy, Tony, porn bombing me.
It's like the same person.
I mean, it's like, and he does it like every day.
And it's like, he just uses somebody's name that I know,
that I like, let him back on if I'm like half asleep.
It's, I mean, it's like, you know, he doesn't know.
He just, and he goes, let's go.
And like last night, I was like half asleep.
That's why I didn't take a minute later.
God didn't say, no one said anything for like a minute.
This is penis without, no one's telling you.
I thought you'd see it.
I thought you were seeing it.
That's why you were enjoying it for about 10 seconds.
I was with the human page, human page talk.
Yeah
I'm wiping themselves. I'm wiping themselves. It was horrific. I'm wiping. It was horrific.
I'm alive. Oh, yeah. It's a girl bomb. It's a girl bomb. Oh, I don't want to see that. Yeah. Well,
it's like the guy had a guy came on and then he put his like hand to his face and all of a sudden
like it just looks like it exploded. Like it was all the great. It's just great. The graphics,
but it's like, but it's just like to make them think that, you know, just like to make the
His face was there one minute
And then it was just completely gone. It was like just flattered me everywhere. Oh my god. Oh my god
I don't endorse this. I don't endorse this porn bombing or anything
But any porn bombers out there listening if you can use the two girls one cup next time
The guy did that guy someone just use that on me. Where's that you?
Do you perform on that? I mean that now you're asking someone else is your phone
I've never seen that video, I've never seen that video, I've never heard about it, I've never seen that video, I've never seen that video, I've never heard about it, I've never seen that video, I've never seen that video, I've never seen that video, I've never seen that video, I've never seen that video, I've never seen that video, I've never seen that video, I've never seen that video, I've never seen that video, I've never seen that video, I've never seen that video, I've never seen that video, I've never seen that video, I've never seen that video, I've never seen that video, I've never seen that video, I've never seen that video, I've never seen that video, I've never seen that video, I've never seen that video, I've never seen that video, I've never seen that video, I've never seen that video, I've never seen that video, I've never seen that video, I've never seen that video
Yeah, I swear I've never seen the video, but I've heard about what happened. So
Reference I got well
So innocent two girls kissing nice music and then it just goes down here from this
I just wanted to get on really quick say hi to psych
Goddy, it was good to meet you, sir.
Good to talk to you, and I hope everybody has a good day.
Thank you, Trevor.
Yeah, thank you.
Take it easy, pal.
You too.
And cheer up, will you?
Cheer up.
Yeah.
I know.
I want a happy face.
Happy face next time, Trevor.
Hey, what are you doing tonight?
You going out?
I'm going out, and I don't really.
But look, do you like my new avatar photo?
Look at this picture you picked up.
No, actually, I'm honest with God, you know that, right?
You don't like it. I don't like it, but that's just my personal taste. I don't like satanic goats
Ah, please. I'm a Capricorn, so I'm allowed to. Oh, okay. Okay. Well, if that's what it is, then okay
I like it. You don't like satanic goats. Oh, please. I don't. I have a phobia. You ride the goat. I know you do.
you know as god i have a thing against satanic goats
did uh okay so he's he is rabbi i don't know betting us for sure he is i don't
know betting i don't know what we're betting us for sure
was that baffin man no this is just i just said i just said a mystical goat it's
just like a nice like you know like a little okay if it's a mystical capricorn
goat then i can i can do it with that yeah that's all
baffin man no no i'm not a baffin from it fan
Yeah, well Baphomet is more but you know transgender than a than a goat, but yeah
He does have a good head. That's why they pushed the transgender agenda, right?
Well, not because of Baphomet, but yeah
They are pushing the transgender agenda for probably nefarious purposes and not and also not for purposes the
Necessarily pro-trans. Yeah, I mean, I mean, that's why they have I was like, you know, it's such a big deal. Yeah, it's iconic
Satanic thing. Well, it's like, I mean, that's part of it is just like, you know, changing around the roles, right?
It's like putting everything on its head. That's part of it. It's like infusing society. Everything's reversed, you know
Everything
Yeah, it's all everything's inverted. It's all the inverted just like the you know, the pentagram is inverted and so is everything else so so
yeah, but
Satanism it can be very no it has positive side so it's like words like yeah
This is about self-improvement in a way and but it's like that goes into like that's extreme that narcissism and psychopathy
Where it's like, you know, it basically is incurred, you know, it's like it basically it will turn you into that if you're not already
just based on like
Oh, what will you know, it was just turning your thoughts of humanity into animals. Well, you hate people
Yeah, well basically it's like atheism basically for most people, but I know you hear me. Hold on. Let me see. Hold on
See fucking Satan that doing his job again. Satan at work. Yeah, can you hear me now?
Hello, you hear me shit, you hear me? Hold on
Do you hear me God God you hear me? Hello?
Hello
Shit well, I don't know can you hear me? I
Don't know if you can hear me. Can you guys hear me in the chat? Okay? You're both of us. I don't know my okay, so
Hey, JT, so I can't hear God now
Just God talking
Okay, now God we can't hear you though. You might not muted. Okay. Well, anyway
You know you can love humanity or you can like Satan kicked you off. Oh, no come back up I
Love humanity, but I see it I see it's flawed, you know, but it's like that's I think that's part of it
You know the beauty of things is that you know, we're not perfect, right?
We can just sound GPS. I'm sure you'd all know all about and you know, Ziggy knows all about it, too
I mean, I talked to you about I actually I mean, I came from that that was actually, you know
I came from that background in a way, right? Ah
Long had always fixed the audio
But it was like, you know
It's a very
You know, I was a rebel without a cause maybe when I was a teenager really, right? Satan is evil mountain
It's a con it's a concept you can call it the concept of evil. Yeah, I'm gonna be evil, right?
Like I said, I always think about like Satan like like a slug worth from Willy Wonka
Slugworth is like Petter was Willy Wonka. He's always copying Willy Wonka
You know just like the double kind copies of God, but not to create his own stuff, right and then
The then the turns out like Slugworth works for Willy Wonka, right and he was who's there to test the kids
Is he was actually like the end of the purest heart, right?
Just based on would they sell out
Billy Wonka for whatever they were offered for that for the everlasting gob stopper by a slow word, right?
I mean that's like not like the
forbidden fruit, right?
So go betray God to take some of the fruit from his garden, right? Go take one of his pieces of fruit
That's whole thing, right? It's just a trick
that
You can look at things. I like Superman Superman's kind of like a Jewish archetype for like, you know, the Jewish superhero kind of archetype
So that I'm not like that into comics kind of thing, but
It's a feeling you know, it's very simple. Love Superman if I go crazy, um, I call you
What's the evil Superman throughout this week? I don't know. I'll tell you the evil Superman
Um, yeah, oh, yeah guys we're almost at 100 members by the way guys and almost and also um
I have the emojis in chat now so you guys you can type the
Put the emojis in there's like 10 of them right now. I think 10 emojis just for members to put in
and
If you have suggestions, I can put four more right now
And then I can, once I hit 100, which I'm almost at,
I think I'm at like almost four more subscriptions to 100.
And then I can add more, even more.
So we'll have a whole repertoire.
Yeah, there you go.
There's the help me.
Yeah, so I have to help me one there,
in case like, you know, people like...
Need some help in the chat you can just go help me help me and so I can see you can just type that icon
I mean, I won't see that. I'll see this help help me, right? I'll see the text, but
You get the point so
That and so if somebody's adopting or something or you need or you need to get attention like just like you post that in the chat
Oh, and JT is the wing flying monkeys. She's the flying monkeys. Yes, we discussed those on narcissism. They're called proxy abusers
They are there when the narcissist the main the main head vampire or you know when the
whoever's
You're the supply of which is like what they consider you they consider you like well appliances like a
When the relation goes bad with some sort of narcissist relationship goes bad with you they consider it like the refrigerator breaking
Oh, no, it's like whose mouth is that?
I don't know. It might be a vampire mouth. I'm not sure I have to look at the
Look at it. Let me see. I don't know. I just I had this little
Certain clip are and I was just one I chose but if it's like, you know
You can give me other suggestions for it.
Let me see.
Okay.
Abuse by proxy.
Yeah, it is.
I mean, it's by proxy.
By proxy means, what, you're making a troll face?
I mean, by proxy means they have somebody else do it.
So it's like, oh, so you go into contact with a narcissist.
So then they have some mutual friends or something
that are charmed by them or their friends anyway.
So they're going to say, hey, can you go over to this person's house, see how they're doing,
like, gather information, kind of like, you know, they like to think of themselves as like secret
secret agents or spies or like, you know, like, they think they work with a CIA or something,
right? I made the new logo and banner. Yes, I made them through Canva. Yeah, I did. How do you like them?
I hope that I'm doing a good job at that.
I'm trying to do like, you know,
yeah, music going,
we can do another AI song if you guys want to today.
Oh, it's impressive.
Oh, thank you.
Yeah, well, Canva is pretty cool software.
I mean, or, you know, an app.
I'm on a free trial.
Thank you very much.
Yeah, I'm testing new stuff. I have but you know, I've been I make really cool things
I made it like these graphics like I made this is a panel open and I can see the panels closed right there
See if I'm like my open close sign and then I mean, this is the logo. I mean, it's it's really like, you know
I can't really take credit. I just tell the AI or you know, and sometimes I just put my name on it
And you can person license. Oh, yeah, it's pretty cool
Uh, what is this one blue? Okay, and their backgrounds things show you this background
The background so I'm a purple rain it looks best though guys like kind of like this one or this one
And we'll just use that for
Okay, you're doing good.
Good cat, how is everyone doing?
Hey, Vader, let's see.
Thank you so much, thank you so much.
If you guys want any advice for graphics
or any kind of stuff, I can tell you all the stuff I use.
Okay, yeah.
Vader why are you why are you but that is Vader looking sick? Okay, so guys I want to welcome if anybody's on
See what am I on rumble and kick? I think welcome. This is my first time to see me on rumble. I don't
it's just
You know, it's new I'm just you know. Hi. I don't know if anyone's gonna watch me there, but we'll see
Hear me now. My mic was off. I think
Okay, better
Yeah, you're both side. Yeah, I'm sorry guys. Yeah, I'm low on audio right now
I did not charge enough before I started my mistake my mistake
No wrench no peace. Oh, well, how about
You're lucky you're you're a chat
Wait, why are you mad? Oh, he's mad
with my rumble it is psyche awakens i think it's just like the awakens ts y c h e a w a key
yeah like the awakens on rumble and kick um yeah um we'll see how it goes i don't know it's like you
know go ahead and follow me there you know if you want it i'm pretty sick i don't know if it's
free i don't know if he's even timed out in chat but he's definitely was on the panel last night
He's rumble any good guys. What do you think? I mean, I think I've been there. I mean it looks like
You know, they're not as good as you too, of course
And they're so much more complicated like the you know, this the back room you to this is so nice and simple like a
Today's the streaming on YouTube our number. Why do you think that brown panda? I think the
You know, it's like they might you might do some you know have some things you're not supposed to talk about but they already do right
There's a lot of things you're not supposed to talk about, right?
So there's a bit more stuff you can't talk about.
It's just going to be, those ads, I don't think the streaming is limited.
We're always going to want a live stream.
You can do juice videos, and then you can go to discord or something. I don't know we'll figure it out
It's better play when the channels in better play for when the channels in the shit show. Okay. Yeah, I
See it listed on ip2. Well, you can go ahead and try to try to put my show on there
But I don't I don't know I don't know what I could do to do that. I
I think they should list me of course, but
It's up to them
I've said my teeth for that of that, you know, if I say anything it just gets the fans all riled up and like
Harassing me. He gets very sensitive and ban chance for the smallest thing. Yeah, so I'll probably get banned off kicks. So but
Who cares?
It's like what I've had one person come to the chat
IPQ shit. Yeah, it's not that big anymore
Yeah, but so I was telling you so let's do a AI song. Okay, so what should we do to the song bit?
So who's gonna be in the song today?
What should it what should it kind of be about? Let's let's write it together
Everyone can give suggestions and then we'll try to decide where's my pen
Well, I'll have to see a pen
Okay, well, we'll just memorize them. Okay. Okay, so I am I am I am pretty blind. Okay, so, you know, AI song
Okay, let's do an AI song. Okay, so who's in the chat?
Okay
Let's make a song about
flying monkeys
Okay, so what you're saying you want to be in the song? I'm just doing evil some I'd say I mean
Yeah, I'll talk about the I'll talk about the evil some evil people on like
It's like the villains like like like who's the villain like he was the villain on the show on and
Blogger we can do a diss song we can do who is it was a villain. I mean those are like
Mr.. Big Pipes is the villain
I
Don't know I don't want to get
It's your big pipes big
Q
Hmm, I don't know
What do you think guys
Any suggestion who's this who's some villains in the show? Okay. I'll just talk to us. I'll just I'll just make a song for the people that were banned
Maybe banned people who's banned MC Nemesis
And I really haven't banned anybody though. I don't know
Hard it's not feeling hard, okay, let me see have like
Big
I have my ideas
Okay
They're good chat gpt
Okay chat gpt
Huh, and then you all you have to do is like say write me a like a AI song, you know
It's all free and stuff. Okay
Okay
Right
Oops
Oh
Okay, okay, hold on
Okay, this will be funny
Oh
Okay, any ideas, it's finished. It's you okay
Yeah
Okay, I think I wrote it. Let me see
Okay, okay
Okay, I made it okay, so they made it. Oh shit, this is sounds good
It's a bit says bouncy trap and a playful dis vibe. Okay, so the bouncy so it's a trap song, okay?
So interesting, okay?
Won't tell you too much about it. I'll tell you I'll tell you the guy is called panel panel graveyard is called panel graveyard
this should be funny. Okay. Okay, so copy. Okay. So then I go AI, AI, user generator.
Okay. I plug it in. Find in. Okay. Plug it in. Very easy to do.
When you put the kind of music it is, let's see, here's the lyrics.
Okay, okay.
And then I just rewind.
Okay.
I can't wait to hear this one, this will be good.
I deleted too much of it, okay.
Okay, here we go, guys.
Okay, so then it says it's called panel of graveyard.
And genre is trap.
Let's see, where's the trap?
There's like a million styles too, and it's so hard to find. Okay, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap, trap
But I think they would I think they have trap here, but I don't oh, huh
So what should I do instead of trap if I can't find it I can do I don't want to keep you guys waiting hip-hop
the diss track so
Okay, I'll just I'll just do hip-hop or something. I'll do hip-hop. No, I'll do future household. That's future house
Could be a mumble wrap with coast wrap I guess west coast wrap that's kind of like trap, right?
Okay, that's just generating it
Okay, I'll predict jamban
Okay, so they'll so it's almost
I think it's good
It's creating it now
I can't wait for this one. This will be cool
Okay, you know graveyard
Oh guys are you excited? She went to tarot card reading and she's most of the mess around. Oh, I don't know. It's like, yeah
People say oh, it's against the vibe. I think I don't I think it's compatible with it with everything. No, I don't know
It's not
The only evil is in people. It's not in the cards, you know
Okay, so it's downloading a panel graveyard, so I'll get my streamer ready to go so I'm ready to put this right in there
I was trying to make music videos out of it.
It's like, I'm just having a little trouble, right?
So Hannah claims, okay, let me just go for studio.
Okay, and then I just make my cameras off.
Okay, I'm in.
I just have to
Hopefully it'll be ready soon
Creating it that's like a few minutes to do though. So yeah, I know beta. That's terrible, huh? It's okay. I know it wasn't you I
Know I know yeah, oh
Yep
So we're almost there hopefully it's almost done. Oh, it's ready. Okay, so download mp3
File download
Hi Tricks. Okay, one second. Okay. So then add music. Hopefully it'll be right there. Okay.
Reasons. Okay. Okay. Audio. Okay. In here, download. Okay. It's here. It's here, guys.
You guys ready to hear the premiere of panel graveyard. I don't know if it'll be funny. We'll see
Hi tracks
Hi, babe
Ready hold on a second. Okay. It's ready to go
The panels get cut, let's talk about who didn't survive the fight
They got kicked off the panel, now they haunt the stream
Trying to flex with no talent, just a boot and a scream
You acting like stars, but you barely gleam
Now you stuck in the chat like a failed meme
You're met emcees, now this is boy sit down quick
Gay and loud's fine, but stop saying that
You drop bars with no rhythm, more cringe than raw
I had to boot you out like a windows flaw
All-all-all d-
flash me you bro no thanks your balls got less views than my tarot ranks this ain't
on megal this is mystic art you showed up nasty and left with a fart
qq gets green when my numbers climb jealousy's a color that don't match your sign
trying to drag me down with that weak debate
But your mic cuts out when I levitate
Adblogger try to clone me bleached and all
But your styles knock off like a bathroom stall
My panel's real, yours is Botox fake
Keep scrubbin' that hole, I'm makin' earthquakes
Sig puffin' dull like a two-hour nap
Calling yourself incel, now you just yap
No sauce, no spice, no vibe, no thrill
Your background noise with an ego to fill
To Mr. Bigpipes, more like Mr. Mid
You talk a lot of-
cringe for a grown-ass kid jealous in the chat cuz the crowd chose me while you
gas your mic with mediocrity this panel's protected the vibe is tight if you
show up wild you're gone by night tarot cards cut don't test the flame get
booted fast we remember your name Nick they got kicked off the panel now they
haunt the stream trying to flex with no talent just a boot and a scream now they
rage in the comments petty and mean but I'm still live still lit still queend
next time bring something real to the table till then bye bye
what did you say? i thought it was pretty decent
Not bad. Hi, hi. What'd you think? That was pretty good. I mean, it was like, you know,
it did pretty good. Hey, I know, but I know I was going to put Alexander in there. But then the
blogger Bleach Asshole was like so irresistible. And they put that theme in the lyrics. They put
the buddy Bleach and then the thing about Botox. And I didn't say anything about Botox,
That cool I
Didn't have all I did was like I didn't like it like kind of like
Guess a lot of information correctly. I don't know. It's a weird. Hey, be da
And I'm gonna write a song for be the next it's gonna be just about beta
Oh, I'm doing way too much. Hi guys. Hi
Yeah, I think it pipes long a time ago. I know I should know
I also if you didn't hear like MC nemesis was in there in the like, you know
He was like the first person to be banned pretty much. He he has some kind of explosive
Disorder where he can't like stop explosive reaction like for you. He always has to say the m word no matter like
Can't stop saying it. It's like I kind of like Tourette's but like more more dumb
It's like more like he's just like stupid
So and then he was like, you know, he came out on the show. Yeah, he's disgusting. He's disgusting
He was like one of my first guests you I think he might have been the first person to come try to come on the panel
So
Yeah back story you're hearing some of the lore of lore freaky awakens
Um
Okay, you didn't get a chance to unblock. Okay, let me know who it was I can have a look I can have a look at
Let me see if my rumbles up. Let me see how it looks. Let me see rumble
Okay, I mean it's it's up. I mean it's absolutely nobody's I mean that's the thing
It's like okay. How is anybody gonna find me like you know, it's like nobody's gonna
These other platforms are not gonna work for me. It's okay. It's like it's just gonna yeah, is this gonna be you I mean the other platform
I mean it's like
Someone said I was like how many viewers are you getting I think I asked like Chris. Okay, I think how many who's my rumble? Okay
All right, babe, hold on a second.
Oh, it's a monetized livestream.
Oh, yeah.
Monetized livestream, okay.
Here's my rumble account, I think.
Okay, there's my rumble. Okay, so here's the okay, so that's
not Lord Vader. That is a fake Lord Vader. Again, I'm going to ban that, I guess. Yep.
I recognize your names now, okay.
Hold on where my glasses, I can't put my glass
Okay, yeah
Oh
Yeah, I try I try with them seen them as this I try I try
So yeah, I'm getting a new a stange tomorrow for my
My camera because this one is like falling over
So I
Guess I'll write the beat a slot
You see
Yeah
So how's everybody's day? What is today? Today is Tuesday, July 15th. Thank you. Thank you,
Rob it
Little crazy
Okay
Time is a moment, okay
Okay, I'm ready to start.
Close it out.
Shit.
I had a good thing.
Okay, I got it.
Not deleted.
How are we doing, guys?
Okay, so it's kind of harder to write on this tablet.
Okay, oh, here it is, okay.
So high tracks.
This one's attention.
Come here.
What's wrong?
Being beauty, okay
Okay, hey easy, okay, so I mean
Tricks yeah
He's going nuts today, okay. Oh, okay, it's writing a song
But you get to choose what the instrumental or what it sounds like, okay?
Copy, okay
I will do a song with my cats too
Uh, okay, what do you uh beat away would you like?
Okay, it can be like any genre pretty much is like every
Okay
Love song, okay, so
Love song so it says genre I can put
Hey Lenore I can put
We're doing readings a little bit. Hold on. So I'll guess love song I guess that would be
That would be Sonata a sonata
Okay, you're leaving why are you leaving so early? Okay. Well, I'll be over good day to you. I hope you're not mad. Okay, let's see
Let's do
You do I'm babe
What was it? Arabic music?
I don't know if you like it.
Moonlight Sonata. Oh, Sonata. Okay, which way is Sonata? We'll do it.
Generating a Sonata.
For Beta.
Hi. Hi.
You're obsessed. Oh, you're your cat woman. I'm a cat man
Here
Okay, moonlight Sinatra
Yeah, and so then now we wait you thought it was useful world
Up and away. Okay, so hope everybody's okay. Hope everybody's okay. Okay
How many of these I think I can make like 300 probably saw me so we'll see how we'll see how long it lasts
I just did the trial another trial though. I actually bought the
one month membership
Should be good guys
Okay, oh my gosh and I put cats it made them thumbnail cats
You're scared of the lyrics now? Uh-oh.
Okay, let me clear up some space, too, for this.
Downloading. Yeah, so what's going on in chat?
Next you remember to get a girth there but I'd like to keep stretching a sphincter this way you oh my gosh, hold on
Who's the cat killer what's going on hopefully nobody's ever done that
His love has been reported
They're probably licking her lips in your cat in the back. Oh, no, no, no eating tricks
fix the
I think it's good. I don't think it tastes good
Knorr Knorr is over here, too. Mr. Sensen, if you stand, oh make any shot. Oh
I
Think big dinosaur picture your picture on death. You know, she's such a dynamic interesting person
You never know the true story with her, right? Why that night things don't work
That does you probably put the you might have put the name in wrong one, right? But no, it works
well, it doesn't
Delete people like this is the mod for me. It's just basically those comments for me
Oh, okay
Sorry this is guys
It will be...
I wonder if I could probably propose,
like, you know, just put like the description in here,
but I think chat CPC does the very better.
Oh, you're talking about your,
I know the, oh, the code where,
yeah, you have to put it first,
you have to put it like this, like this, like this one.
Think it works
There you go, oh
It's ready. It's ready. Yeah, you're ready for the new song. Let's see if I can get this done
D3
Okay, okay, it's downloaded. Oh one second
Okay, here it is.
Okay, are you ready?
You said, write a funny, cute, loving song about Bita.
She is the host of Beat as Kitty.
She is a beautiful Persian woman.
She is so funny.
She has a hysterical laugh.
She is so loyal and true.
I have a BKG tattoo.
Her cats are Mickey and Muhammad.
I will love her always.
Thank you, Bita.
Sure, here's a funny, cute, and loving song about Bita.
The host of Beat as Kitties, with a mix of sweetness laughter
and purring kitties.
Think acoustic ukulele or soft indie pop vibe.
Thank you, Bita.
Oh, beata, you're a Persian queen
On screen with cats, you're livin' the dream
Mickey and Muhammad at your side
You laugh so loud the stars collide
You host Beatas Kitties, it's a wild ride
With eyeliner sharp and a heart so wide
You tell the truth, you never lie
Even when your cats knock down the Wi-Fi
Thank you, beata, you magical girl
With that hysterical laugh that could shake the world
It's true, cause I'll always love you
Beta Boo!
You're so loyal, funny, crazy and sweet
Like a TikTok cat with tiny feet
Thank you, Beta, for being you
Even when Muhammad steals your shoe
She's got sass and she's got style and she can make a troll cry in a while
We're just one wink and that Persian grace and a kitty filter on her face
Beta's heart is full of gold
She'll keep you warm when the world is cold and when she laughs, oh man, you'll see it's like a rainbow
with extra
Mickey's meowing
In the background beat, Muhammad's knockin' down stuff with his feet
The beat just giggles and sings along like she's starin' in her own sitcom
Thank you beat, you magical girl
With that hysterical laugh that could shake the world
I got a BKG tattoo, it's true
Like a tiktok cat with tiny feet
Thank you, Bita, for being you
Even when you meow on live too
So here's my song, it's cheesy but true
Written with cat hair and love for you
Beat as kitty's forever will be
A show of love and cats and Bita
You say
Wow, oh, how sweet that was that was just we
That was adorable
I just gave it a little bit of input and then it came up with that whole thing. That was amazing. Thank you so much. Love you. Hey
What's wrong? I think Tricks is, Tricks is horny, I think. What are you horny?
Yeah, he's like, where am I cute? I know, where's our kitty cats? Where's the kitty cats? Where are all the kitty cats?
Oh
That was cute
Thank you be and it's kind of like I didn't know that's what that's what the sonata sounded like
It's kind of like very upbeat in the
Thank you all
Thank you
They and thank you how sweet I mean how awesome I'm able to like you know
They combine humans and and uh machines and now you can get some cool stuff
you know
You say your cat was horny, yeah tricks are you little horny?
Yeah, I don't know the cats are kind of
Kind of been running around lately. Hey, babe
Here yeah, well
I'm a sort of ice sometimes right
Yes getting crazy isn't it or be like what's that it or is like what the hell? Yeah, isn't that cool? It's yeah
Yeah, you can go to AIMusicGen.AI I think is what I use and then you say you know
you can it's like free but you can only play it unless you get the it has to
upgrade you can't download the song you can just stream it you just play it you
know. Yeah. Oh J-Dogs stop it.
Anyone seen an MPD here?
MPD, oh, you know, there's MPDs everywhere.
I think most of the population might be them.
Richard, like, you know, basically,
well, MPD comes from like, you know, non-playing MPD.
Oh, MPD, oh, narcissistic personality disorder.
Okay.
I think it's an NPC, which is like not,
NPC is like one letter off.
And then an MPD is the,
One letter off the New York Police Department
Which is how many letters of Alice's off from being a comfortable. Okay, I'm just kidding. Okay, so anyway
Um, what day is what is Tuesday is Tuesday today, um, I have
I didn't drink last night. I say I did I had a beer I had a beer in my
Yeah
But groomers are you know, you can we can you cats personal they groom themselves second of all, you know
We can also groom them as it's no dogs. Yeah, the big some of the dogs need their hair cut a certain way cats
They don't really
particularly need a groomer unless they're you know, they their hair gets real mad at it or something or
you know usually
Fine they're very clean animals
Even like the the Prophet Muhammad with he like talked about how like
You could share your food with the cat, you could share your bowl, and you could sleep in the same bed and stuff like that, which is pretty revolutionary at the time to think about that.
Thank you guys for the subscriptions on rumble too. Thank you so much
Yeah
Yeah, if you know by the jt. Yeah, you're not mp. Oh, yeah, let's not call it CV
I mean like you might be a narcissist, but you know a lot of people are I
Think we all we all we all have some good degree of narcissism, especially the society you have to like it's like we're various self-conscious society
We're very
It focused on, hey, we're a very individualist center, you know?
Doug D, no, I love to do that, mod delete, stuff like that, and then if need be,
you can start timing him out.
He's already banned on some other accounts, you know, for saying really terrible things.
Stay turned.
Can someone delete that?
That's stay turned.
So please, that's not appropriate to talk about, it's not the time or place.
Okay, MPD, so you're the MPD, Slayer's the NPC and Alex is the NYPD.
I'm just kidding.
I didn't say that stuff. You're hacking impersonated. Well, that's the danger of being hacked so that you could be, you know.
NPDJT, nope, I just heard, hey, there's a rear skyline.
Okay, thank you, JT.
The moon, Saturn and Neptune Alliance.
You're seeing best in the Easter night sky.
Saturn will appear in your Pisces with the moon just above
and dim Neptune.
Yes.
It's actually even said but it's even said that the M on the cat's forehead stands for Mohammed, Mary or
Mal with the Egyptian an Egyptian cat goddess
Yeah, milder roar display. Oh beautiful. Thank you for letting us know about that
I wonder like, you know Neptune and Saturn so it sounds like dreams and like maybe something about dreams coming in reality
This is what I intuitively think.
Are there Pisces?
Yeah, that's ruled by Neptune, right?
And Jupiter.
Oh, so my beard's getting pretty thick now.
He please put a hex on y'all. No, I don't really do I don't I don't not really do I don't do hexes
I don't do any kind of like I
Just all I do is like return to sender
Maybe it's the closest thing and then you can do that yourself and so you just you know
Just do a prayer for return sender and that acid return to the
If he's sending any energy, but if he's not, then leave him alone.
Here's a question.
Why do the pyramids in Sudan have the same painting as the one in Egypt?
Because it's all fake.
It's all just, I don't want to get too much into it, but it's because it's the same organization
I love saying, if we look at the constellation in the sky through telescopes, it's interesting to think, yeah, when you see them close up, too, they don't really look like our descriptions, our classical descriptions.
They kind of look like these weird moving blobs of something, you know, almost there. I don't know. Not aliens? No.
They've come from Sudan
Which I mean, oh, which is the African slaves didn't you talking about what what slaves?
Okay
Yeah, oh if you guys want to join my discord, too, there is like a lot going on my discord
There's a lot of like sometimes they know stuff will be set on the show. Oh, is this like, you know, it's just true
It's like post proof, you know, you know, it's post proof on the discord and then
You verify some things. Okay. Oh, okay all the pyramids. Mmm. Yeah, again
There's maps there's like 300 year old maps
400 year old maps of Egypt with without the pyramids on
Like we do they do you think they would have put remembered to put at least like you know something about the pyramid on the map
I mean, or but they did put pyramids other places and they made it all shaped all kind of it is very weird
Okay, there guys. There's a lot of them
I hope it's not sacred text. You can go to like the there's like the internet book archive and there's these books and they're like
There's hundreds of books actually there's out hundreds, but if you'd like you have to kind of like
Hey summer, how are you doing if you're interested in like history and stuff like that?
You can just see these books that were written like you know a couple hundred years ago because especially
First of all you have to look at people that are writing books people that are publishing books and like wire books free publish and stuff
Have you ever thought about something called slam jobs in jail? What does that mean? Is that where someone?
What is it? What does that refer to time? I like what people say we don't know how they built them and they figure out years ago
Yeah, you said you're calling in. Oh, yeah, I want don't threaten people
J-dog
Yeah, what does it mean what are they?
Bung holes
At Oliver's the Oliver's the biggest bonghole
Yeah
Mmm, so when we eat today
Subway I just say Tuesday when I was at subway today
Hardcore BJ. Yeah, and I give slam jobs. I would totally get a slam job to
What about a really cute celly for sure
Let's see. Oh the chat is going crazy. Hey, what's up guys? Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello
That's okay. So yeah, so I was reading like some stat TV suggestions. They're like, okay
Well, how about like read cards like on the like especially because you have like the drama
It's like, you know, you can pull things by the energy of like that particular situations, but I'm just on like
You know, I think it's I think it's kind of the collective reading but it's like more the collective of this room
It's like, you know, we're kind of like it's like it's kind of like a soul soul tribe
And so we might have some things in common. So maybe this thing is something to be in common
I had subway or I want I mean, I'm playing on getting some I have I'm playing games though. It's five fifty one
Yeah, and it goes through so I'll pull some cards on the chat
We'll see what's going on in the chat.
This is just everybody here.
May, the person, the people with messages,
I'm sure you see, receive these messages.
Oh, KT, are you good?
Yep, you got the help me, help me, help me.
Yeah, yeah, thank you.
Turn up the e-ballot.
Okay, so we're just shuffling these cards.
Oh yeah, thank you, the goddess.
Yes, here we go.
I love it, I love it.
I believe that it's triple goddess, maybe Hakate.
Okay, what's going on with the chat right now?
People in the chat, look at the chat as a collective,
as a soul tribe.
Let's what do we got in common?
What is message for all of us?
Oh, oh, oh, okay, I'll take, too many cards came up.
Too many cards, okay, the message is for us.
Okay to the goose, okay
So let's do five cards for the chat and some advice. Okay. What do we got for this? What's going on with the chat?
Oh, okay temperance and so
Finding some kind of balance within ourselves, right? It's like because we got sometimes there's like the two, you know
In this duality, right? Yeah, these two
Sometimes we have the good twins the bad twin, you know
But I think instead of like starving one and like, you know, just beating the other I think maybe
We, you know, kind of like love both, love both sides of
ourselves and this learn how to kind of dance together,
like dance with it, right?
But, you know, there's, we might have two sides to ourselves,
right?
They ultimately were one, okay?
Five of swords, but it's in reverse.
And so there's been like less fighting.
It's been like, you know, sometimes this is usually
lucifer the cat, you know, throwing out all the, all the
You know, they're kind of like just like falling on the floor and the cats like, you know, upside down
You know, it's a kind of like put down our swords for a while. It's just
And not not like a not a mean battle I
Feel like we're not at war but we might
And I feel like also like I don't feel if we really are at war with anybody else. I feel like a lot of us
aren't really provoking or doing anything that we can tell but just maybe our
spirit provokes people sometimes so let's see what else we got okay seven of
coins okay seven of coins you get the chariot so what movies oh so that that
Well, it's definitely like, you know, ready for the harvest, right? It's like working on stuff and like
We're waiting for something to pay off, right?
It will it is it will pay off, right?
You have a long path ahead of you and are working hard to set your stuff up for success
Seven of coins advises you to make decisions with the long-term in mind to careful planning now leads to big rewards in the future
Okay, so yeah
plan, you know, it's like we're now now is the time to like, you know, get that page started get that
You know your show started or
You know find the job you want or do whatever you want to do if you want to be a writer
Even on YouTube, there's a million things. There's a million jobs on YouTube. You know, it's like just jobs like, you know
Not maybe jobs people are hiring, but it's like things you can
Do, you know on YouTube like right a lot
You can give advice on a lot of these things too. So I don't know. I think
It's gonna be a good place to be a plus. It's like the best platform, right? We're on the best platform
Yeah, so we have this treasure, right?
four of coins
You know
There it is. We have the jewels. We have a lot of good stuff
The point is like not just to show off and everything is to you know, actually
Treasurer and also to be generous. Okay, but realize that's what we have. Let me see four coins
It represents happiness and stability
And professionally everything within the treasure chest things are coming together nicely focused on building solid foundations that we will set
Us up for long-term success and that sounds just like the car, you know the previous card. It's like we're
It's like we're really working to set ourselves up for success in the future and now is the time
to start that business or put forth that idea, that invention, the energy, that
so many things. If you have a movie concept, then you can fill your own movies. Now you can use AI
to create movies. I mean, you can make your dreams come true yourself without these old traditional
ways, right? Could I ever have a show like 20 years ago? Could I have my own show with, you know,
30 to 100 people inside this chat talking and stuff. No, I cannot because
It was a different world, right? I mean unless I was a you know a broadcaster. Okay, so here's the advice the advice of the Empress
Okay, you know, maybe this is like his emperors. Maybe so there's some beautiful emperors. You know, this is of course
that
tangled tangled kind of wicked mother right there, you know, but
You know, there was a good there's a good harder person there. See that actually cared about tangled right, you know
He was more concerned about the hair. It seems like sometimes, right?
but
Yeah, but the hair represents that blonde
You don't want to say that youth youth forever, right, but Empress all the Queens in the deck, okay?
Whoever you are remember all the women all the women here are just definitely Queens, and I don't think they have the
This kind of this kind of make it big Linus energy
But I'm going to read about the Empress from
In this take in this deck because it is kind of a more evil Empress they have
As like Mother Gothel, the Empress is a powerful maternal figure who places a high value on beauty.
Mother Gothel uses the magic flower to keep her youthful appearance for hundreds of years.
But when the flower's magic is transferred to Rapunzel, Gothel is determined to stay young by any means necessary,
even if it means keeping Rapunzel locked in a tower.
So it says, the Empress reminds you to appreciate the beauty all around you, but remember, the beauty is more than skin deep.
Now is the time to nurture your friendships, connect with the magic and splendor of nature, gather some friends for a stroll outside, enjoy the fresh air, enchanted flowers, princesses and towers.
Who knows what magic you might stumble upon.
Hello.
What's up?
Yeah, how you been doing?
I'm doing good, Scythe.
Yo Scythe, read my cards, Scythe.
You want me to read your cards? Okay.
Yeah, I got no doubt that day you said you were going to read my cards and everybody popped up.
Okay, I'll read your cards. I'm just up there right now.
I'll put myself on bigger here.
I'll do like four cards for you. Okay, so first we got okay. We got judgment. We got judgment
Okay, so the judgment has been called on some kind of situation in your life something that maybe was unfair to you
It is now like you know judgment
I guess is like the when the horn is blown it's kind of like okay put your pencils down like you know
It's time for the judge, you know, it's the
It's time for the justice so justice also always falls in the judgment usually but so but yes
So justice is about to happen for something for you until I was unfair or I don't know if you're involved in anything legally
But it looks like that'll be resolved. Oh my god, look right after that. I pulled up the justice
Well, I
Just said that it's like it's so justice so this will definitely be following the judgment
It is the next card right after that. Like, you know, they typically are one after the other in the deck
So they are this is chronological and so you will be that's also the scales
So things are being weighed out things are being made fair and things. Yeah, definitely
You will be getting this justice for something you've been waiting for it seems like and then also
Okay, we got two of wands and stuff, but there's like there's somebody you're not coming together with that you could be coming together with I
Don't know
Wait what that's about let me see
So because you know if you do put your power with somebody
It will you know magnify both powers, but it says you being presented with a decision as a this is okay
So it says when reverse the one shows you've been caught off guard and unprepared in a situation such as your magical opponent turning himself into a germ and
affecting you with dragonpox if you're feeling bewildered or blindsided by a sudden change take a moment to center yourself assess the predicament
Adapt as necessary and keep your eyes on the prize if you stay focused you'll navigate through this and come out on top
Okay. Yeah, but it's like, you know, there's maybe there's something you're, you're
something you're not, you're not considering or something like that. Okay. And then it can't,
and then I see it could lead to heartbreak though. I don't know. Are you having problems with it?
Seems to me, maybe some kind of problem in a relationship. But it's like, the heartbreak is,
you know, never good to it can be healed. But I don't know. It's like, are you
Are you
Yeah, okay
And so and so you feel like like okay, yeah, I guess we were you powerful with this person, okay
Okay
Well, something's gonna be happening really fast. Okay. Oh, it's like, okay, so it's like you're I don't know
You're this is like kind of the feeling trapped inside your head about something and so I need some clarification on that though
Let me just get okay
Okay, so something's hidden right now because you got the moon. So it's like it's kind of saying
For the kinds of cars saying it's none of my business or it's saying
It's not to be revealed yet. It's still secret, but it will be revealed and
Okay, okay, something about your defenses, okay?
Okay, so this is like usually, like everything's protected.
This means, are your defenses,
it's something about your defenses being down, okay?
And so, I would say, you know, strengthen your defenses.
I would say, you know...
I'll just increase security, be more careful than usual,
and like right now, I'll tell you too,
the advice from the book, let me see, seven of the ones.
Reversed, it says, okay, so it says,
It says indicates you're feeling overwhelmed and exasperated, you've been working hard and are starting to lose momentum.
You've come so far, now's not the time to give up, so keep going.
Yeah, you're gonna want to keep going, like, you know, strengthen your resolve, whatever it is, because, you know,
it's like your defenses might be dead, might be down, or someone might see that, your defenses might be down.
And so, you know, you're just gonna want to...
I used to watch a lot of shows about that, you know, with the gypsy, you know, that's cool.
Okay, cool.
Now, as I always see you on reading these cards, I say, you know, let me try that.
But you asked me one day, you said, you want to be your card, other than that, I'm good.
Yeah, I said today was the day, you know what I mean?
Hope you like the reason
When I was in PA, he was a little smaller and my daughter wanted it, I grabbed it, you know what I mean, but you know what I mean, I told my daughter I didn't want, I didn't want them on animals, you know what I mean, I kept it, just I didn't want to see it in the streets.
Oh
But I told my daughter what she wanted to do with the cats, because I got a female cat and I don't want the boy cat to mate.
My female
Well, yeah, what are them fix I mean, and this keeps the cat I mean it's like
Already got three cats
Okay, we'll be careful because they can get pregnant very young and they can also
They got nine cats on your hand
And I gave it to my daughter's
And then she I made it again with the boy cat the one I found he made it with her
She had two kittens. I got rid of her the kittens when they when they started eating I gave it to um
Somebody I knew I gave it to them. I knew they was gonna take care of it
I just want to give it to the black cat
Yeah
You're doing good here. Here we go, guys. Oh, that's a safety. I'll be burning. I'll run us into my house. Yeah. Yeah. There you go. Oh, KZ. What up, KZ?
Here we go. The mic is new. What up, bro?
What up, man, can you hear me? Yes, they blocked me in your channel again, man
You know what why what would you say I?
Didn't say nothing. It's still from the same last time
What's the name I think you I think you unblock the other one, but this is like that when I use all the time now
Okay, I'll look into it. I go with my backseat
It's the KZE
Okay
Say naked twisted in your patio. I drew I did you about that J-dog. Can we play some time can be the daydream about that?
No, that's me
And I'm playing it with you
On who said something what? Oh
Well, I hope he didn't but Doug. I thought you did Doug. That was you Doug. Wasn't that you don't get to that?
Yeah, it was you that said that dog and
Please you know do that and I hope that was a little easier and gave yourself
So how's everything going good
Who's that?
Who's here and this is the LES running NYC or something. I don't know if I've been on panel him before. What's up, man?
What up?
The other day it was a nice ass like crazy. Remember that
You know the other day was crazy. Yeah, it was crazy. That's nice. You unfortunately Mike shows keeping
Okay, that's cool. Yeah
That's nice, I like that
Okay, how's that?
There's another car. Yeah, I was like
It's accurate
It was way better. Yeah, I took me off that. I took myself off the headphones. Yeah, that's good. That's good much better
Very good. Thank you for a thank you for your audio
Yo KZ I saw you a couple times on here
And I was on the panel when you was talking to him before it was just like a lot of people screaming at each other
No, I was there. Yeah
But everybody was screaming at each other. I'm like, you're the fuck and that's the follow-up and I left
Yeah, well, he's crazy around here
Yo, I didn't know you got your arms like you I didn't know you got pom-pom messity
Yeah, it was like I think Gotti and Paige were on the panel and they were just talking and then it was somebody that had a
Vader's name I just brought him up and I wasn't even looking at the screen and then it's like it was just
It was Tony I can tell I can see it
Yeah, but I got the heebie jeebies
My soul man
Laura saw me
He was outside me
I was right there outside, bro
That's how I know this
Can you hear me? Yeah
This we can't comment
Yeah, it's not dead yet, but no, I don't even want to cut it, right, if you don't cut it.
Yeah, it seems like they're having a conversation of their own. So I'll just let him come back when he's ready
That wasn't just me. You heard that too. No, no, yeah
There's like there's like there's like a bunch of people there. He says like I
Wasn't an audio problem an echo. It was just somebody else talking over. I don't know
It was just weird. He was talking about Santa Claus is outside or something. I think that I mean, uh, I mean, uh
La-La Land. Okay. All these people's podcasts brought it for p- oh, come on. Hey, DougD. Don't say that in the chat.
Yeah, happy birthday, okay, oh
Whose birthday is it? It is people's birthday today. Let me see. They said it was
You remember whose birthday it is guys? I always forget
Yeah
So what's okay? Who's this who's who's in your picture? Okay, so is that Kate? Okay, what's the fuck? No
That was Kate in this picture, was that
What's wrong with people what in the fuck
Okay, that wasn't me. That wasn't me. I had nothing to do with that case. I had nothing to do.
Yeah, can't be trusted. Sorry.
His profile photo is somebody else's and he knows that he's not supposed to have other people's, especially, you know, her.
All she does, there's no reason to do that except to try to get her mad at me for something.
It wasn't, yeah, it wasn't him.
Yeah, I think it was I think it was her. That's I don't know
Well, he can like, you know black midget somewhere else
Was it was I don't know it was it Kate I thought was Kate was not Kate
I'm sorry. Now I'm in trouble. Now I'm in trouble. No. I don't know. I don't know.
What is this picture of?
What happened?
Who is that picture of?
There's four extra.
He was that he blew off his hand on the 4th of July
He's a gang guy. I know
podcast oh
Well, I don't want his picture on my show. I would you want no jumper to be well. He's a crib
He's a crib. Oh
I'm not feeling you're in Los Angeles to shit. That's what he is my path. I'm not a
Oh
Like four fingers so that's not gonna that's gonna make me making the game sign more difficult
Oh, okay for extra. Okay. Well, maybe you can have yours. Okay. Well, anyway, I don't want to talk to you. Bye
How annoying people are oh my god
Yeah, let's bring up let's bring up gangs and get you know, let's get street gangs involved in the show now
Okay, please
I don't have problems
I I'm not anything I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm my cult leader. I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't
Is this like kind of like retarded
I prefer I don't I prefer the you know
If I was to admit gang affiliation on the show be on a watch list, so what would that be very smart to do? I'm not going to
Well, I
Thought it was I thought it was Kate Dada Doug because it is people will people put that up. Oh, he's still back there
Yeah
Yeah, I was gonna say he lost four fingers it's gonna get me doing that the gang sign harder to do you have to do with
Which one hand?
That's a bad joke. It's not funny
Okay, and anyway, maybe he's over what what is that now? What's your picture up? Who's that that Kate again?
What is that?
That was Kate. That's hilarious. No, that's uh, I just got it water some
Okay, oh nice, you thought that was Kate that is
It was Kate was that
I saw Kate's face. It was it was I'm sorry
Yeah, it was her why do you know why would you put her on the show like why would you do that?
Like why would you because she knows she doesn't like made me do it. She made me do it
Like she's he made you do it and she's terrifying. You know that
Okay
Well, I don't want her me. I don't deal with her minions right now. Okay?
I can't do with any more flying monsters right now.
Say, can you play the AI rap song for Bita?
Yes!
Oh, the one I played last night.
Oh, Bita, did you hear that one?
You were in another song, Bita, if you wanna hear that one.
Oh, I'll play that.
Here's the other song, I'll play it.
Let's see here.
This is called, it's a very sweet song.
summer walks in like a storm with a flame, a tattooed fire and a golden name, tough as steel.
Okay, that's enough. I'm sorry. It was cute. Oh, hold on. Let's see. How many measurements
does Prince play? Oh, you didn't hear that one? Okay. I'll play it. Yeah, here's your
She'll break your walls with just her smile
Christine's eyes they see it all
With wisdom deep like an endless fall and fozzy by her side
Little ball of grace their love lights up this pixel space
And every night
My sweet
Like a desert wind, laugh so loud, it pulls you in.
Drama queen with a crown so proud, she'll turn your side.
makes us whole she lives the
That's so sweet. I thought that was sweet. It wasn't kind of cringe. Stop it. Stop it.
Hi, I'm right here. Oh, oh, yes, exactly. It was cute. It was cute. It was just...
I know. Not everyone would like it. Not everyone would like it. It's highly
The I think I think it was highly accurate
But it did it knew like it knows other details and it's picked up other details without you can't see a telling it
Which is kind of cool
Yeah, that was lovely. Oh see I think it was cute
Guys there's like a million genres there's a there's a it's like the possibilities are so endless. Yeah
Christina, oh so cute. I love having the pets name. It's so cool having the
Think real song actually real song. I know that uh, it's controversial and everything, but I think it's any is cute
Oh
Yes, I mean have all the songs of my cats and I also have
Now, you know, I've had thought a lot of people are good at like something
I'm not good at instruments like playing instrument or sitting down having to concentrate and I'm not a good at that
I'm good at like
You know knowing like what
Like would be good good concepts and stuff like that
So it's like, you know, it's like you can kind of put your talent together with tech
GPT on some level and they come up with some products rather than like, you know, just dreamy, but I can like
Put things into action
Yeah, I mean I do some more more songs, you know, now I have I almost have an album, you know ready, right?
You know, maybe I'll have a
Or at least some track. Oh, I'll just give them away for free of course, you know, they're all people all be free
Yes
Uh, if you imagine
It's cute though, because it's a little personalized. You know, it's like, you know, it's personalized. You need to just go track
Yeah, you can do just go. Let's see what you can just go. Let's see what that song will be about.
Let's go through them. Oh
So
Yeah, or if anyone has a song concept they want me to try out or
some kind of thing or like suggestion you guys you can give suggestions because
it's like I'm 70 so you want to discuss something that just go in the disco
okay okay well so if someone people can type like three things early okay or
things you like about the show and so just type in what you like about the
show and I'll pick like five of them and then I'll just type in your suggestions
and do what they come out with. What kind of grown man needs shippers and
processes? Well I guess you know kind that are unmarried or the kind that are
you know would be promiscuous and have a romantic relationship otherwise it's
I want to put five things, but it's like not you don't have to think of five things that one thing from like five people
That's it. That's what I need and then I can I can start adding them
This will be this will be written by you guys so all I'm all I'm gonna do is like cast cartoon the hosts music, okay
Like that
Okay
Welcome, okay
My speedos yes, okay
Okay, let's see oh my internet out what's going on
No internet
Oh, my wife I was turned off
Principal controls are on oh shit
There's no control password
I know I had one oh
Yeah, okay
Okay, oh
He's mad at me what he's already mad at me because you keep like saying weird stuff that I don't feel like it's red
you're like
Okay
Okay, so beta. I'm looking at person sheets interview. Okay. Okay
Okay, let's see.
Let's see what else.
Let's love about the show.
Let me see.
Okay, yeah, it's time to be on the second channel, okay.
So it says, okay, let me see.
Okay, okay.
The show is always on.
No, I'm not going to say these out loud.
Cats, the curtains.
But Hold, okay. But Plugs, I'm just going to infer that one, okay. But Plugs, welcome me.
purple curtains. Okay, uh, should be a nice. Okay.
Okay, I'm a boy blue. That's a very weird thing to say. Let's see. Okay, all these
Okay, I think that's good
Okay, let's see
Oh, it uses things like things so hard.
Oh, why is it thinking so hard?
Well, I'm going to have to redo it.
Maybe because I didn't say please, I don't know.
Or you couldn't figure out what I was talking about.
shit
Okay, copy okay, I'll say please at least okay, please
Okay, what's going on?
She has CPT's and being infinity.
I don't know, my chat GPS is all messing up.
Shit.
One of those things, right?
Okay, well, I'm just gonna, it's not working,
so I'm just gonna put it in the regular,
fucking, I'll just try it over there.
Let's see.
Maybe we should make things open or something.
Perfect, okay.
I'll do it and.
I'll do the disco one, okay? Generate.
Let's see how this goes. It might be terrible because I didn't put it through the chatGPC
because the chatGPC was not working for some reason.
I don't know why, but let's see if it's making it up.
You like oh you like board games I
Play one game on a on a tablet it's called garden scapes
Okay
We're gonna need a disco song guys coming up soon disco can you see any special
Wait in the water. Wait in the water, children. Wait in the water. Something's going on in the water.
Swing low, sweet chariot. Come in the boat to carry me home. Swing low, sweet chariot.
Oh
Sorry Shakrefa didn't like that. Oh, yeah Shakrefa that are your friends with the
Big big and Nisha my my super condolences. I know she passed away
How about um, let's do another one on the leaders of Babylon when we went down
Da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da
There we sat down yeah, we wept when we remembered Zion
By the rivers of Bob, I think this is your pizza's there so one over again. Okay
Let's see I
Keep your same now up here same, but I don't like cold play and like you see in cold play. I'm losing
Okay, so now the song's ready. Are you ready to hear it guys? Let's see save mp3
We'll see how it goes. I don't know if it did it correctly or whatever. We'll see it'll be a mystery to all of us
Let's see how about
Schmjörg
Fuck my dad Schmjörg
Waiting a while. I thought that was like a church song
Guys I am by the way on rumble and kick streaming here right now as well. Go streaming. Oh, here I come on
We're just gonna work me. Okay, there we go. I mean, okay, yeah assets. Hey, we'll see how this goes
Let's see if this is like, it might be really bad.
I don't know if it's really bad.
We'll just have to try again.
Please write a cute song of my fans favorite parts of my show
Hello
Okay, so I'm sorry about that guys. I'm sorry
Guys, it's generated a new the new one. I need to I'm sorry guys. You're smiling. Thank you
Hello, hello
Turn down your microphone or your
It's a noise. Okay, there we go. Thank you
Thank you Alex, how are you?
Hello
Hi
Hi, how are you? Hi, how are you?
I'm doing well, howdy
Howdy
Howdy partner
Have you heard, oh yeah, you were here, you're not included in the song
I know, I called it, I called it, and I'm wondering why you haven't played it yet
That was the first song you made
And it was a fucking awesome song, bro, that she was dope
The other two, eh
but you had to do that pussy shit for beta i'm assuming i made it i made like eight songs so far
but i made some other good ones too but yeah but that was the first one you said right the one from
yesterday um i played the first one i played i yeah i only had one yesterday and then i sort of
made a bunch of new i made like five new ones yesterday you made it and then you cut the you
Let's see. I'm oh, yeah, so it's everyone love that shit man. It's generating a new one
He's down crisp today's people saying they like your new microphone. That's good
Okay, bye. Bye. Over. It's a very low volume. Yeah, hopefully this is almost done. Let me see
This is creating a song. Yeah, the last time
What just happened by the way, I caught that happens the song you've tried to play started playing what you asked it
That was funny
Because I guess it's just it's more special. It says they post a song ideas and stuff like that in there
But it's like I would like make a song of my fans favorite part of my shit
No, I was like shut up
Yeah, but uh, yeah, so it hopefully it'll I
Play no song. Don't be scared of beta. Don't be scared of beta because it says she dances with a bottle
I'll play let me see if I'm crazy
You like the card the kid though. There's one called madness number one called crazy. I think
Don't want me taking flight
This one that one's still
Yeah, this is it
trash then she flips rage queen mad at me girl please the show runs on caffeine
Sykes twisted laughing loud whiskey in his veins slurs flying left and right we
cut the feed no shame but the chats on fire can't tame this flame this ain't
your mama's podcast this a runaway train welcome to the madness buckle up
tight boob flashing on cam chat losing their minds Michael getting dawned Alex
taking flight it's wild it's wrong and we do it every night
She's got them simping hearts in the chat
But she ain't got time for a dude like that
Diamond flirting hard, let the girls react
It's a freak show, party, no filter, all facts
Yo
Yo Michael drops a line gong not tonight Alex tried a joke boom sent into the night panel looking sideways
Someone's got a fight producers on mute praying this don't spike diamonds feeling spicy shirts slipping down low
Oops, she says with a wink. That's the whole show sides half asleep. I still cracking jokes
Slurred out wisdom with a bourbon so glow no rules just rolls
We pretend to play one hand on the mute of the letting it spray
Circus a riot a beautiful mess one wrong word and we're trending in the press
Welcome to the madness buckle up tight boobs flashing on cam chat losing their minds michael getting gong to alex taking flight
It's wild it's wrong and we do it every night page got him simping hearts in the chat
But she ain't got time for a dude like that diamond flirting hard let the girls react
It's a freak show party. No filter all fact
Lights out one more round, beat is on the line, yelling at a ghost from a bottle of wine, we laugh, we cry, we crash, rewind, same time next week, you know the vibe.
that's a number one hit single
of the album
welcome to the madness
okay
now my computer is acting up
now it's not trying to download
or anything
i won't confuse you more i'll be back later
thanks for that
okay
sorry guys
i'll do it for my phone
technical difficulties
okay
Yeah, that was a nice one. I liked that. Okay, I was just fine. He's not confusing always little flustered. Okay
Oh, you didn't like it, it's okay. It's okay. Everyone's gonna like everything
Okay, now this works, okay, so
Oh
No wonder
It's okay. Everything's just falling apart, don't worry.
Everything's fine.
Yeah, are you being nice? Are you being nice Canada track?
Be nice, okay
I know you do I know I can tell that that you can't right I
Pick that up I picked up right away
Okay, it's uploading
We shall see who should be our sounds okay, I tell I can just tell your fans of your fan of Benny's
Food number one
beautiful mess where the trivia is rigged but we still say yes purple curtains swaying mods
holding the line with psyche at the helm and everything's fine
Every
Psyche's world. These are gonna be fucking that was a banger guys. I have my first album in one day
Amazing what she is amazing. It was great. I like these songs
Thank you guys
That was your song and Psyche's world
They're they're able to like talk about like I just said like
cheating at trivia and they were able to come over like three leers about
Cheating on trivia Google in hand
Hi, babe
Don't you both that yeah, I
Wanted to do like
When it does tell me more tell me more
Yeah, it's inchable. Yeah, it's actually I don't know
He did play out in the turnblad and hairspray
Hmm someone just came in the back, but I missed them
Your player and you get played but that's the cause called karma my sweetheart. It's called karma
The trick is don't play with people
Then
Right, so you play with it at least there's no better. I don't know
Yeah, okay, so
So what is it? Who's they talking to? Like how sick is this on rumble like in a rumble chat room?
Probably have you seen a flight logs everyone's on those like in flight logs Beyonce
horny love
Everyone else we're going to look at two people. No, there's like hundreds of people a lot of people even Spielberg, I believe
Hey
I can't I don't want to let it talk about that because I heard people's reading a stream still either for telling
I'm so I don't I mean you can talk about a chat, but you just uh on a
Me me comment or say in the names when I'm not going to really just have something it but it won't come first
And it would have said it won't come on to my stream yard because and so how would I even it has to be on rumble and stream
Oh, no shirt
i like it hello hello yo hi how are you um
you know are you okay yeah man yeah okay yeah out of me no i just yeah for sure bro are you good
I'm good. I'm good bro
Yeah, what you were just about to talk about I'm gonna talk about it without talking about it. I had a big realization about
Don't worry, I'm not even gonna make sense unless you had been listening to you but that list
I don't think that everybody on it did anything bad like
You got to think like
That guy was like a quote-unquote
Financier and a quote-unquote like scientist researcher. So some of those people I
Like I don't think Stephen Hawking went out there for weird shit
I think he really went out there for a science seminar and I think that might be the problem with it is that
If people who are legitimate and doing legitimate business were dealing with that guy for things that weren't
You know what you're thinking of then
A lot of people could really get their whole lives fucked up over
The one thing he did, do you know what I mean?
Which was well, which one thing he did like having the 14 year olds and massage therapist or what? Oh
I'm sure he did all that. I all I'm saying is that like
He wasn't just doing that kind of business. He was also a quote-on-quote
financier and like a science
Lancer yeah, I mean he had him he had him he had a math to use a math teacher at
My you or something wasn't he wasn't he like a math or something like yeah, so I just mean
I think there might have been people who dealt with him outside of his weirdo shit and
Those people don't necessarily want the list to come out because they could be like yo
I am not a pedophile, I was working with him over whatever found me a shan or charity.
Is that what you even make him accused of on a list?
I don't think so, it's not even, it's just, it's not.
But don't just think if they release the list, there's got to be people on that list who aren't necessarily bad people.
But if they release it, they're going to be bad people.
Well, yeah, I don't know are people good people. I mean they already had the flight logs released and nobody really cared
And they're gonna love people on the flight logs. That's a fair point
Yeah, I mean, it's like
That was not already no, there's not gonna be a bombshell. It's not already known like in this case. Oh, it's alright
So someone always does this oh, you know Bill Gates with them all Bill Gates is already down the flight
We already know that Bill Gates was um
So that's already like Bill Gates and the Prince and those guys did weird shit
But I got to think a guy like Stephen Hawking was really just going out there for science
Well, I mean, Stephen Hawking is in a wheelchair.
He's a quadriplegic.
I mean, it's like, what's he going to do anyway?
He's just going to fucking watch something.
I mean, it's like, uh, maybe, maybe.
I don't think people are concerned about Stephen Hawking.
I mean, at the end of the day, I mean, he's in a wheelchair
like in his voice box.
I mean, it's like, let me know if he's alive at this point.
They could just, I don't think he is.
But that, that's just all I meant, like, was just that, like,
I don't think every person on that list is, quote, unquote,
like predator vibe.
And I think that's why it's not getting released.
Sure, ma'am in this again. It depends on like who's on the list and if they're they're having to do with keeping it keeping it off
Or like, you know if they have anybody in the courts that are working for them or politicians lobbying for them to be kept
Oh, no private like if I borrowed money like you said like if I borrowed money from that guy from my foundation
And then that list comes out and I'm like holy fuck. I'm not a pedophile. I just took the guy's fucking money
What's going on? It would suck
Like that would really suck
Well, it's like saying like, you know, everybody that like is like in business with Michael Jackson is now, you know, I'm now stony
There's a funny name, but so it's by that logic that everyone on the internet is and every everybody is right
So that's where pretty much people are right now
You're right, so yeah
So I cheated Tom Petty that they're waiting. Oh, okay
Yeah, I mean it's like all I heard about that the whole thing is like, okay, so
You feel it again or this moment. Yeah, I'll just call her right. This is the one. Yeah
I just the story says she went to these
middle school or high schools or private schools and there's all white all white
I saw all mostly white people right and then we should we go and they talked to
these girls and so they would get these girls that were 14 years old and they'd
go and they get on a plane they fly to the island you know I just I don't know
how they didn't come out a month later that just happened right you think their
parents would be aware they're flying around you know Florida onto islands and
working as massage therapist but
Okay, let's just say they would be kept all the girls were kept to the secret and then they would have the girls recruit other girls
So, you know kind of like a pyramid like where they're like, okay
Well, you don't have to be a massage therapist. You can just be a recruiter for the girls
You know and then so they bring their friends and stuff like that, right?
And so that's the story to have us believe if we all if we're gonna believe this is even true
My opinion is this is just uh, sigh up. It is just a sigh up and another thing
Violet people's emotions
If you want to watch
There's a finnish in temple on his island finnish in temple. I mean space
I'm Eric Weinstein who is a physicist
Who i'm kind of skeptical of why he's so popular right now
But he has a really good interview where he talks about
How like his meeting with the guy and how it went and what they talked about
and how
A lot of people don't like aren't looking at the bigger picture of this guy. Uh, but yeah
If you want to if you ever want to like listen to someone Eric Weinstein
He says a lot of really interesting stuff because he was apparently he was super interested in gravity
He was holding like gravitation
Earth's gravitation like seminars and stuff and having scientists and people come out and the other one was eugenics
He was really big into eugenics trying to figure out a way to like make his bloodline
Live forever all this kind of shit
So the science stuff of it is all like he wasn't just a crazy pedophile
He was a crazy guy with a lot of money who was in a lot of fucking pockets
so when you hear this guy talk about it, it's like
I mean, the pedophile shit is gross and weird, but like
They say the word PDF. Yeah, I mean we already heard we heard it
We heard about like on Fox News I thought all about how yeah, yeah, he had like this plans are like
Breeze like a bunch of babies and stuff like that
Like, you know, he's like a basically a farm for like human human beings
And he was gonna have a bloodline like take over the world or something like that
I mean, it's like some kind of like I can find the article about it. It was I mean, I was like do as a news
Um, but I will just like, I'll just call him J. E. Just for like the sake. Yeah. I know.
Sorry, I forget that word is a bad word. Um, but yeah, I'm not saying the guy's a good guy.
It's a clinical word, but it's just like, I think, I don't know if it's a good to have on the show.
Okay. So, but I'll say, you know, the craziest thing about all of it is, is your, your jizz, um,
of
a
Um
Yeah, I know he's the ms. Oh m. Oh ss ad. Okay. Anyway, he's not. No, he's not just most that he started
That's what okay. Yeah. Yeah. So it screams sigh up. Okay, but I'll also j e e
Okay, so that's e so that's 33, right the wealthy financier who was accused of sex trafficking has been an unusual dream
He hopes to see the human race with his dna by impregnating women at his vast new mexico ranch
Mr. E over the years confided to sciences and others about his scheme according to four people familiar with his thinking
Although there is no evidence that ever came to fruition
Mr. E's vision and reflected his long-standing fascination with what he had been known as
Notice trans humanism the science of improving the human population through technologies like genetic engineering and AI
Critics have likened transhumanism to a modern-day version of eugenics
But this credit it field of improving the human race through controlled breeding
Mr. E, who was charged with the trafficking of girls as young as 14, was a serial illusionist.
He lied about his identities of his clients, his wealth, his financial prowess, his personal
achievements, but he managed to use connections and charisma to cultivate valuable relationships
with business and political leaders, interviews with more than a dozen of his acquaintances
show that he used the same tactics to insinuate himself in the elite
scientific community, that's allowing him to pursue his
interest in these genics and other fringe fields like
psychriogenics. Lawyers from
not guilty to sex trafficking and not. Okay. And so, yeah.
So weird.
And it says he attracted a glittering array
of prominent scientists, including Nobel Prize-winning
Murray Gell-Mann, who discovered the cork,
the theoretical physicist and best-selling author
Stephen Hawking, paleontologist, evolutionary biologist,
Steven J. Gould, Oliver Sacks, the neurologist
and best-selling author, George M. Church,
molecular engineer, who identified genes
that can alter and create superior humans,
and MIT theoretical physicist Frank Wisek and Nobel Laureate.
The lure for the scientists was his money. He dangled financing for the pet projects.
Some of the scientists had the prospect of financing blinded them to the seriousness
of the sexual transgressions and even let them to give credence to some of Mr. Epstein's
half-big scientific musings.
Scientists gathered dinner parties at Mr. Epstein's Manhattan mansion where Dom Perignon and expensive wines flowed freely, even though he did not drink.
He hosted buffet lunches at Harvard's Program for Evolutionary Dynamics, which he had helped start with a $6.5 million donation.
Well, he helped start it with a $6.5 million donation, so of course he's invited.
Well, some of Mr. Pinker's hails held him as brilliant.
He was here, Mr. Pinker described him as an intellectual imposter.
He would abruptly change the subject.
It's missing an observation with an adolescent's wisecrack.
Wow, OK.
This is exactly what the Weinstein guy said.
He's like, it was like he was, what did he say?
Like a facade.
Like he was there presenting himself as this thing.
But if you were actually that thing,
you wouldn't be that stupid.
And he said that.
He thinks most of these scientists like you're naming off probably went out there and we're like this guy's crazy
And never talked to him again, and it sucks that they're on his lists. Yeah
That's like a typical of a you know
Con artists like how they how they're gonna be but there's many con artists that actually
And big kids at the top, you know, you can't on your way there's sure
And so I think he's a Mosad. I'm pretty sure he's a Mosad operative. So the most another really interesting thing
So like I'm really into watches and so I started being like what watches did Epstein wear and I'm looking at his wrist
And I noticed one is a Vacheron Constantine and I look it up and the one he's wearing is fake
He's wearing a fake Vacheron
So then I search up Jeffrey Epstein watches and apparently he was known all through like the 80s 90s 2000
to go and wear replicas of Rolex or Vasharall and or Clashute.
These like $40,000, $50,000 watches and all mental shit to see if he's
in a business meeting and the guy doesn't notice or compliments his watch.
He goes, Oh, that guy doesn't know my watch is fake.
It's all just like mental fucking play.
Yeah.
Super weird shit.
Seeing it's like the person, the scat, the Connors themselves or seeing
how they, how they, yeah.
Yeah, so it's interesting, but it's like, yeah, also, you know...
There's not many, there's one, I think, recording of Geoffrey Epstein, that they have, and it's just been a little,
core thing, it could be very easily some kind of AI. There's all this suspicious stuff with the death and stuff.
I mean, it's like, if you look into it, there's a lot of weird symbolism, there's a lot of little tells that I picked up over the years about
you're being told there's something more to the story. So, I remain skeptical, but, you know, it's like it is something that's riling people up,
Like you know one of those black and white things like oh, you know
So he's just has to be all bad all good. We like to put people in these boxes of like all bad all good
One thing or another right straight plan for the gay man
LFC yeah, straight plan for the gay man. Well, who's the who which gay man mr.
Phoebe stood mr. What is that? Oh, yeah? Okay?
Well, I don't know you're talking to chat
Let's see. They'll all still see or be actually buy this. Okay, so that's something that rich people will do too
They they will often have replicas and not have their actual jewelry because they are like, you know targets of being robbed, right?
So that has like for sure, but when you're Epstein you can be robbed and go buy another one
Yeah, yeah, but
You're on in the ocean and just order another one
So you're saying he's a con artist, but that doesn't make sense that he's a con artist.
And then he actually was so successful because when he wouldn't you like give up the con like unless they just love the con like
Connors like wouldn't you like kind of give that up and like be like see how we're thinking about it this much
That's exactly what he wanted. He wanted
That's a psychological operation, but it's like we talk about it
But it just be considerous not even true as part of the thing and then it's like then you can take a six in one like the like the really
Pressing concern off of it. There's no there's no emotion involved in it for me
I just look at it very cold like okay. I just look at like I have no emotion involved in it, right?
Okay, that was a show back in the day. Okay. Yeah
It's though
Cuz I think like if he went to a dinner party wearing a fake watch and then you know a couple goes home
And they're like honey
He was wearing a fake basher on and then his wife goes well, that's so his proper jewelry doesn't get stolen
Are people looking at there are people looking at they've watched that carefully. I mean, it's like I guess they give me
So watch is a whole thing in the business world. A watch is a whole yeah, it's a
It's your status. It's your income status
It's your right, right
Replicas are good for a passing glance and it's like, you know
It's like even if you're like into watches then like unless you're like you may go look at the serial number and like look for
Dolly's like things you should you think they're usually like, you know usually a lot of
And then you can then also well to people would say another wealthy person they'd be like, oh, yeah
Well, he's wearing a fake watch. Of course, you know, I wear fake watches too because you know, like I'm when I go to sort of play
I don't know. It's like I don't want to be they have my
washed stolen up, you know, somewhere, I don't know, people are concerned when you're even
in rich people, even though they can buy another thing, they don't they are probably pretty much
like some of the some very thrifty people that are, you know, they've got rich by not by spending
all their money on washes and stuff like that, they are rich, you know, through smart and smart
being smart investments, right? So it's like, so in business, like, you learn pretty early that
Having a watch is it's a little bit less now, but it's coming back because of the fucking smart watches
but so basically a watch is supposed to be 10% of your income and it's you're supposed to be able to show in
in business that
we're talking about lawyers and
marketers and stock market people and fucking top money like bankers
So it's 10% of your income and someone can look and go okay, this guy bought the Rolex
He's he's basic
But then if you're like, oh this guy bought the Vacheron Constantin 2 2 2 you're like actually he enjoys art
He's pretty smart because he found that watch and that's not cheap. So he's making this much a year
It's a whole thing. It's a conversation without talking is what the watch is in business
Well, you know and people who are up in that shit really understand it and I can yeah to all that, but yeah
Watch the conversation without talking. Okay. Yeah
So he doesn't know fashion shit. It's what that's interesting fashion high-end thing. Okay
Well, yeah, I know he is here's the clothing store. I know but yeah as for I mean, there's a lot of different
Yeah, I'm talking about business people like you know stockbrokers lawyers. They're also get better stuff in common, too
Right, so I sounds like he had the island scam course $99. Yeah
Well, I don't know. No, it's a man's shoe. It's like there are
Certain little tales and it's like, yeah, people do care about watches. I'm just saying
It's also when you find out someone only makes a hundred K a year and their watch is 25 grand
You know, they're a poser and they're not about it
Mm-hmm. Well, I'd say being so concerned about how much people are making to those two is like I'm gonna stick up there
Obviously if they're unless they're in business when you're dealing with other business partners
You want to know that there's sound financially, right?
But you'll know that they'll have a reputation for that it won't just be based on their how their watches when they walk in
I mean I'm saying they'll have a it'd be like you're not gonna like oh
Wow, he's wearing his watch might be a knock up. Oh, that's gonna be these guys want to see my watches, so I'm gonna show them
This is a Candino 24 Jewel automatic doesn't need to be wound. It's from the 70s.
This is a smaller Candino automatic Swiss made. It's an old Navy watch. This is a self winding
so you have to wind it every 36 hours. This is a citizen eco drive. This is like a $600 piece.
It's solar powered so light and sun keep it going. It never dies. It's made of titanium
This is a young Hans, this is a German 17 jewel fucking
Artifact that you just don't fucking have this is called a max bill. This is like a thousand dollar watch and
The guy telling me that I've got a fucking Cassio can fuck off
because this is from before he was born it's German it's got a ceramic dial and to be honest
the uh yeah the art deco vibes on this below that guy's mom out of the water
and then um I've got like a basic Nike digital for when I want to be sporty that's from 1999
uh and then I got like a whole case of shit that I'm working on too because I also
work on watches and restore them.
This is a Swiss Anacar made in the 70s,
if you like Miami Vice.
It's like another, you know, that $600,000 watch, all Swiss.
Man, I'm automatic
This is a kinetic watch
So this watch has a battery in it
but it winds
by shaking it and
Then this is the Russian war watch right here, buddy. This is what this is what the fucking Russian pilots wore
24-hour self-winding motherfucker. It's a Rakita
Yeah, I've I just showed you guys like three to five grand and watches
There you go. You have a fan
Sounds plastic
Hi, he ignored you cat cat. I'm sorry
Yeah, I'm not over here. Just like spilling gas on watches because I
I do like I'm a watch guy
This is a Rolex Submariner. It's made out of solid gold. It's not a blue
It's not a blue
35 grand, you know, let me see the face. That's my can of chew. I'm a hillbilly loser. Oh
This is the best I could do
It's a submarine or an explorer. It's a Submariner
That's all that's fucking hard bro solid gold not the bluesy. That's an old man's watch
I don't like the blue. I got the black dial got the black dial
That's sick man. That's really nice. Did you is it a was it passed down to you or did you buy it or what's the story?
I bought it, bro
That's sick, man
Thank you. How many years ago? Oh less than a year ago. Oh, wow
Yeah, I'm working on another one the white gold Pepsi with a blue dial
And people bro, you're like I I appreciate replicas too. You're not just fucking with me like I could be a rap
It's not a replica. All right. We're
Yeah, I wouldn't I wouldn't do that
There are some pretty pretty good reps out there these days though
Yeah, no, I I paid 35 G's for it's not you paid 35. So you went you went gray market
Yeah, it's cheaper gray actually
They're like really yeah, they're cheap. Yeah, the the solid gold subs are cheaper on the gray right now
So the GMT's
Interesting. Yeah, it's good time to buy them
That's all safe. Mm-hmm. That's all good. Yeah. Bye
Okay, why better than oh
Yeah, my father was a big watch guy
I mean, you know in Capricorn's two are known to it's like watches. It's supposed to be a good gift for us because you know
Saturn time
But uh, I don't like to remind it at the time sometimes I like to I don't even like to know what day this sometimes right?
Unless I have to
They're making basic losses with Rolex and then this stuff. Oh, wow. Christine is your Rolex automatic
So the reason I have so many watches is because they're all going towards my Rolex
And I'm pretty sure I'm just gonna get a fucking oyster date for eight grand because I don't need a $25,000
Submariner
Or a GMT
I don't dive, you know what I mean.
The thing that's so sick about a Rolex,
like Christine had her's passed down for 25 years,
like I want to be able to get a Rolex
and then give it to my kid
and then he can give it to his kid
and it'll just be in the family.
I have a Pulp Fiction style, right?
Didn't you say you had a watch from your dad's like didn't you tell me that or
Was it just that your dad had a watch? He had watches back. I do have one
I think I have a fake Rolex or something. I don't know. I think you give me one. I don't know. Yeah, I
Didn't get any of his watches
Yeah, so if I make any cool watches that I believe, you know, I'm more of a
Ring person, but I'm not even wearing rings right now. I know jewelry, huh? I remember your oldest granddaughter. Do you wear gold or silver?
Do I well, I know I like I do I think silver is the gold to me looks
Kind of more brown. I like I like platinum
Yeah, same bro, and like white gold. I can't wear yellow gold on my skin
Yeah, and
But yeah, I haven't had during a while. So it's your sneaker collection. I wear my dad's I did get my dad's sandals
And so I wear my dad's working stocks. That's and I'm wearing them for like a year
They're not molded to my feet
Working stocks are nice shoes
Whether they be either vegan or something like that
But shoes my shoes here's my shoe. I bet Christine's Rolex is a little ladies date. Just
Bit of a smaller dial, but the same like the nice Datejust
A lot of guys are actually starting to wear the ladies Datejusts too because they're smaller, but they look cool
Well, that's that that I might judge a guy if I was in that's great
And the guy came in with a woman's watch would be like, okay
What's his name Timothy? Is it Timothy Charlemagne or whatever that one famous guy?
He's been wearing a lot like really dainty watches and I don't think it looks bad at all
Yeah
Well, my my wrist is so skinny like I don't like it. What I have to have a watch is all tight always tightened, right?
And I could use a very dainty watch. I bet same bro. Yeah, I
Don't think yeah, yeah, Christine. I believe you I know the watch it was really popular
In that era too like
Well, if you ever watch madman, you know, you know
Okay, watch they're out of fashion with silicone now. Yeah, well now that we have like, you know
Now they are kind of an old-fashioned kind of accessory and I know there starts for certain people that just love them
You know, it's like a it's like a status symbol. It's like a you know
They really want to buy that first watch that's gonna be big a big deal for a lot of people there
Then there's people that are coming back, you know why like the fun. Yeah
Because everybody's wearing fucking Apple watches
And then they go, wait, I don't have to wear my Apple watch all day, and I'm used to wearing a watch.
So then they start looking at other things, and it's like, actually the Apple watch turned people on to wearing things on their wrist again.
Yeah, I mean, it's like, again, and there's the Apple watch and the Casio, those are pretty like, you know, like, you know, this plasticky, uh, efficient watch.
It's a work watch. It's great. It tells time. Yeah, but it's about really the function.
And if you work in construction or a trade, when you're doing your job,
you don't want to pull out your cell phone. If you look down at your wrist and you see the time,
it's so nice. And when you're in the middle of a job, you're just like, oh, there's the time. Okay,
I think we should just like, you know, we can also put like a sundial on our chest and we can always tell the time
But looking at the shadow. That would be pointy
Yeah, that would be me hugging it would make, you know
Do you think a rhinoceros can tell the time by like on its nose?
I don't think so because they don't probably I don't have a concept of time. That's more of a human. Yeah, that's a good one
You just you're right psych
Right. I know I am
I know I am
Nossers, yeah
Whoa, be a unicorn a unicorn can't fake it. You can't see the top of its head though to you
We look at the Sun and tell time. No, we can look at the shadow it casts
usually
And this is the night time then it's like the shadows too dark
Yeah, I guess animals just know by looking at the Sun. They're like, oh, it's dark it soon
Well, it's like we really do have like just like animals. We have like an innate sense of the time like we have a really kind of can
Can know we kind of like just
You know, we were like naturally assumed to it, but you know, you always have to create an extra step
Watch man the other night I got off here and I walked to the store for some pop and I found a dog behind the
gas station and I ended up spending
The next six hours sitting outside with this dog
Trying to find an owner and not wanting to leave it alone. It was a small it was such a sad experience
Why are you laughing? Oh
Right, right. No, I was laughing a little bit. So the okay
So this dog bro, I'm like walking to get a pop and it runs out at me barking
And I thought it wanted it was like trying to leave me somewhere and it brings me back behind the gas station and there's a bike
And I'm like holy fuck
So I'm looking around and there's no owner or anything no tag
But it doesn't want to leave the bike that it's by and it's like trying to get me
Can't even explain it bro. It was a smart lab, and it like wanted my help, but I didn't know how to help it
so we ended up just
Sitting there for hours
Until I called animal care, and they knew the dog and it's this homeless guy's dog
Um, I knew it is by the you just on the phone Wow
Yeah, like when I described it and told so it didn't have a tag on the call-up caller
But I had like a Toronto Maple Leafs tag and so I said I also live in a much smaller city than you guys
But I just said I was like this dog and they're like yeah
We've actually picked that dog up before it's a homeless guys dog
and
So I guess they got it back to him
But it was just so crazy man like
At one point, so I've been sitting there for three hours with this dog because I didn't want to leave it alone. It was so scared, and I was like, alright, I'm going to go home and get a leash and bring it back and try to walk the dog to my house.
So I went out, I came home, I went back, dog is in the exact same spot, just sleeping.
and I hooked up this leash and started to walk
and it looked at me and just ran right back to the bike
as if to say like, I can't fucking leave this spot.
So then like Animal Care came and put it in the truck
and it just would not wanna go.
It was like its owner told it to stay there
and it stayed there for fucking eight hours, bro,
like in the same spot.
Brought it food and water
Anyways, I wanted to fucking take the dog home and give it a new home, but I think he's pretty attached to his homeless owner
I'm sure that they help each other out, but it was I
Don't know. I like animals
Yeah
You just like me, you know, I mean about about one of my friends have he's homeless and he have a dog and
I told him it's a bully, and you know, she's cute and shit.
I told him, you know, can I take the dog?
And he, you know what I mean?
He feed the dog, he take care of it.
But he said, nah, but that dog, his dog, you know,
like when he leaves, that dog get up and follow him.
And he told the dog to stay there or stay there
with no problem.
Mm-hmm. They're really I know I understand what you mean. Yeah, I understand what you mean
But some homeless people do take care they don't oh
He did it's like I mean the dog had some
Like a bit of mange and maybe fleas and one of its ears was a little swollen
But I mean that's living on the street, you know what I mean, but
Yeah
That's from the rain and all that stuff when it rains hard and the water on the ears they get on air mites
Well, and the other thing I thought about if I was homeless and my dog needed to go to the vet
I'd tell it stay here and
Then animal care comes and picks it up
And then you go in the morning and pick up your dog and they've already given it some free care
Yeah, that's right. Yeah
So that might have even been what was happening that maybe he knew that the dog needed to go see a vet
But he didn't have the money so he's like listen bud you stay right here
Now, but I know
I don't know what you I don't know you from but some veterinarians. Have you homeless? They do help the homeless out
For sure. They've started to a bit here. I live in Ontario like South of Toronto. Oh
That's a different state
Yeah, I'm in Canada for sure, but
Now as I see a lot of homeless people who have dogs and they take care of them and when they get sick
I don't know how they pay the bill, but they make it a way in the house to take care of their dog
Okay, you know
That's why the dog stays with them, you know
Yeah, it was the dog wanted company like it would it wanted me to stay with it. It was so funny
Now I find I'll be finding dogs and cats and all that shit and then when I when I find like a little dog
I'll call animal shelter have them take them and they find them a go home sometimes
Well
There are a lot of dogs on the street. So yeah, that's always a good
Shelter yeah shelter animals are some great animals to adopt if you're looking to adopt animal
They're really animals. Yeah, totally. Yeah, well, that's the thing man. This dog was so well trained. I and
smart like
Yeah, I
Was weird
Mm-hmm, okay 28 80 talks midnight or she loses. Oh, okay, so oh be that how's it? How's your back going?
Tell me yeah, I don't know. I think someone did tell me about a YouTube video where a dog is told to wait
And the guy never comes back and the dog dies waiting and this dog was definitely like that where it like
it
It would it stayed in the exact same spot for fucking eight hours like I couldn't I
Couldn't believe it
I'd walk home and get a coffee and come back and check on her and she'd still just be laying there
Yep waiting for someone
But I'm sure like I've had a lot of dogs, I'm sure if I told my dog to fucking
Stay and wait and I didn't come back for eight hours. My dog would be like fuck that guy. I'm going somewhere
Yeah, it's like almost there's a story of like an elephant the elephants change up when it's a baby, you know, and then it's like, you know, and so
It's you know, the chain keeps it in the same place
But then it gets big and it's still chained up, but it's not strong enough to break the chain.
It could break it actually kind of easy if it's just like, you know, pull its head a little bit or force it,
but it's like, but it just, it has, it lives in the limitation of the chain thinking that it still has the chain on,
or the chain is still has the power over it, and even though it's more powerful than the chain at that point, and so,
yeah, and so that's what, you know,
We are like sometimes
No, but the limitations we place on our cells are the biggest ones
Really aren't the obstacle our biggest obstacles ourselves really
Hey summer hey summer
The loss with JD sports
Yeah, I'm not doing no lawsuit, but that's suck now that
You can make fun of that all you want, but losing one of my favorite jobs I've ever had
really sucked
Especially because it was for doing something I thought was good
So psych you heard about that, right?
Well, which job was this?
So I was selling sneakers there for a while
Mm-hmm. I was like helping manage JD sports supervisor
Visual visual manager
mm-hmm and
One day I was working and these kids ran in
Well, yeah, I'll have it up. I
Did tell you this right? Yeah, I do remember but go ahead you can tell again if you want it's like you but no
But just you're making fun of me you're asking if I'm setting a lawsuit. It's just like no
I just hate getting fired which suck
Yeah, but yeah, I and it was like I grabbed a pile of clothes back
Yeah
Yeah, I know
Well, we were always told in like loss prevention like not to ever chase and I wouldn't say they leave the store
You don't like leave the store you're supposed to chase and I'd be dangerous for us and stuff like that for sure
And there's lawsuits and stuff that were involved with the chasing amount and stuff
So and it just wasn't explained to me. So like I started at that place in the back of house
basically
Organizing all the sneakers in the back stock and then they put me up on the front
And they didn't really give me a lot of front-of-house training because I've already ran a store
so I know how to sell and
It was also like, you know, if it was my store, I
Buy all the prop me and my girlfriend buy all the product for our store
So if someone takes a fucking shirt from my store, I'm running down the street after them
I don't give a fuck, but I don't have a corporation policy over my head
So I was kind of think like it was just instinctually. I just grabbed the shit
I'll never do it again. I learned
Think that it that's how you supposed to do it, but it's like yeah
Because all these
This is like even like really not crazy world where like there's been like burglars who have fallen off someone's roof
And then suit suit the people for like, you know for her damn. Yeah
Yeah, totally
So it's like, yeah, it's kind of going crazy a little bit sometimes, but
Something to use as races and shit. Wow
Grabbing a shop was a good way to get to you exactly
Which is why they I
Think I and I agree if you injure the shoplifter they can sue you but like even in this case
I didn't even touch the shoplifter. I only touched the pile of clothing that was piling out of his hands
So I mean if he wanted to try and press charges the camera wouldn't show him getting hurt
It would show him not leaving the store with the clothes and you probably wouldn't win a suit
But oh my god. Hey, what's up guys?
And I agree
Yeah, I suppose to grab them, it's like it's very legal to do that, being in, it's not a good idea.
Talk to your loss prevention, they may even say the store is lost anyway, so it's not, you don't want to get involved.
Oh, 100%, and I thought about that after too, I'm like, gee, you can lose as much as they want, I don't know how my job is.
The kids who rush the store?
Oh, well that was happening all the time over here like they're rushing all the stores. Yeah, but I think it's like
That was all that was all set up by other organizations do that, but
In order to organize crime and in my city, it's a Syrian gang
Specifically that's been targeting a couple malls
And they have a group of young kids that go in well the older guys sitting cars outside and it's funny
Well, it's not funny, but I had this guy come into the store
right before these kids run in and
He walks in staring at his phone and walks to the back of the store staring at his phone
And I said to him I was like hey man
Can I help you out with anything and he just looked at me and kept walking
And I'm like why the fuck would you enter a store that you want to shop in and keep looking at your phone?
And then I realized he was letting the kids know like come now. He was not there to shop
So it's like this weird like organized thing and apparently they're they definitely scope out the scene definitely
They don't know what time to come in yeah
It just, yeah, I mean, they can, yeah, I, I wish I had have known all that before I grabbed the clothing, because I needed that fucking job.
So.
Yeah.
Well, they say hindsight is 2020, right?
So anyway.
He's seen him to come out. There's no I'm being it to stop it. Oh, yeah
But no, they were asking if I'm suing and it's like no, I'm not
It's moving on with my life
Okay, there's other jobs, you know
Yeah, it doesn't feel like it you're right for yourself
I do that a bit. Okay. Um, let's see. Who's putting dishes away? I think it is Canada
Dryers. Oh, I was putting dishes away. Is it too noisy? I'm just going to cook dinner
They're just they don't put their dishes away, so they're all trippin out
That's the sound dishes make when you put them back in the cupboard. I leave mine on my counter full of shit
Man, I lived with this fucking guy once who couldn't clean up after himself and he'd just throw plates in the fucking garbage
If a plate like got too crusted instead of washing it you just fucking throw it out
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. I keep, I'm starting to kiss him. Kiss him a little while.
I bet there's some people in the chat right now that relate to that.
Anyone relate to what he's saying about putting away your dishes?
Your emotions already prove you're drinking? Let me see.
You know the sound? Yeah. Christy knows the sound.
I know the sound. I've heard of that sound. It's just dishes clanking.
Emptying the dishwasher.
Yeah
Trying to get my try to get some merge set up
I have the logo, you know, and so I'm trying to put the have like the stuff set up
I'm just trying to figure out how to fill it on my my page, you know
Do dropshipping with like printify? Yeah, I mean it's like that's that's that's the things that on
YouTube they work with like he's bringing and they Shopify and they all them, you know
I just yeah, it's like I just working on integrating it and it's like not the easiest thing, but I'm working on
Let's you don't a pan addition today. Yeah, I
Have to you know, sometimes when I got too bad. I would ask
I made it by dollar store stuff in a store everything away. Hey, cut. This is yeah
Kind of easier. Yeah, when you're single and living on your own having like one set of dishes or having paper plates. It's ideal
Yes, oh
Lola
Had his purin you can have it read yourself while doing dishes. Oh, it's okay
Am I am I really too loud like yeah, you're too loud you're too loud
Listen. Hi. I put something for you backstage. I don't know if you saw it. It's a link.
And if you like watches, like if you're like to repair them and like, you know, just like interested in like antiques and stuff like that, watch that.
It's really cool. He's from Canada. Yeah, you'll like it. I was like addicted to, I think I've seen every single episode of every single one of this show.
to watch it in one sentence, but he would go to like estate sales and then he would look in the back of like standard watches and he would find like to roll like, you know, engines and movements.
That's sick.
Yeah, that's so funny that you know about that stuff. Are you into that or you just stumbled on it?
Yeah, I stumbled on it because um, I like to see him doing like a state like looking for like other
specialty is watches and
Eventually got like so good at it that now he just deals with like antique cars
Now he like takes cars apart and he buys like, you know old-ass cars like okay?
Yeah, but he's still one of his passions and he's got a huge watch collection of himself
He's from Canada from Alberta
Oh, wow. Yeah, I'm definitely going to check that out.
Yeah. Thanks, Bita.
No worries. What are you guys doing?
I like that you know about the movements.
Like I'm sitting up here talking about watches and not one person mentioned movement and you come up here like, yeah, it's got all the old Rolex movements.
It's like, ah, Bita knows what's got.
Well, I could see the glow in your eyes when you were showing your pieces.
So it's like something you definitely like.
And yeah, that's a good investment, you know.
for sure. What are you doing, Saiki?
Making AI, you're welcome.
Designing some products for my store.
Some more?
I'm just doing some fashion design right now.
What are we going to get in merch and stuff?
Well, it's soon because I'm designing it some stuff now.
Like, I have a fish taco design.
I have, like, I put my logo on one of them.
It'll just be like, I have a sticker.
Let me see, a sticker.
You can make these little key chains that look like little
tacos and they have that like, you know, they kind of that
eraser feeling and then in the back of it, it's a sight to
it, you know, whatever people can hold it on such a door. Yes.
Send me a bunch of stickers and I'll run around and I'll stick
it all over like the stop signs. I really will. I have a
sticker. I'm gonna do stickers. I'm gonna do the mugs. I'm
Speedos speedo. I don't know if they have I don't see them here. I don't see speedos here, but maybe I
Would you know?
Let's see. Okay, so accessories they have what do they have they have I can make
I won't scroll down
Oh, yeah. Okay. So there's stickers, jewelry, bags, and footwear.
I would love to design your jewelry if you would let me send you some sample pieces.
Okay. Yeah, I don't know if they have it through.
We've talked about this.
We could do it on, and I could sell it on the show.
Yeah. I'll make you some stuff for yourself.
You like bracelets and stuff like that?
Mm-hmm. You never wear like jumps on bracelets. Okay. Yeah, I like them
I thought for the butthole scam. Yeah, no butthole scam. Yep
Never again. Okay. I do. Okay. Can you listing name of my design? This is called the Lenore
logo
Okay, and
description
The
Nor
Lenores the cat
Logo, okay, and
Yeah, the Norris, okay, so
Let me see if it launches
Then I guess oh, I think I launched it. Oh my gosh generating product images dating product images. Oh cool. I
Think I have maybe put the first listing up guys
and then oh look
My first sale is live. I'm gonna
Let me see, where is that?
On the, you know,
that logo.
Oh cool, so you already did it?
Congratulations.
Yeah, it's going to be on the
product right there, and then you can go
Um, Jenna, let's see if it's connected to my store yet.
I like the design too, because it reminds me like I'm an Egyptian style cat.
Mm-hmm. Yeah, I thought it, yeah, it's just huge. I was thinking that too, actually.
Um, let me see. Okay, so then I go to the integration, the back thing.
I might be able to do it right now. Let me see.
Man it's products
Display products you store. Oh, no, I don't see it yet. Oh, we've got the stores up
Wow, okay
Man, I was not he just tried to grab my hand and freaking kiss my hand and then try to freaking. I don't know
I'll do me or something
I would have been creeped.
Let's see.
Uh-oh.
Okay.
What?
I don't know how to do this, but I'll figure out later.
So, beta, okay, now that, okay, so why does the logo looks,
yeah, looks much better than what made it big.
Okay, well, it's like AI is pretty amazing.
I don't know why they look different or anything.
There was a different, but it was Canva,
they put the size, it makes the size perfect.
You know, I'm sorry, hold on, perfect.
You made one AI song, but I don't know if you knew
whether you were muted or...
Yeah, maybe.
...all together, I'm not really sure what happened.
Okay, which one was that guys, you know, it was the one that was like all the chatters were giving recommendations of
What we should be in the song. Do you remember that one? Yeah
Anybody hear that or no, sometimes no, it was not
When you try to play it, but oh
Maybe what I knew when I knew maybe amused the whole thing. I thought it didn't you my microphone
You put all that hard work into it and then you played it and we didn't hear anything
Guys, did you anybody hear anything or no, but why didn't no one someone said anything like it's not playing everybody did everybody person
It was like you're muted. Yeah
Okay, hold on. I'll play it again
You guys here
beautiful mess where the trivia is rigged but we still say yes purple curtains swaying mods
holding the line with psyche at the helm and everything's fine
I'm good
I'm good for that
What the- what- what- what are you cooking bro?
What are you cooking?
Little uh-
I'm trying to fool you cookin' bro
I'm gonna do a chicken breast
with some mashed potatoes and carrots
A little breaded chicken breast
Oh, shit
That's nice
Ha ha ha ha ha
If you're not a cat, just pull up a chair
It's like you, what are you laughing at?
It's my song, can you hear it?
Huh?
It's a song!
Oh, it's a song?
Oh, it's good.
Look at the shape of that.
That's a nice vibrato.
I did J1
Love and lore
Welcome to this world, and welcome to this song.
That's amazing.
I love it.
I liked it. I thought it was very cute.
I like it too. It was beautiful.
Yeah, I like the part where it's a person cheats on the trivia and then
Saxon
Yeah, it is love and lore, you know lawyers, you know, you have here my my lore. Wow. It's like already it's
Okay, can you explain to me what love and lore means?
Lord Lord is like your seat lower is like the story your story like right?
Yeah, and there's mythology I tell mythology
Okay, yeah, all right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I'm live something like that. That's right
Sike those awful lay us off for a beat up
I did I did he did he did like a lot of them
They were all really funny from he went from this thing to like a really sweet loved one. It was adorable. How are you Jay?
Okay, I don't I didn't know that all right cool. Yeah, Jane one. I'll play I'll play again later
Okay, for sure, okay, was that you that came in here and showed your Rolex earlier
No, that was
Just some random guy
Do you hear
Say what about Alex you made a song with him right was there a video of you and Alex
Yeah, there's a video
But yeah
Being told what to do I do it all the time. I come up here. I'm like play this and he's like I'll do it later
It's not played. It's because his ego doesn't like that
He doesn't like that. No one comes up being tells you to play this and that I don't psyche better. He knows himself, bro
My back
My back Alex. Okay, you're you're fine. Yeah, so play it. Just play it
But she one wants to hear a song of me and beat up that he hasn't heard yet
It's a good choice quote madness. Welcome to the mad man
Welcome to America
But the chats on fire can't see me one. It's a freak show party. No filter all facts
Yo Michael drops a line gong not tonight Alex tried to joke boom sent into the night
Panel looking sideways. Someone's gonna grow producers on me praying this don't spike
I'm feeling spicy shirts
Oops, she says with a wink. That's the whole show sides half asleep. I still crap. Yo, J1
You want a cat wisdom with a bourbon so glow? No rules just rolls. We pretend to play one hand on the mute other letting it spray
A beautiful mess, one wrong word and we're trending in the press
Welcome to the madness, buckle up tight
Boobs smashing on cam chat, losing their minds
Michael gettin' gong to Alex takin' flight
It's a long and rude every night, page got him simpin' hearts in the chat
But she ain't got time for a dude like that
Diamond flirtin' hard, let the girls react
It's a freak show, party, no filter, all facts
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
Yeah, I didn't hear that.
I heard it over and over again.
But then I realized I was bad.
Played so much song.
What was that?
I played it.
I started for later.
I mean, not later, earlier.
You're good.
I'll talk about it later.
My baby.
Oh, here comes my cat while I'm trying to fucking cook.
Wow!
Look at this little Hitler stash.
Oh my god, you got a tuxedo.
Aww, it's cute.
That one looks like my Mickey.
Oh, yeah.
Who's Charlie?
So cute.
Meow.
Who doesn't have a cat? I know Summer has one, Sax, me, of course me and Psyche, who else?
We're all cat people up in here. I like dogs too, but everybody has a freaking cat.
Yeah, cats. Kitty cats. Yeah, I love the city on my left. I was going to say cats don't drool,
but that's not necessarily true. I've had a couple cats that were big droolers.
Yeah, my cat will sleep sometimes like once in a while and he's so cute. He'll wake up and he had a little Julie on his fur
Hey, did you choose? Yeah, the one that looks like yours with the long hair. Yeah, those guys they usually are droolers
Or if you give them like a treat they're already drooling
But thank you for all the fun. They're all cute. Thank you all fine. Oh, you're welcome
I'll make some I'll make some more in the future. I have all this month. I'll make I'll make them
I can make the 300 or something so we'll have all tons of fun
Let's make one for the chat like all the chatters
Okay. Yeah, what do we want with everyone's name for everyone's name in the song or a lot of people's
We see
Yeah
Have a summer song. I mean, I made a beat a song today. I'm gonna make I'll make up
I'll make songs for people. It'll be cool. I'll be good. We good
Have it's a fun
Here I say hi Lola say hi. Oh, hey, oh, here's a dog and I was standing
But that was my cat yelling
Yo, what's up psyche? How you doing man?
Polices here military police and so
I want to know why LES was talking over the phone
What does he have no respect is he jealous or just plain stupid
How you talking about buddy
The song the psyche just played that summer came up and said yo, why were you talking we couldn't hear it
When you're trying to talk to j1 he wasn't answering because we were all listening to the song but nobody got it
That song the why did your monkey asked not registered that we were listening to a song and you're supposed to shut the fuck up
And when you talk you shut the fuck up you dumb clown motherfucker
That wasn't what I asked
Don't talk shit Alex. Don't talk shit. Don't you scare yourself my nigga. Don't talk shit
Let's get away. It's for me. No why bro. No lie
What come on? Oh my little nigga use chronic little bitch
The same way I was crying like a little bitch. He was crying like a little bitch. Shut the fuck up already
Fucking idea what this man is talking about right now. You know what I'm talking about. I don't have to say no more
What was like Brian so I can make fun of myself
You don't want to fuck about Alex.
I actually, I don't.
No, you always get mad, and it's not, you know, I'm not.
No, I'm not
So I asked you why you took over a song like a pussy and now I'm crying like a little bitch
So what are you talking about? You was bro? I was
When and where when and where?
You want to make it a dang court
But you know what I'm talking about, you know what I'm talking about, you know what I'm talking about, you know what I'm talking about, you know what I'm talking about, you know what I'm talking about, you know what I'm talking about, you know what I'm talking about, you know what I'm talking about, you know what I'm talking about, you know what I'm talking about, you know what I'm talking about, you know what I'm talking about, you know what I'm talking about, you know what I'm talking about, you know what I'm talking about, you know what I'm talking about, you know what I'm talking about, you know what I'm talking about, you know what I'm talking about, you know what I'm talking about, you know what I'm talking about, you know what I'm talking about, you know what I'm talking about, you know what I'm talking about, you know what I'm talking about, you know what I'm talking about, you know what I'm talking
Now we'll see what are you talking over the song? How about that? My butt cheeks are hurting. Yeah, whatever you went
Why did you just talk over that all some songs?
We're gonna play it again. We're gonna play it again. And so and if you talk, you're gonna get banned from here
You understand new boy
Yeah, whatever so learn your place in the pecking order as so I'm not like you, bro
You don't be a little monkey. I'm not like you. You're always going on people panel. I like you
No shit nobody's like me motherfucker ain't nobody like you motherfucker
I think if you guys rewind back, he played all the songs, but then he'll probably play it again, too.
Listen, Minnie Mouse, calm down.
She sounds like Minnie Mouse to me.
It's Minnie Mouse.
Where's Mickey? Where's Mickey?
He's over here killing you up cheating on you a fucking daisy Donald's wife
She doesn't take those cats about bro, they're dirty
That's a true man grooming themselves
No, they don't, but you couldn't sell the dill, you gotta wash them anyway.
You got to wash your cat you got to be fucking washed. They think traumatizing for them
With their sandy tongue
Great, and they're the cutest thing ever and they're healthy as fuck
You had the cat when you were making that tortilla and that cheese and that turkey or whatever you were making that little sandwich you were making on that
taco
you had your cat you had my cat comes on the counter i know but you were okay no but i'm not
saying the counter was dirty but the cat you were petting the cat and the cat had loose hair and
gangura
From not being they're fucking cats, bro. That's what they have. Yes, but I saw it
Everywhere
You didn't wash your hands. I need to go with seven cats, bro and everything she would
Fucking for a ball like that. No, that's right, but you know, do you wash your hands with me the restroom beta?
He's got black and white on his hair, that's my baby, he has black and white and all his brothers were gingers.
No, no, no, the other one.
No, no, no, he had gangra, all kinds of gangra.
Why just don't have fucking dandruff, are you kidding me?
No, it's that day, that day, maybe not right now, not right now, but that day on the screen.
What are you talking about? This is like his little, he has a little black and white on his hair.
No, not that part. That's the normal part of the cat.
Any machine dog is none of your fucking business, asshole.
Why are you getting so defensive, Pita?
Because you're sitting in your fucking-
Shitting on my fucking chest.
I'm not shitting on your cat. I'm saying you-
I'm shitting on you for not taking care of your cat.
That's what I'm doing.
Alright, well you know what? Go call Pita.
Peter, no, I'm gonna call Vita and the fuck Peter, I'm calling Vita.
Dummy.
Waste of time talking to fucking stupid.
I'm sort of fucking dumb.
Why are you so angry, Vita?
You need to just take a chill pill.
Because I remember, I just like, you're just such a stupid person to argue with.
You're like one of the lowest of the lowest to talk to.
How am I the lowest of the lowest to talk to?
Because you say?
I mean, let's not ruin the energy, so I'll leave right now because I can't stand your
fucking ass, okay?
Go ahead, Vita.
I'll tell you why.
You're a fucking doctor. You don't black are you black are you you're my last name black
Black are you got to do and he's your mind you idiot
I have a screenshot of it, so what are you talking about here?
Over there. Oh, hi black RG. Oh, hi. How are you doing? Like nothing happened?
You're mad at me for doxing somebody else, but you're mad at black RG for doxing your family
Hello
Yeah, let's talk to somebody else because I'm like none of them would just fucking talk to stupid
I wish I could give you guys my best Gordon Ramsay accent while I make this dinner, but
I'm trying to figure out what the fuck you're making
I'm about to sprinkle some buttery breadcrumbs all over this ranch sauce chicken breast
You're gonna put in the oven that's where I'm gonna put it beta sounds good sounds good
We better than hot dogs hot dogs are disgusting
How God do the best thing in the world? We don't just don't know what she's missing out on
Who thinks everything's processed food and everything's beneath her?
It's just my preference in food. I don't fucking like hot dogs. I don't have to eat them, God.
I can lay on my ass, J-Dog.
Hot dogs are processed. What are you talking about? They're very highly processed.
They're one of the most highly processed foods in the world.
Exactly.
Nothing wrong with a hot dog, J-Dog.
I'm losing brain cells every time you speak you do brain cells because you have zero brain cells to offer
Hello everybody good comeback this greater
Oh don't worry i'm here to ruin everybody else's brain cells now i'm here now
So make these fucking daisy because donald's too busy running around up to louis doing you and mini mouse beta it's just like
That's my theory
Just like in J dawg came up here with the
Well, could I expose you for your dirtiness the way you do your act?
My dirtiness, by the way.
The way you're dirty and you cook your food and you have your cacks filthy, that's harassing you.
How much do you watch our day, dog?
Is dirtiness even a word?
Do you feel like you're watching every fucking second of her?
You don't like her? Why are you watching her so fucking much?
What are you talking about? This was one of the panels that I was on when he was talking about it.
I'm just curious because that's all the fuck you've been talking about. Like, you was always talking about a chat.
It's all you want to talk about up here. Like, you're like part of the fucking whole panel, but it's really shit.
We'll give you some.
Exactly. We'll give you some.
All good
No one gives a fuck what you're talking about did you hear that one? No one has background how come I
You're trying to ruin the world. I thought you died like five years ago.
You're a fucking loser, so...
You're talking about
They just go after business
Oh, he's opening the oven
What is that? Yeah, I told you green eggs in the ham
Oh, yeah, that's chicken nuggets and
Yeah
That's it
So, is anybody else affected by this lovely fucking heat wave?
Oh, I see ya.
My landscaper.
Landscaping better than I know you are.
You know what, I'm just here to be nice and spread the good vibes and, you know, bitch about landscaping.
Yeah
90 fucking to 100 degrees every fucking day. I'm from Ohio. We don't do Florida
that's keeping all companies make money man
Bows they keep America's fucking yo, there's some big landscaping companies. That should make food. There's plenty. I mean fuck
You can throw a fucking rock anywhere on your street, you're gonna hit a fucking landscaper, right?
I see around me they come with these trucks were like these giant tubes
and blowers so they just like blow the whole street leaves and then like this giant vacuum
just sucks it in and they're just shoveling it into it but these are like the industrial
one day uh not it's so fucking hot here though the grass ain't fucking growing and we ain't
getting fucking rain if it rains it rains for five fucking minutes ten minutes just like
Dickloads of money. I mean, thank God. You gotta go to the complexes, bro
They talk condo communities and all those communities like the complex
It don't matter even the business the businesses are the dudes that do business like a commercial
They still lose the money because he's fucking commercial the grass ain't fucking growing
Don't matter how much you water it here right now grass ain't fun grown
What or not
Sprinklers are going off every night. I have sprinklers fucking shooting up every night at 2 a.m.. I'm 100% telling you
I live in a very rich neighborhood
Motherfuckers got sprinklers everywhere every mother fuckers yard is brown right now
That's to be a like a worry that's a sign that
You know global warming kind of shit that thing all right
I'm gonna say global warming, but the climate shift is a real thing
you've got a water that shit a lot grass to make it green people can't afford
To be fair, there's a lot of Indians and Asians moving in the neighborhood and they could give a
fuck about what the outside of their house looks like. Well, I haven't seen a brown grass around me.
True. Not that you say that. Everything around here is green. Don't talk about much. Green.
Thank you. And it's not a racist statement. That is just truly what it is. Yep. Oh, man,
you should see what Canada's like, bro. That's, uh, it's not Canada anymore. It's little India.
Yep, and then you go to fucking UK and it's becoming a mini mini Afghanistan. Oh, no more Canada
But you know, this is what it is
that's his life
Hey, look, we're gonna be in Mexico here though. I'm just saying what if the CIA took out Epstein to protect the elite?
What if
What if they put
He didn't want to talk. He didn't want him to talk about that. Okay. All right, I'll drop it. I'll drop it
I don't know what happened or he got dropped off. It could have been an accident
Yeah
I just want to apologize for the other day I was extremely frustrated at other things
No, no, no, she mentioned summer don't believe her. She's a liar. She meant every word of it
She's a guy and I know how to apologize and take accountability it when I respect
Your uncle fucker, you're an uncle fucker you're an uncle fucker
That's the kind of character we have he's disgusting
the fucking like supreme fucking scumbag like lords
No, no, no Alex, you're don't even compare yourself to that
Anyways, I'll catch you. I hope you have a good dinner sacks as I always good seeing you by Alex
And
I'm just top fucking liver, thank you beta
Just on with her the other day, too. Oh
You're satchel on it don't matter. Also satchel on Don
Nice to meet you. I don't think I fucking
Interacted with you before that's Canada dry in the chat. Have you ever seen that name?
Well, I don't get to see the chat very often because
Well, so this screen or the chat I usually pick this screen
So my face
or looking at the chat and
You know
I'm not sorry. I'd rather show my face as much as chat. Don't want to see my face
No, everyone loves your face everyone loves faces more than the more avatars
100% some people can't do it for some reason, you know
You just can't question it or whatever they have their reasons for that
Got their personal choices
I can't do it because of my job. I've been saying this since day one other people. I don't know why
So, uh, thank you for dealing with all the riffraff and bullshit in your job
Make our streets safer as long as you're not a parking meter, bitch
Fuck those guys
Yo, Saskatchewan, I got the same toaster in the corner and I angle it
just like you
it reminds me of my kids
that bacon, the little torso in the corner
and they angle it, like that, the same thing, like angled
so funny
it looks weird
it looks better like that
then
No, it looks good like that. That's how it's supposed to be. Yeah. Yeah, I look like that doesn't work
That works fire does everything a toaster. So fun all in one unit, baby
Yeah, this thing does it has an air fry option, but it kind of sucks
All right, because it's a toast an air fryer. You're right
You got to get the rack air fryer that like opens out like the toaster does not the fucking stupid
I fucking hate the tray toaster. I have air fryer
I have right now the the ninja and you open the door and it's like the bowl type shit. I think fucking eat that thing sucks
I don't like that ninja brand
That's why I live by it. I got ninja. I got ninja
You know what air fryer's I don't like by the way, it's the sharpest blade
You'll have a touch the first day I got it
I just touched nick the blade and I was bleeding for two hours. He can't hold that ninja bullshit
But I know why I don't like to keep it
Which is Colombian made
Makes sense in a kitchen. You've got all these industrial things. So there's a the industrial food processor is a
You get jaded yeah, so there's like the mixer is a Vita Vita mix and then the
Fuck what's the name of the food slices bro? No, you're right. They just like some of infomercial
They take all the real equipment and make their own affordable version of it. Yes, they do and there's
Someone had a good one back in the day food processor. Who of it?
There's some lady. Oh, and you need some water. I bet it's hot. It's all about the Vitamix really
You're not gay. Are you a sas? And a robo-coop? Oh
That's an industrial ninja bro that thing is just
He didn't hear it. I say I think
He doesn't look gay, he's too skinny
He has psyched body. He's like psych. No, no psych psych psych sick. He's skinny. He's
no
you're skinny guys look for a thousand
he's thicker than he is
and he's big all the long
he's like 140 pounds wet
psych's gotta be around 170-80
and I will
accurate on the 140 pounds
maybe 150
now 140
called it and you said psych is what 170 no one 70. Yeah, oh dude all day
What is that strikey? It's not the height. It's not the height. He's and I'm not saying he's fat
He just has more on him than then says catch one down
Yeah, I try man, and I eat like three meals a day. I swear. It's my metabolism or I've got a shape worm
I'm trying to gain weight. It's so fucking hard man
I was 200 pounds one in my life
199 I stepped on the scale and it said
199 oh my my yeah, I was
And my legit shit is 175. I wish I was
That's what I gotta keep it
I think you know fluctuates when person I think it would be an industrial one because it's in the industry
Yeah, yeah, I say look baby. Oh, you're the 200
The meaning is in the word
You can bench press them probably yeah 100%
I mean, fuck I used to be I was almost 300 pounds, but that was just pure
All right, all right, so if you encounter Isaiah and you get into a fight with him
He can bench press you the way you what are you gonna do?
You're gonna have to turn into a ninja my friend. You're gonna have to go back to
The neck the balls the Adams apple pressure points. You have to become a ninja
someone like this
okay so become a ninja bro
if you're 140 and you encounter a 220 motherfucker
he can just grab you by the throat
he's the force along with the
so then you become a ninja
for about 4 minutes of plating
so I'm gonna go smoke pot
here you go, here's one arm on the ladder
there you go, it's like 30 pounds
I think
something like that
Shitty fucking metal ladder. I tell you though if I put on a different t-shirt. I'm gonna look less skinny
It's this fucking t-shirt. It is. I never seen you this
Her name was Chloe she was giving me
Stop my shot and one for once
You came in a pussy. No, no, no, I got a phone number. I'm not a man horn. Oh, I don't try to fucking
But you got a number from a girl
Did I did what often for me? No, you made your move. I'm shy
Hold on you had balls and made the move. I did
100% like three hours actually four hours ago now today. Yeah. Oh, yeah
Oh, so you're picking shit right now. You're happy as hell. Oh, yeah
Yeah, I'm right a little bit of that cloud night. Hi. Yeah. Yeah, you got the butterflies in the stomach like a high school girl
That don't even feel
you know what it was it was a sure thing easy fucking move though because i'm standing at a bar
and i was pointing in her direction but i was actually talking about this old dude who played
a song right behind her but then she starts staring at me and then she starts eye contact four or five
fucking times oh and don't deal don't deal my man yeah and then i went and smoked a cigarette with
I asked for a number and then she's like you got five seconds. I'm like, oh fuck
I ain't got my phone on me. Wow bar and she's like, all right
We walk in she's like all right ask me again in five seconds
See the t-shirt difference as you gave it to you different guy. I hope so
Put it in your phone. You like
No, she texted back. Oh, oh you're in there my man off rip you want to say that's it play your cars, right?
you don't want any less skinny in that shirt by the way you still look just to
fuck you
I don't know he looks better, this one looks better
he's lying, this one looks better, you do not
that shirt makes you look like psych
I swear to God. I was like what
Yeah, this shirt looks you look normal again
But like I'm not saying he didn't look not normal in the first shirt
No, he looks like say it looks just as normal as the last shirt to me
Maybe I see people and not what they're wearing, you know, oh shit
You also don't have a fucking shirt on but yeah, no, I don't know. I feel better. I feel better in this shirt
This could be your wife, I tell you first-degree rod garage right now. I'm not wearing a shirt there wouldn't death
So you're not gay. I always I gave
all of the
the
You know, you know the only downside was right because I started you know, I talked with you from and she's like
Yeah, I'm from Cleveland. It's the ghetto. It's like blah blah blah this street
I'm like, all right, you're borderline ghetto whatever the fuck and then she got a little like a
Black white girl. I'm like, all right. All right. No, don't do that because you're gonna fucking turn me off now
I think she's shut the fuck up and be a nice white girl that I just met
Keep that ghetto fucking twang out of here. All right, but something entices you. Yeah
the
And you just met a girl from the same area. Yep. Wow
That's like your ex's ghost haunting your stuff
She does
Yeah, you better at least get some puss
I just hope she got that black vagina, you know
Where is she now she lives in Cleveland boat she why she here
To you. Oh, dude. I live in fucking Cleveland. What are you talking about? Oh, you're in Cleveland. I
Thought you were in Texas, bro
Yeah, cuz I got a beard and fucking look
It's got you on talk to us. Yeah, you're
What? Oh, I'm sorry. I started doing some other shit
I'm just waiting for my fucking dinner here. You know very much. Oh man dick. Oh
Yeah
Randy sorry tascat but don't tell me that's not macho man that might be oh
yeah from the top rope do any of you guys like a reggae at all? Randy macho man
having the air Elizabeth when the hook manious see Hulkster get pinned by the
macho man oh yeah I'm gonna I'm gonna rain elbows from the top ropes yeah he's
I didn't have much let me real like three-quarters of a bag like he did and then fucking I'll come back to you. Oh
God
All right. All right. No, it's a sketch one. No
What no, what do you do for work?
Now what are you doing right now?
Sorry sask, I couldn't help it bro
because he looks like a macho man, which was my favorite wrestler back in the day
, I still want to say, it's fine, it's fine
whoo!
because you were talking and I cut you off
that's fine
I didn't see it
what is it? it's hard to, it comes through blurry
It's uh, it's like an old 70s Candino automatic. It's swiss like an old Swiss watch
I love watches man. It's like us. It reminds me of God and us right there right there. Hold it for a minute
Yeah, I like that. That's nice. It's very cool
Just like a classic working man's watch, you know what I mean, mm-hmm
Nothing fancy nice leather strap comfortable size not too
Big into watches younger now whatever
That's my favorite watch yes, I do have
Also, and that is my favorite watch just with the black face and the gold little dot on the 12
I got it's called the museum black leather black face with the diamond on the 12. Yep. Yeah, love them
I love my Mavado. Let's call the museum Mavado
The box of loans and
And the whole family came out and congratulated me like nice job nice job because I gave it a go
I only spent a hundred and twenty five dollars on it. I got an unclean city. Yeah, I'm not gonna get too much into that watch
If you guys like it you like it. It's not that I like military watches now, you know, I'm just prepared for hell, bro
like the model is out the window and that's on a hot date with some you know
Beautiful girl, but yeah, I'll get your stuff put my my water one for that one night, but
For the rest of the month. It's military watches, baby. Oh and
Hamilton khaki automatic field watch
You fucking solid that sounds expensive. It's about a thousand bucks. Exactly
See right talking the everyday shit, right the diesel watch. I think it's around maybe 150 probably $200 now with some inflation
It's the
Green olive green band. All right rock band. It's a little bit bigger of a face
But it has everything, you know your compass you're you know all three different fucking clocks
But it's got the feature where it's cool. It doesn't
So it likes a red instead of you know, so when you hit it, yeah, how old you bastard?
Did you remember the watch that was like a little calculator?
It was like
That's pre G shock man that shit's iconic that is the way pre G no that was like six great shit those
Oh
But when I I remember you know 90s as a kid that was the shit of watches
Dude, it was in back to the future like all the good movies had the characters wearing that watch
No, what the code with the calculator on it. Yeah. Yeah, that was like the futuristic. What yeah
I had to bend a came out because it was still the shit in the 90s and then what took over that watch
What was the next watch?
To go with a G-Shock is like the next step of that product
Maybe in popularity yes, I mean obviously feature-wise and what the fuck it actually was that's true
No, no beepers member beepers beep beep beep
There was a little thing called a beeper you get beeped and you call the number a number
The beeper watch was hard
The people know and then they came up with a beeper. That was big
It looked like a garage or door opener and it would be digital that was literally you those are the only beepers
I remember with a big
Oh, yeah, like yo, I got power
Yo, who's the man
Yo society's crazy it's still that way like who's the man look at itself and look at this BMW like who
Still the same shit
You know, I thought like that for so long because I'm like buying my nice trucks and shit and I'm like, man, yeah, I'm the shit and I'm like, you know, the last, literally the last year I'm like, man, that's such a piece of shit for thinking that way.
I'm like, I have nothing. This truck don't make me. Truck don't make me nothing.
It's funny though, because something about having a beeper felt cooler than having an iPhone.
It's like an iPhone comes out every year, but like when the beeper came out and people had beepers, it was like, shit!
Yeah, you could appreciate it.
Like, well, I mean, I don't know, I guess looking back on it, you could appreciate, right?
I mean, when the iPhone came out, it was kind of like...
I mean, if we go to that round, there was smoke signals back in the day, dude.
Yeah, right.
Like, yo, contact told me, like, spark a smoke signal, like, ooh, smoke them back.
Yeah, my camp can cook meat over a fucking fire.
Hey, you guys are eating raw steak still, shit, bitches.
Nah.
No, no, no, think about it, though, right?
So from the pagers, the next major step, I think, really?
For like tech shit the Motorola razor, dude, and then there's a sidekick sidekick was big after the razor
But the razor was like
Damn that was the shit for flip no KIA had a couple moments in between everyone else to
Like they were just there doing like no KIA man. It's fucking no KIA. Who's calling? I don't remember no KIA
I don't think it was popular though like like you know what okay to have a no KIA for me
So for me, I would have been in like grade five, six, and parents are just starting to get cell phones, right?
It's the 90s, but kids don't have them yet. So the Nokia was the like
standard like mom or dad's phone that we brought out at night. Yeah, you're stick-faced fucking
Exactly, like, oh, I got mom's cell phone and it's the Nokia. That's for me. What no, but like Sarah with virgin mobile
I forgot what the fuck it was called. But yeah, it was my favorite phone fucking too
Yeah, it's you know that front you know all buttons no flip then I went to the keys here a so ho which was the cool white
Phone with a little fucking square
And then I went to a razor which was tits
No, yeah had some cool gaming phones that didn't really take off. Mm-hmm. Do you remember those?
Well only rich kids had them with like all the buttons and the screen in the middle AT&T tilt
So it was a slide out at first that was what I had in the screen tilted
So it's like you're holding a like this and then you can tilt the screen
Yeah, they came out with a tilt to which actually wasn't a tilting phone
Which was kind of weird. It was more like a stick face front, but dude that phone
Always one of my favorite phones that we'll go down as but yes, and the rich kids had it. I wasn't rich
I just knew how to bitch and leverage my parents. Yeah
But I might have had like an LG chocolate for my first phone, you know chocolate chocolate, too. I
Didn't have them, but I don't know. Oh, I sold cell phones for many many many fucking years, too
It's funny how that we we experienced a complete like industry that came and went as like like the pre smartphone industry of just
So many different variations of phones. It came what like
1999 and it was gone by what?
2010 uh
2000 the first iPhone was like
2000 and like
Seven I want to say and I bet it wasn't until 2010 that everyone switched over. Oh
Well, there was a massive switch, but you're right. Yeah, no 100% because everybody's new technology. I don't know man
But then again, think yeah again the flip phones though like realistically the flip phones flip
So real flip phones not like the brick fucking like the big brick right like fold out
Like actual just you know flip
10 decade probably a decade. They were around. Yeah
smartphones popped and
Ah, dude. Yeah, the first thing to think of just that like it is possible for something that we're into to only last a decade or something we're currently doing to only last a decade and no one ever thinks in the moment that way blue ray.
Oh, exactly blue ray. I mean DVD lasted a little longer than that right because it was like blue ray versus eight.
What was the other one there was like a race to see who was going to
High definition. There was the HD disc
Was there I do oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah because PlayStation did Blu-ray and then there
And someone else did proprietary that had that other yeah HD
Well, even at that point still it was still a fucking fail in the end
Because nobody really did fail because it was basically just DVD with a bit of a different flight a
Higher bit a higher bit rate that gave a little bit better of a fucking resolution, but it's like bro
We already have DVDs. It's good when they came out with blu-ray the thing was the camera still couldn't record
And a high enough quality at that point, anyway, it really makes a difference, right?
So these Hollywood movies, like, all right, they're getting released, but
you know, your Blu-ray, like, that just looked a little nicer at first.
Granted, yes, it got better as the years went on with Blu-ray, but if, you know,
if you didn't have a PlayStation or a Blu-ray player, you ain't watching that shit.
I guess it was bigly downloaded.
Let's go back to Lime Wire days, man. I miss Lime Wire.
and bear share
What was the other one ice something I'm wire bear share
Napster Napster pissed me off. I hate a Napster well by the time I started doing like be more illegally downloading ship
Napster was like monthly fee shit
Bro, I would have been like eight or nine when my cousin downloaded Napster on my computer
And I fucking remember I downloaded the like
The it was a prank phone call between two guys
It's like a Chinese
Chinese chicken guy calls the fucking Chinese
restaurant prank
It was super old like viral thing I
downloaded Eminem the real Slim Shady and maybe like 50 cent in the club and
I was like Napster's the fucking greatest
My my father that was never around would just his
Around my knees a man
So his compensation was he the love Napster and Shazam
So he would just drop off, you know, like once a month or so whenever we happen to fucking see
Drop off some like ripped DVDs that he had made like games, right?
And it took two distance for games in New York, New York at that fucking point
Right like just I click
I don't fucking stupid shit, right?
Um, but yeah, no, I was fucking the limewire all day, bro, until they cut it and then I had to go to the Pirate Bay, but limewire was this shit, dude.
So Saskatchewan, where's your dad?
I'm guessing that around. I say it's not around, mine not around.
That's a crazy little trend, right?
But that's a dick.
Saskatchewan, did you have a lesson from them?
So I might be able to be the best that you can be when I was really young my mom got with my stepdad
And so he's been in my life for a long time
But now so and it's always been good, but my mom never really let him kind of take charge. She does because
my mom they never do they never do when it's a step dad because exactly they still feel like it's not their kid
Yeah, you get it. I get it. I like I love my stepdad
He's great, but now that he has his own two kids with my mom. You can tell there's a bit of a different
Yeah, it's like he shifted the dynamic
And that's weird man how shit changes right people change
He lives in
BC and he's lived there basically since before I was born. My mom called him and was like you're actually like I know you just moved to BC but I'm pregnant and he was like oh that's too bad.
That sucks.
With you, she was pregnant with you.
Yeah.
and he said that's too bad, why?
kind of, yeah
I feel like we're around the
how old are you, I feel like we're around the same age
92, I'm 32
okay, yeah, I'm a little
I'm 35, so I figured
we were right on this fucking same number
same number
I know girls that have told me
that their parents told them they were a mistake
and now they love it more than anything
So if my dad tell me I was a mistake my stepsister told me that my dad told her I was a mistake
Yeah, and that hurts a little more because you don't know to believe her
So it plants a seed and deep down you believe it
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
I think two years ago might have been last summer actually last summer
Summer to you summers ago. I had no fucking idea
Because my mom and my sister had stopped talking for a few years and terrible fallout
I had never had a new new why right so my sister's telling me she's like oh yeah um
No mom got really pissed at me one day and said you're lucky
And i'm like what do you mean and she's like well i didn't know and she's like well i don't care
By that so she went and asked my aunt about what my mom meant about your lucky i came back right
so my mom used that stated said that shit like you're lucky I came back in a fight with my sister
and she found out my mom actually gave her up for a fucking adoption for a month and then went
back and picked you up from the adoption clinic whoa early adop whatever
Yeah, right right and like my that's a statement of the dude my mouth douchebag douchebag
You're gonna turn around to use that in a fight against your child. And yes, we were both mistakes without question, but
I see no one was a mistake. Oh
No, I was a mistake. Oh god damn it Remington. What did you fucking just chew up?
Where did you get?
Where the fuck did you even get these?
but
All of that will make you the best parent on the planet. When it's your turn to
With just the best gift that you can ever receive in your life
I and then you're gonna not put them through what you've been through and it's gonna make you the best dad on the planet
Yeah, I I want to raise a child for the sole fact of just ego
Let's rub it in my dad's face and also to make the world a better place. Hopefully
Don't know though. I am an asshole. So, you know, they might they might be an asshole, too
But I digress I'll still be a better dad than my fucking dad was
and potentially mom
But I'll never abandon that I will never if I fucking if I get a girl pregnant and
You know, hopefully well, I did get one pregnant
But there was a miscarriage minor details if I get a chick pregnant and there's babies born. There's no, you know
the court's going to have to keep me out of that child's life, and that's a stretch on top of it
it could backfire and the court will keep you in the way of life, because now you got to pay child support for 21 years
don't care, I mean that's fine, but as long as at that point I'll have a visit, I'll have a visitation bro
that depends how much you want to
I don't care, I don't care about the payment
I'll go with the pussy, it's the pussy word
Raising a child and now half of your pay goes to you better make sure you're in love motherfucker
You better love that bitch
What is it about then love because when you're sticking that pussy and you calm next thing she's pregnant
And next thing you're in court like yo, you gotta support you gotta help and now you're landscaping your ass off
Like wow half of my landscaping is going to her and I might go to jail if I don't keep it up
You miss one you miss one child support payment. You go to jail. That's how it works here, bro
That's how scary it is with that shit. I'm gonna be a natural. It's the weirdest thing the United States
They do especially New York. Oh, I don't know you live in
They do not play with that.
You know, there's three things you can't fuck around.
Not paying your taxes, not paying child support,
and having a DWI.
Those three things are on top of the list.
Look at this.
A nice car drive down the street,
and Alex just veered off into the ghetto
and started knocking out.
trash can, right? No shit. Let's take the baseball bet out the fucking car window right now.
But no, no, no, no, I do agree though. Think about the stupidity behind the child support
shit, right? We're going to take your driver's license away. Why? You're just now even hindering
more somebody getting a fucking job to even try to start paying fucking child support.
Why the fuck would you take a driver's license away? Right? All right.
You know, we'll hit you on taxes, we'll put you into fucking debt or some shit, you know, whatever the fuck, I don't know, hit your credit.
But the driver's license is the dumbest thing to fucking take away.
Let's make you less responsible of a human being.
Fuck.
I mean, granted, clearly they weren't that responsible to begin with, but, you know, at least with a car you can fucking make money.
But hey, sorry
Oh, that was a break out another baseball bat, what'd you eat for dinner? I had some
like
breaded chicken breast potatoes and carrots pretty basic shit
That sounds I mean fuck that it still sounds good. It's awesome. Oh, yeah
Healthy, I mean your problem is you didn't you want to gain weight. You didn't do you know like a nice fatty fried fucker
So you're gonna gain your weight
Actually, actually just come to the stage for like a month or two. You'll you'll you'll throw on fucking pounds in a heartbeat
eat subway I hate subway though are you a lot of fucking Wendy's I'm not gonna
lie oh dude I I hope your Wendy's is better our what while at least around
here the Wendy's just fucking sucks like I wanted a greasy old-school burger like
they usually have now it's like there's no grease it tastes like shit and it's
clearly now frozen patties even though they say never frozen
But our subways though, I don't know if the subway is the same in Canada as far as recipe goes
But United States subway is
Actually not considered food quality like not right by food
Yeah, and a lot of other countries because it's just so fake and sugar processed. It's mainly very similar here with subway bro like
I can't smell it something about the smell of subway when I walk by it. I get I don't want to eat
it's such a weird food smell and
For some reason like right across the board from the lettuce to the tomatoes to the bread
It all has the same sort of zest. I don't know what the fuck that smell is
There's there's a chemical taste to it also that uh, you know, I taste every fucking time, but it's cold
Ryan is or some shit
It's cold not fresh in there
If it has a set it means it's not fresh from they got two different sauces that I put on there
And there's like a chipotle and like I don't know Baja, whatever the fuck. I don't know too
Bro, I had a subway sub the other day and I smashed the fuck out of it because I couldn't taste the chemicals because the fucking sauce over fucking wrote it and
But I just lost it fucking hate it, bro. It's the sauce the sauce makes it better. Well, the sauce makes it
Edible sauce makes it anything better
But so shouldn't you fuck subway? Oh, but every once in a while man
And it's bullshit, right? Yeah, they raise their prices. Why all your shit's fake anyway
Yeah, how you gonna fucking raise your prices for inflation? He's big
And it costed you no more than it was 20 fucking years ago when you did probably cost
bitch
Well, dude, yeah, we're seriously even fucking faker dude
I I would be surprised if their meat was real low cock. I feel like they have Taco Bell style meat
You know what? I don't think you guys have it in the states. Do you have Harveys?
Harveys with a V. Yeah, not Harveys. Harveys. You do not. We do not.
We don't have Harveys here, but we have Harveys with a V.
it used to be this place that like was famous for having a like a restaurant
quality burger, but to go.
Got it.
And it's just like hearties so McDonald's
No, that was never Wendy's Burger King. They got all that in Canadian. They got all that. Yeah, I love all that
I love Burger King actually I actually couldn't eat Burger King
15 fucking years
And the whoppers are gangsters because they use a lot of onion probably bro. No, but you can have it your way
You can take no onion little onion fucking beef onions. Don't flare up gout
No
the
two
It is amazing turmeric though look at look at India right with a crazy ass
Pollution that India has and they still survive and live longer than most
Americans turmeric all their crazy bad fucking environmental shit that should
kill them faster
they have to make it everything to mark is fucking on me
you know what I bought today it's a leaf called the can't can't duck
Candela
Candela I bought a pound of it for 30 hours today some leaf. It's a tea from Egypt
It's a plant from Egypt. I went to some nutrition store to find it. I have to go out of my way
And yeah, I'm gonna turn it to tea. I think it is the holy grail can can
I think it's can and dollar can and dollar some shit like that
Yeah, it's a leaf you can get cream whatever, but I got the organic bag and I'm gonna drink it
holy grail
Oh, yeah, I do want to say
Time a time of moon oil time a new time a new oil
Some shit like that. That is amazing. I also got that and then there's a thing called the cinnamon from Thailand
You got to get your ass
Some Thailand cinnamon
Did really a surprise in the end?
Holy grail, I surprised
Well, I look like I'm 25
But really you're 24
I actually am.
Exactly.
Oh, shit.
Who the fuck did I put in my fucking smokes? What the fuck?
Damn.
How the fuck did I lose these things?
They're in my fucking garage.
Who is it? Yes, Katrina
Callan doula. Yes, Callan doula plant. It is the holy grail. Get your hands on that shit immediately
I just bought a pound today for $30. It's a big bag too of the dry leaves
It comes in all your cream all this shit
But the best you want the organic the leaves and you turn that shit into tea and drink it
You're gonna fuck you know you got age 10 years
the
I just met I need that can and do look at it. Let's go. I need a baby. I do my own work
Thailand cinnamon
Dula, I said it growing and leaves
making to tea and drink it apple cider vinegar
Red onion garlic bowl
to have to wrap with the season for the rest of your life
to go in it
Thanks Christine, and you didn't share with me, I had to find out myself months later
about this secret magical plant from Egypt.
Walk like in Egypt, Sean.
I mean, I mean, you know, that you should be, they're really asshole for not preaching
the cream of some young guy to you, man.
Fucking.
Cream of some young guy.
Oh, yeah.
Love that.
Cream of some young guy.
I'm hung low my name me me hung low
Me on low
We will some young guys
Love that I made a prank call in high school, of course dude dude was on the phone move 35 fucking minutes
I happened to get the one Chinese fucking restaurant in our area they had an old white dude working a phone
Oh, that was fucking amazing.
What the fuck?
Back to the kitchen.
He's like, oh, yeah, all right.
You know, after like literally 30 minutes on the phone, he's like, oh, yeah, I think
I was talking to the kitchen.
I think we got what you want, like dead fucking serious, like we think we know what you're
That's like a fucking movie, bro.
A white guy at the phone at a Chinese restaurant.
Right.
That don't happen.
Yeah, exactly.
It's like a movie.
It's always the wife.
What you want?
What you order?
No, you know, it's funny bro. If you called a restaurant in Canada
Whether it was Chinese
American Greek
Yeah
Indian people work at every ethnic restaurant in Canada. There is no official
Italians don't work at the Italian restaurants. It's Indian people. Yeah, Mexicans don't work in the Mexican restaurants
Indian people do. So you don't actually get authentic cultural flavors in Canada.
You get India's version. It's taste of Sicily owned by Patel. Yes, it's
fucking so sick of it. Oh shit man.
Yeah, no, that's yeah, it's got to be fucking irritating. I mean, it's
It's like one thing that cultural diversity but have cultural takeover is a complete other conversation
Yep
Unfortunately, I don't remember. I don't know who's the new front. Who's the prime minister for you guys now? Oh
Fucking the carney we someone a car. What's a carney a carnival guy a car. Yeah
A carney they've all got weird names like Trump he trumps shit this guy's gonna be a fucking carnival professor
It's the clown ring. I mean, I I'm on the fence with Trump now
I'm not a Trump guy. I'm not I'm a nobody guy. I got time. They're not a single politician shit
Yeah, I was for Trump and then I got I'm just burnt out and I
Um, they're all on agendas by corporations that we can't even understand or a regular
person can't even wrap their heads around what politics and corporations are doing.
All right.
And even better, we can't change it, right?
And at the end of the day, they can't even fathom what's actually going on.
We can change it, but it's the fight. Nobody fucking wants, you know
Well a where's we it's hard now because there's so much division which division makes control
B, it's the hard fight man. It's it
Even exposing the exiles are not gonna change it, you know
It's still gonna like that's not gonna bring down the whole
It's not the amount of exposure or anything like they could come out and say that fucking
Joe Biden fucking molested 20 kids and Trump was there fucking with the video camera, right?
It ain't gonna change nobody's fucking opinion, right? Because everybody's yeah, and now they're
gonna have to throw a couple people out there. There's too many people asking questions. All it is
is literally it's fighting the system, but the problem is it's got to be global. It's not just us,
Everybody's fucking intertwined Canada, you know, Mexico, UK. Fuck it.
Everybody is correct. And we're just talking our neighborhoods like, wow.
Exactly. We're sitting here fighting about boys and girls while they're sitting there fighting
about how much money can we milk out of the fucking slaves in the States before there's an uprising.
Like that's our other slaves anywhere. Right. Like literally that literally is it.
Look at the issues people fight over ain't none of it talking about fucking
Policies the the national debt whenever you hear anybody fucking protests in the street
Protest over gas. Okay, great. You used gas to fucking get to the protest when you rode the fucking bus there like fuck off
You're you're the fight over the wrong fucking things. Oh
Sorry, I don't I don't I don't want to get
Psyche to kick us off for talking. That was the bond with the 10th. That was the bond with the 10th on it
The old school puppy
Hopefully one day though, well, it won't be one. No one day will be bad. I digress
This weather though this weather some shit
all do the flooding I'm sure you've seen the flooding in Jersey that's it's fun
wild
learning Jersey you saw what happened in Texas from
all absolutely I saw a taxes the yeah taxes is really really bad I so you
believe in God
I had yes, yes, I do okay
So where do you think God was that night in Texas or did he cause it?
Did he just rain on people and wash fucking a hundred kids down the river and kill them
Biblically, why would God do that?
Biblical statement is our God is a vengeful God our God is a vengeful God on little kids
It's not a God our God is not a God of mercy
right I got why not wash out fucking every person on the planet or hit it with electric
but it's uh i'm not saying i'm not saying god controlled that
hey of course he did if he's god he controls the mother nature he controls wind water fire earth
all the way it's under his control humans also god did that god made that what happened god killed
if you believe in God, you believe that God did that
I don't believe that
so shut the fuck up and tell me what you think about that
I am, I don't believe God did that, I believe in
there is
you owe, what, he was off that night drinking
God wasn't home and he wasn't checking the planet
and just let a hundred kids die
who did it then?
there's, there's, there's other
the devil?
the devil did it?
um
mother nature?
Humanity humans can manipulate the weather, right? So so so Bill Clinton did it asshole
Don't put it in George Bush. I
Was the stupid heart?
Yeah, is that what you think heart totally exists out of Arabia openly has cloud seeding
Where they're talking lithium and gold dust and some other shit and silver dust
So you're going with our fun this funny one. What's in God? It was par
I don't think God was part of it, aside from creating the humans that were able to create ways to manipulate the environment, other than that, no, God was not part of it.
Uh, harp can't do that, bro.
A bunch of antennas in some remote shit can't control weather. So I think you'd be surprised at what it could do
Why deny it like I'm not saying he's a hundred percent, right? Oh, so show me the proof
A bunch of antennas in a cornfield can do that
That's the technology they have is that what you're saying because that's what you just said
And now you're mocking God if you believe that now you're mocking God
Like it was just fucking humans playing with fucking the stupid instruments
Brother we have microscopes. We don't even know we can't get to the moon. You think they control the weather
You're crazy
There's only one person that can control the sun the moon and the weather and it's got well
He did that for that night for what reason is what I want to talk through
Bro, go. Have you ever seen a climatized like a climate?
controlled atmosphere before
Because they do and right there's climate controlled atmospheres a small version would be
Yeah, I've been to a sign there where they have a little box and you can create a tornado
Scientists have figure out how to put moisture in the air. It's not that
Think about that like oh, yes
to wipe out, they figure that out.
Maybe not a flood, but maybe enough to melt.
And they implement it.
Why would they kill little kids?
The detective machines?
You're arguing this simple like base thing.
Look at it at a bigger scope, bro.
Like really.
Help me see it in a bigger scale.
It's not, so it's not like Omi put in the fucking codes
to make a flooded river.
He's like, they're probably are able to go,
oh, well, if we melt these ice caps.
or if we center heat in this area we're going to melt something that's never melted before
or if we create so much rain in this area in this area that have never seen so much rain
it's going to alter this area in a way that's never been seen before it's just using atmosphere
it's not like a fucking cold for a flood or a cold for the sun to pop out at a different time
it's just people understanding how climate works and then
fucking being able to
Yeah, it's not you're a mind blowing it out
What makes this happen in a cloud again cloud seeding is what it's called first Saudi Arabia
Openly does it to create rain, right?
They do cloud seeding to create rainstorms. They control their fucking weather, right?
100% is an example of a country that openly does that and it is openly out there and talked about
Why would it be so crazy then that the United States couldn't do that, or any other country
in which there was an accusation that the United States caused the crazy, torrential
flooding and earthquakes in China for the last couple years, right?
And then there was a statement that China caused a lot of the shit going on here, I
I mean, think about it.
It's the major nations involved in the accusations in which...
Is it really that crazy and unlimited fucking budget to unlimited?
Yeah, bro, but to say someone controls the weather. That's a little crazy. Hey, no
Like that. Yeah. No, he's right. No one is controlling the weather every day and fucking oh, it's gonna do this now
Okay, but they can alter it. They have figured out a way to
Okay, they figure out a way to do something to alter it and make things happen
like rain or water or some shit okay i get it now if you if they have the best scientists in the
world that understand physics that understand that i can buy specifically Saudi Arabia i think
it's figure it out it's not money it's not science like it's
I don't know man. It's chemicals. It's it's it's literally it's chemical
And and I mean there's an example your temp trails wait wait chem trails is an example of it, right?
Cloud seating with chem trails to affect climate, right?
That is openly stated by the Air Force if you go to the Air Force website
They talk about using chem trails for various fucking bullshit, right? You can go to the Air Force website for that
but doesn't the weather channel know everything right?
they could tell us what's coming a week ahead
they missed that
think about it on another scale
so think about the ocean when there's a nuclear disaster
and it polluted part of the ocean
and they could find parts of the ocean out
fucking hundreds of miles away from the detonation site
so right there you go okay so this this particle of nuclear
reaction whatever I don't know I'm not a scientist
Can travel that far and affect the ocean out there? What can I put up here to affect it up here? It's like it's not mind-blowing
Yep, it's no. Well, it's it's no you're making sense now in the conspiracy sense
It's just chemistry conspiracy theory is a harp did it for some reason for that moment in that location
They didn't want nobody
And because in reality they tell us the weather months ahead. So that's bullshit. So they that's a cover-up and
Maybe they were just trying to take someone out in that area
Some people will blow up a whole bar just to kill one person in it. Oh 100% I lived in that shit in Colombia
They'll blow up a whole fucking block just to get to one person
And so that's another thing
United States government having the ability to wipe somebody out without even having to send somebody
Bro, that's the perfect way to do it, right? Like who plugged by senator who knows who was in camping that day
Who's gonna send a bill or change shit?
by U.C.A.
Who didn't find the bill the right way
and they're paying you a job.
Like you're talking about,
that's the way they would use it.
One more point I want to make too, Alex,
is that you're thinking in your mind,
like, oh, create rain, make flood.
It's not like that.
It's that the scientists understand,
okay, so what makes rain?
or what makes a thunder storm?
Yeah, correct. Like when I
raise the fog, the fog goes
back up in this area. We're
going to heat it up because
that's yeah, exactly. We
under the big rainstorm. It's
so foggy, right? It's fog. It's
like they can create 500 times
fog.
Yeah
Elements
If you can find a way to duplicate fog moisture going back into the clouds after rainstorm
and I think that's what they did. They can duplicate it a hundred times, hold and make it rain.
100% without questions.
Yes, I'm on board.
Saudi is absolutely an example because they fucking do that.
But I want to make the statement, you look at North Carolina and they're crazy flooding in the mountains.
And it's just three guys on YouTube that can figure this out.
Look, so North Carolina is flooding, right?
major worst flooding was these old families and it's the biggest lithium deposit in the
united states in the mountains of north carolina where that major ass flooding came from you
see companies coming in to buy it out mainly the largest one being the gates foundation
you look at a lot of other natural disasters where it's ruining quote-unquote farmland or
Gates Foundation is the major buyer
Palestine, Ohio the train derailment and all the chemical spill in the Amish country in the small-ass town of other weather
Whatever other normal white people mainly Amish farmland
Gates Foundation, but almost all of that fucking property up is everybody vacated the area because it's contaminated
When everyone's saying the cat is bullshit because we have an operator stop the radar
Everything to see that coming
You know saying they could have read that I'm like yo, it's gonna be raining galore like there's a stream fog
Something they would have caught that
All right, so Texas they show you guys all right. This is an example. Yeah, right?
They would have caught that for Texas
I mean that shit was fucking wild though 45 minutes and
The one river they were showing rose 20 feet man may natural disasters
We're stepping into a whole new era of hell
We are oh 100 that's basically what you guys are exposing. This is corporation health
This is man made natural defense. It's it's not even an exposure. This is shit. That's been going on for fucking years
It's just people kind of
Yes, so sometimes our quick turn earthquake is their day name bombs under the sea and saying it's an earthquake
Yes, that well it's yes well actually yes 100% that that is a thing happening I've got another point too it's kind of off topic but on topic you could go to the world economic forum.
And you could be intelligent enough to read something and go oh what they're saying here is they need to control the population
And they want to eliminate people and someone else would read it and go and that's what you got from that
Yep
And so that just proves that there's a lot of people who can't even really pick up on the fact that they're saying it
They're just using big words and different forms of of talk that you've never heard before and so you go all that's crazy
Yeah, it's like no that he said something
it's like when someone politely tells you to fuck off and they're like
I'm sorry sir we're not gonna do this right now thank you and you're like
they just told you to fuck off you know and I'm being nice and I'm like
how do you do it yeah I'm just being a nice guy right now
fucking what oh you told me to fuck off oh that's so funny
and then the other person's really pissed
But to the agreement though right all right so common sense right
Understanding there's no common sense anymore, right? I mean obviously the perfect example. What's a boy and what's a girl?
Common sense don't exist in the same way it did before
So to agree with your WEC reading and the report put out there
It's people are gonna perceive it how they fucking want to there's
I want to say the global common sense where I really want to say the vast majority of
the population agrees and understands and it's not for your political or religious or
ideological views, it's just in the sense of boy, girl, science, you know, gravity.
We all understand and agree and it's not anything, you know, it just is, right?
Right
But there's the overwhelming voice
mainly in the social media platforms and
News Network and corruptions and blah blah blah
That enough people listen to or at least especially social media enough people on social media the internet
make their voice so much louder.
Yeah, it's starting to see the shift.
You are starting to see a shift where it's a lot of people.
Oh, wait, this isn't actually happening in my community.
What's this person going on about?
Exactly, and now it's like, all right, cool, like, yeah,
like, all right, so, you know, the racism shit,
and I'm sitting here like, all right,
I live in a very white, affluent area,
and I've never had an issue with the cops, right?
Granted, I've heard some stories about them pulling over or fucking, you know
Specifically, I don't know say black people and giving them tickets for stupid shit like, you know, right a little over to fucking speed limit, right?
Okay
Has happened haven't heard about it and haven't haven't heard about it in a fucking long time and
Now we actually have a black cop, right?
We don't have that many cops. So we only got like
But uh, you know
that that is what it is right that's it's not a rampant problem i can't walk down the street
because i'm going to get my ass kicked here no like i don't know like i mean la riots i followed
all that stuff and i i'm not those were those were protests not riots sure okay yeah no
I do think white cops have been pretty shitty to black dudes for a long time. I don't know that it's
Everywhere for sure for sure. Well, I'm not gonna say that's not in history in history, right?
But the flip side is all right
So when there was black cops along with the white cops being shady black cops were also shady black people, right?
Yeah, that's better black people are shady to black people predominantly, right?
He's like y'all out here talking shit about us with our guns. He's like you don't realize I'm afraid of the guy with the gun
too, that's why I have mine
And
Statistically
Black people are killing black people. Well, not even it's yeah
Oh, it's no black people kill black people at a much higher rate yet racism is an argument
so, you know thirty thousand black people are killed by other black people a year and
It's it's I and I gotta say that I about 300 to 500 a year are killed by police officers
Let me talk about media and shit like that. You've got rap that just keeps fucking
Perpetuating the black on black crime. It just needs to go and just read and look at video games
As much as I hate to fucking say it but video games perpetuate some of it, too
I know, like, I love video games, I always have, but it absolutely changes the psyche, too.
Like, young people should not play Grand Theft Auto, right?
Right.
If you're a parent and you're buying your 8 to 13-year-old, ah, maybe not there, well,
you know, yeah, 8 to 13-year-old Grand Theft Auto, and letting them play it all day long.
Yeah.
You're terrible.
What's on your mind?
Yeah.
My first GTA was when I turned 15, which I wish it would have been earlier than that, but it don't matter and
like
It you know it didn't change my mind I ain't gonna try and go out and kill nobody and fucking try to be a gangster, but
The same point though. I think I was developed enough to understand the difference versus
You know some of these fucking kids out here
And we're in the age of two parenting where,
here's a fucking tablet.
Yeah, go watch YouTube.
Don't make a peep, fucking.
I'm gonna sit here and drink my fuck.
That's all I need to let us.
Oh yeah, if parents are stoked
if their kid's distracted by the tablet,
because it means they can go back to not having a kid.
Yep, exactly.
Exactly, I can go do whatever the fuck
I was planning on doing or wanted to do,
instead of actually
And let the internet teach my child how to be a person.
Yep, yep, we're gonna let the fucking people try and fucking, you know, yeah, the the influencer
Fucking tell my kid that they're probably trans and fucking put some ideas in their head or that they're fucking there
They're an outcast and you know, they should worship slenderman like
But not take any fucking responsibility when
I don't know their kid gets into a fucking fight fucking low-key what I was talking about with Tupac
It wasn't guy. It was hard. I'm still trying to wrap my mind around that one
There's an interview with Tupac where he says I'm tired of white moms
Claiming that all black guys who live in the ghetto with a gun are fucking bad people
You know because I'm also running from black guys with guns
And that's why I have one and that's what I'm referencing fucking low-key and you go watch the interview yourself
It is it is really funny to with that statement because every white dude in the ghetto is running from every fucking white chick
That's not some ghetto ass fucking white chick
You don't know you cross the street
It's just funny to see people like who live amongst shit and people who don't and the opinions and then yeah
I can tell you the most racism in my life is
one
Which I call the reverse racism
Number two though is I've only been harassed by
Well, that wasn't racism. No one cop was just that cops just a fucking douche bag
Never by the police
Aside from maybe one, but I don't want to call that racist. I just think he was being a fucking asshole. Maybe he was being racist. So one night
Pokemon go came out and I was playing Pokemon go at midnight
He's just cops give me a hard time. He's like, you're supposed to tell me if you're carrying or not
I wasn't actually carrying my gun because I was in the very white affluent neighborhood
Not my you know, I think you know, I think I say wait wait. So the racist is it is
Security guards the black security guards will follow me around them all
But
It's only the black security guards never had a white security guard following weird
Right, so what do you think that is?
It's just a control thing. It's not race. It's just control. No, no, it's it's race. It's race because he could follow the Asian kid
He could follow the which is weird though
Well, there wasn't other black people so that's why the security guard picked me and I was with my white girl at the time
Well, actually the white girl cuz I only date white girls, but I was in the girl at the time and
Like he's following us around. I'm like, okay, like
we're literally looking at $10 items and JC penny right now on the stupid shelf like
The fuck can you get your beers for a poof of life? I think that beard is glued on. I don't think it's a real beard
It's not there's no way you can grow it that long
it's been long that's fake
I've had my beard on
my beard was down here before
Do you see untrackable
I can't really yank it any harder than I am
Yank it a little, just a little bit, just a yank it a little
I'm giving it a little yank, you know, I got a little tug on
And it's with my tug hand too, I mean
Alright, let me get in your beard head though
I ain't ripping this shit off
Let me get in your beard head
You probably look better without it
It makes you look younger when you're clean shaven
I'd look like a 12 year old when I'm clean shaven
There you go, why would you want to look older?
Um, I don't get it, you want to look like a man, like where's the beer thing for me?
I don't like to hold my N.D. on to bad beer and cigarettes.
And we go ahead
They look like
Goatees, but they love my tree
Here's some proof and I can go over here like you guys you got short. Oh, why why would I want to have that?
Hair on my face. I hate hair, bro
Like the less hair the better like what the fuck on
On your head, but on your body, bro like a supermodel
And I'm gonna
If I shave my beard
Maybe I can pull out of here
you can find a grey in there to pull out
I saw a couple earlier
there's a lot of girls that like it though
right if you look at her
the girl earlier than I see definitely liked it
some girls like Harry
bearded fox and some like
clean shaven
I'm not that Harry, aside from my face
I just can't
I don't know
of the
Well, I don't know say a shave at 8 a.m. By noon. I have razor sharp 5 o'clock shadow all over my face
But it's a razor sharp sprouts and now that now that's when I get complaints
Let's see. All right. What are you gonna do for your new day? You got the number from the girl
Oh, you go for beard looking good. Obviously you got her with the beard. So I wouldn't shave it off, right?
I'm going to trim it up and make it look proper, and she's going to be in that one.
If you've got that numerical scruffy like that.
My hair tops nice and short get the fuck off of me fuck off dog
Yeah, no, I'm all look nice
Like a mohawk shit. That's a that that works for you my black mohawk
Keep that your cheap it up shape up trim the beard and go
So drill it through the fucking bed
Look look look. I'm not a manhore no more. I
I ain't pushing she gave you a number bro. I'm looking for a real relationship. All right
Yeah, no, but I ain't trying to smash on the first date not on the first but why not why not I
I'm trying to uh
Oh, you know, are you on a wife? It took us so fucking a month before we parked
Yeah, it's that way you're going. Okay. All right. That might be a little, you know
that's that's that's how much we're hanging out shit how many dates but just fuck this shit over and keep her
just because you fuck your first date doesn't mean she's not wipey material
but i'll get bored is the problem i'm trying that's my plan on every first date i never take a girl like
hey we're gonna go out i'm going taking you out like i'm fucking you tonight and we'll take
Yeah, no, but nah, I feel my bullshit.
I get, I get fucking, I get bored.
There was one girl, one girl, I waited.
Yeah, I remember that, dumb bitch.
Uh, yeah, I've never waited before, so I, uh,
try to make a press start.
You motherfuckers, stop eating my shit.
Chevery, chevery, still loves.
I'm trying.
I mean, you know, I was just a terrible man who were there.
They look I did have a weight limit though, so I wasn't fucking yeah, but don't you know depends if you want a wife and
Baby, I don't know what you want, bro. I do I do you do all right?
So then forget my advice of fucking on the first date and be a gentleman
Take it all nice steakhouse dinner get her flowers open the door for her. You're gonna have to do all that bullshit
and not even, you know, and just have a good conversation cause the next day
By the weekend, you'll be fucking her and you'll both be in love and if you play any cards, right?
It's a little bambino's bambino's in the picture. Give it a couple weeks, you know, whatever the fuck
That's not a couple weeks ready crazy
Nope. No, if it's real love, you can't keep your hands off each other. You understand this is another thing
the
I'm just a running my intake. I don't know more bro. I fucking like that. No, what do you take?
When you take her out you waste followed your house on a date
You die the next day and she goes on and gets married to some other so
You better fuck it right now. Yeah, yeah, dude if I don't fuck that's fine. It was meant to not be
Dude, I've had 30 wives. I've been divorced 50 times and I fucked them like not on the first date
Every time it's sex is so fucking meaningless to me. And that's why I'm trying to rebuild a fucking meeting about it
Hi, bro, but they're horny pigs. They love sons
They need it. They need a balance of sex and money
They need a man that's gonna support them and fuck them good. That is the like perfect
dream
My man fucks the shit out of me and he handles business. He impregnates me
I'll hold the house down all day with these little kids as long as my man's coming home with loot
You know, that's what they want. They want a man to support them and fuck them good and that's the perfect marriage
I know my you cannot fuck them good. They're gonna start cheating on you. No matter how much money you make
You know, I know
it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not that it's not
A guy that's going to stand up for them, protect them, take care of them, pay, you know, put
a roof overhead and food in her mouth and she'll give you all the kids you want and
take care of the household as long as you hold up your piece of the bargain.
You're going to protect me and you're going to provide for me and you better fuck me good
every fucking day because sex is extremely important to women.
of the
It's easy to you know, get a girl and you know, you go through that Romeo fucking face the first six months
No one could do nothing wrong
Nobody you're just in love your fucking like Jackrabbit's and then she gets real
That's what honeymoon face
And then you have to keep that face going
If you cannot keep the Honeymoon face going, you're done.
They're gonna get sick of you and just be like, I'm out.
Because that's all they want, that same energy from those first six months.
The awesome sex, the protection, the gifts, the love, the love bombing, the You're My Queen.
and then it gets old right and then you stop buying them gay and this and that and then they get in
and you don't communicate and then now you want to fuck another bitch and now they're they have your
kid and they they resent you because you're never around they're raising everything in there but I
pay for everything blah blah blah and everything just boom yeah I'm the same motherfucker all the
that it has to be the same way 50 years later that it was on day one possible
that same love from that first date that same energy attraction lost
purely the way you guys can keep your hands over each other like animals that same love
has to live through your relationship if you can't keep that up
It's a wrap, and don't even do it
Don't go into that relationship if it's just bullshit
Like yeah, can we for six months, and then yeah, I'm gonna treat it like shit. That's what I ain't doing
I ain't being a little fucking piece of shit like it was before
I
Know you gotta maintain it see if you to get one and warm and all that but can you maintain it?
And you maintain that relationship that's standard what you showed them
I'm always a good genuine guy and those are the people that are mad 50 years
uh
Imagine looking at your face for 50 years
Everybody goes to their shit 50 year old fuck it 50 year relationship shits. They had some fucking rocky moments
It ain't always perfect, and it's never gonna be you're never gonna maintain that same energy for 50 fucking years
It ain't gonna happen. There's gonna be rocky points. You might go back. You might not you have to at a turn percentage
70 years you still gotta show her who is the man who's the boss remember what we come
Remember like you still gotta keep that level you can't let her
you know surpass you and step on you like
no remember baby remember
of the fucking plate runs the chill and that keeps him intrigued
no i know i know that's where i fucked up on the last relationship i let her
i let her try to start to support and then it just all went downhill
oh fuck
No, no, I gotta be the breadwinner. Well, hey, you know
Take care of the fucking shit
Keep my shit together and I get so fucked up. I know
Although it's all learning
Hey to be fair my ex fucked up too though, so the breadwinner
I
Said here with the kids
Thought I wanted to be a stay at home dance shit and let her be the breadwinner and then I'm like now
Oh, no, no, what are you crazy, bro? Oh, yeah, that will throw you into pussy land
She'll look at you like like like Mary Poppins did that's a trap don't ever fall into that
if
Which is actually just a man, bro. Let's take the real man out. She's gonna cheat on you like yo, Mary Poppins is home
Fuck the shit. I mean junkie. Yeah. Oh, dude 100% happen
Cuz I wasn't fucking her neither. Although I didn't find her attractive no more. So that was kind of part of it
But that's funny
Yeah, bro, they want a man. It was many years, bro. Like, I mean, no
Greensboro with a jackhammer tried to help her lose weight to you know, cuz
I mean, she was almost three. She was around 300 pounds, too.
Holy fuck!
Yeah, exactly. So when I started doing it, and the first, like, five, six, seven years, it was like...
Three, three hundred and fifty, hundred and sixty.
Yeah, is that what I heard? Three?
Yup, yup. So she went from 150 to 300 pounds.
You're not with her anymore?
What?
No.
Oh, yeah, man. It's all good, bro. Don't you know, right? All right. So everybody's got the shit to hold up on like I
I was already fat. I was like 260 when we started dating and I stayed there and then I got fatter and I got just
Literally, but I scaled in at like 295. I'm sure I weighed a little bit. I probably broke 300, but I never
but then I
made it a fucking thing and I lost 60 pounds in three fucking months and
That I quit drinking and quit drinking sugar monsters
And then I kept going down, kept going down, got down to bouncing between 205 and 230 because, well, winter weight is a landscaper and it's a real thing.
Well, yeah, I mean, and I tried to help her lose weight and she wouldn't have it and blah blah blah.
I mean, yeah, you know, I just lost fucking attraction, man. I was like, quite frankly, it was a little gross.
That's not shitty, but it's not shitty
Cuz I guarantee if it was the flip side and the chick saying that dude got fat and I don't like him no more
They'd be okay
By the way cheers
Yeah, 300 that's rough it's rough
That's a big woman. Yep. Yep, you know and
You know little brief in light in the sex life is like she would be on top once a year and that was on my birthday other than that I had a
nine years of being the
Control aside from once a day once a year
Yeah, you don't really want 300 pounds on top. Yeah, you know what I mean? I mean, I wouldn't even care
I was just happy. I didn't have to do all the work for once shit
Yeah, I don't know like yeah, you know was it yeah, yeah
I want to lay back and get fucking taken advantage of sometimes, you know, I'm not
You take me for the ride this time, you know fuck
I've been with a couple of big girls and and when they're on top it sometimes it's it could be uncomfortable
Well, it's just no it's just like I don't feel a lot of movement. It's like holy fuck like oh
You're yeah, I'm in there
And it's a big place to be in and you're feeling things moving around and I'm like yo
Anyways, uh-huh. No, I I know exactly. I know exactly
Even still though I was still happy with that once a year that I have to do work
But yeah, no, but it's because it was a different experience for me though every time that that onesie
True, but yeah, man. No, I just yeah, so I don't know either way done bitch about my ex fucking don't matter
She's a phenomenal human being great person just not for me. I
Don't mind a BBW, you know what I mean, but I do I'm not about that life. I don't like thick girls. I'm not about
No way shit. I
Want skinny petite. That's what I like
Okay
Although this chick isn't quite super. Uh, no, she's she's actually she's probably average size this chick I
from earlier today Chloe
but uh
Yeah, no, I mean, I really want an Asian chick. That's really
That's the dream, but
Then it could happen I'm too dark for that
No, that's not true Filipinos like black guys. Yeah, all right. Okay. I want like a
Chinese or a Japanese girl. Let me let me replace that
My woman is Filipino Filipino. I don't want the dirty Asian
I'm just kidding
No, or Korean I do a Korean girl to
Japanese Korean, I'd rather not Chinese, but I thought I'd settle for Chinese. I
Mean, I guess I do have Chinese tattoos prefer like I like or not
Sorry, I shouldn't say prefer because I don't have a preference, but I like Island girl
You know, yeah, you know, Hawaiian. I don't like tan skin that much, you know
In general like I mean
You know ignoring my black girls, but it's just tan in general. I'm not like a huge tan fan. I like
Yeah, I'm not a fan either. I say I'll be be dirty. What no, no, I like pale girls
I'll fat pig. Why were you on a fucking fat pig? I don't want to fuck a fat pig
I said it'll be me. Don't be a fat page. Hey, I'll read heads. They're interesting. I like skinny little emo girls
I've been with a few you can force up and down
Great, you can just force them open up the sit and spinners, man
you
This is getting bonie
Yeah, I don't like bonnie. I'd like you know, I don't like bonnie
Also, the other is proportional to like coffee, you know, you're not a little
Like say I like I'm a big psych
They can't be looked like put kids and of course, you know, he's right. That's the perfect woman
Like a tea cup that's tipping over man fucking any day now fucking broken back shit. No
Proportional it's got to be proportional with their body
The guy look normal. I want to
You gotta look normal. Yeah normal in the core of law
Exactly
What is normal though? Who is the judge of what is not not look normal just look
They got a look proportional to their body
Meaning what how what's harder like I said you can't
Exactly
According to you. There's nine billion people on the planet. Everyone has a proportional
Opinion like you buddy's got there. So when you say that that's just your I say is opinion of someone being proportional
But there's 9 billion other people out there that might think your proportional description
is insane.
It's out here rolling around.
It's not cool.
It's not cool, bro.
I love that.
It's giddy as fuck.
That ain't proportional.
I love that.
and they want things in serious like I said said the proportional six nine with a fucking pink pussy and long
Well, that's what it says and that's his opinion of proportion of be a pre-wrestling. There's nine billion other people out there
Hey look just because a nine billion people don't mean they all proportional fucking people
so proportional
And you that's Clay said
But hey still want to be with somebody who looks
Their body type body size whatever Katrina, how does your butt have a double chin? What is that even?
that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that
Yeah, it looks weird. It looks weird. Yeah, not proportional. Yeah. Yeah. That's what I'm you
want a normal human looking like the legs match. No, now I get it, bro. I've seen those fucking
Yeah, I think there's some proportional bitches 100%
If there's a chubbier girl, you know, I want her tits to match
I don't want them to be fucking a cuffs and her belly sticks
Yeah, it doesn't matter if you're two feet tall or ten feet. Just look like a normal
Proportional human your body don't have flamingo legs with fucking summer tits
Exactly
Got no fucking ass, you know
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
She's funky one stick more than all of them put together. It's my
Analysis she doesn't get enough cock
She was seven hour cock spunky looks great. She looks good. Oh fuck her. Yeah
But you know she's got kids you got a JT or Justin Ball as a boyfriend, whatever either way
It's oozing out of her like someone fuck me good
Like I mean, I mean glokey if you were lesbian, I'd still probably watch you know, I'm just saying
Low-key, I think it's a man. Oh, no, I said wish them said these men are making me wish I was a lesbian
Yeah, I mean, all right though
True true stay turn you fuck. Don't tell me you gay dick
The state to be L surgery what the hell's that potato head?
It's a as air of Saskatchewan. What's PBL surgery?
Brazilian
Brazilian ball
That's funny. I don't need a hardly they say Nicki Minaj and what a dick
Is that really what it is you can look up the BBL smell so I guess what happens is so what a BBL is
This is a fat from other parts of your body
injected into your ass fat and
Apparently if some girls get too much of these ass fat injections parts of the fat cells die within the ass
And so you actually have, like, dead fat cells in your heart.
Oh, my gosh, so you've got the smell of dick,
you know, depot, or whatever, decomposing bodies in your head.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's actually just recently come out and you had that.
That's crazy!
Oh, my God!
Like, what's that smell?
It smells like a dead squirrel.
and everybody you know once you smell it you would rather it be the fish market that
apparently Cardi B has like uh a dump of a smell bro i smelled that that
shit the dust smelled the other day and i was bugging on it i'm like yo it is the worst smell
on earth there you go there you go you want to talk about it on that looking like fucking Cardi B
It smells weird though. It's not that bad. It's not like you can't take it. You know you can
You're not gonna die from it. If I don't if I don't smell I don't want them to
Like sweat socks like that you had on for 300 years body odor and like a vinegar taste
It's got like a weird like vinegar smell to it as well
Natural is important. It's weird. Fuck the Botox. Fuck the fucking injections
I want to just natural just it smells like garbage rotting basically like knee rotting
And sweat sock
And knee rotting for two months and like some like vinegar smelly thrown in the mix
Yeah, some like basketball player just came out and said he was dating cardi b
But he didn't stay with her because her ass smelled like a dump or something like that. Oh my god. That's crazy
Garbage be oh god, you know that's funny
Yeah, that's what you get.
Honestly, what the fuck?
Yeah, fuck the fake shit, fuck all the shit.
Just be happy with your ass.
Even if you were all that you were on,
I mean, you know, within reason.
I ain't trying to have some chick that hangs off fucking hooks
and has hooks through her fucking back.
I mean, you'd probably be, you'd probably,
whatever you can get, because that happens
I ain't about that life. No, I ain't about whatever.
There's so many BBOs in Vancouver, they're everywhere.
the
You can feel smell
Get her as transplant and then it dies in her eyes and then she smells like she has a dead body in her eyes
Oh my god. Oh pretty much is the short story, right?
That's so disgusting, I mean forget about now wiping, right
Like you actually have to clean your ass cheeks because the sweat on them stings dead.
I
Harder to wipe your ass when you have a BBL to be honest
After she does a concert sweating on stage dancing around
person
No, no person's right like a little bit a little bit of poof. It smells like the streets of NYC. I
Swear to God. That's what it smells like
It's like the urine
vinegary
A Rhyme, food smell, it's death, it's the weirdest gift, bro.
A Chicago drink, a famous Chicago drink of choice.
And you know, don't treat an NYC smell like that,
and you're like, what the fuck is that?
Don't look at NYC and taste like some fresh milk
from Chicago.
Ah!
First and, bro, have any of you
had the pleasure of drinking the lort?
My Lord
My Lord, M-A-L-O-R-T
No
It's Chicago's, it's a Chicago staple
I, I, they're, they are some heinous
What is it, vodka? Like what do you mean? What is it?
I don't know. I'm pretty sure it's classified as a liqueur. It is clear
It tastes like sewer water mixed with a run-off
My god
Throwing a lime straight in your mouth at the same it is fucking atrocious and disgusting. Oh my god
There's something called fermented cabbage. It's called the
Kimchi. Yeah, kimchi brother. I will butcher all of you if I was put in a room
with kimchi, and they were like, the only way out is put your everybody, you're all done.
You don't like kimchi?
That is my nightmare.
That also smells like a dead body.
It smells like kimchi, vinegar, fucking foot odor, Theo, and rind meat all mixed together.
It's just the way it is, mouth.
I have a fucking shrimp face in the fish oil.
Bro, I'll butcher every, the whole planet over kimchi.
I cannot.
I hear a funny story.
That is why I draw the line.
You won't have to butcher me.
I'll eat all the kimchi before fucking you.
I'll tell you a funny story.
I went on a five-day hike in the Rocky Mountains.
And we went and we grabbed snacks before we went and we went to this Asian market and at the time I did like kimchi
And they had all these like other kinds of kimchi. There was one it was like a
Pickled like radishes or something in a package. So I bought them for a snack and we
We hiked the first fucking 24 hours. We got to like we're at like 12,000 feet at a campsite on the top of a mountain
24 hours in like
And I'm eating these things up in the mountain and my stomach starts fucking going wild and they're like
It was like fishy pickled radish, bro. It's smelled like fish paste. It tasted fishy
And bro, I had food poisoning at 12,000 feet on a fucking mountain in like negative 15 degrees in the snow.
It was so fucked, bro. It was wetting, but it was freezing cold, and I had to shit and puke, and it was, oh my god.
Listen, you would have died otherwise. You're in a survival situation. You would have frozen death. Good thing you had the shit.
I need my partner that I was hiking with.
Yeah, there you go.
He's fine.
She was like, holy fuck. Yeah, but she probably suffered especially the female, you know, they don't really like
Contact like you're pulling shitsicles out of you. I don't
You making chocolate anything with fucking fish paste definitely don't eat the brown snow
I thought I was having fucking elevation sickness and then I started feeling different. I was like, no, this is that fucking
Radish, that's called a rotgut. There's a big difference. I mean, yeah, that was your first understand why you were confused, but
Yeah, that is definitely the rotgut. It's not the food poisoning
But uh, yeah, no your first that's when you you shit out you should have a little bit more
You're not Asian. You don't hike on kimchi
Exactly. Yeah, you don't take the dry fish and all the crazy shit they eat hiking. No, you're actually impressive that you made it so far.
Impressive that you made it. Did you say you ate it before or did you eat it when you were already up there?
I had uh, yeah, well, he was like pretty close to the first campsite before
I'm gonna say impressive you fucking made it all the way up there
Oh, you want to look something up look up lake flow in the Rocky Mountains. That's where I went
It's fucking the craziest mountain
That actually I am I am gonna look that up this time is that does that name have something to do with what happened or?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
It's like it's like oh my god. This is up. Look if there was a place to die
I mean, I'm not gonna complain about it being there
You ever see those videos like women when I go like this like
I'll be fine they call flow because if the shit gonna be rolling down the hill so am I here I go
Fuck
I
Leave me one of them little fucking thumb lakes finger lakes down there, and I'll be happy the Finger Lakes
I mean, you know, it's gonna be round by the time I die after some oh, yeah, I get lost up in
They could get fingered in like there's a quote about the finger
That's happened many a times in history
Yeah
Okay, let's just do some weird shit
Also, do you know much there's like
that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that
About the poop. Yeah, I mean that was a dumb. I didn't really bring up an argument. I was just saying
Alex just you fucking return to get up the mountain
We're talking about poop Alex, which you should join what you didn't know to
Which I might have been trying to get into it with you Alex. You'd pipe down real quick where the men talk if you don't mind
Wait, which one?
Don't want me on you
are you meeting them or is he meeting himself, he's meeting himself that's a good thing and he should do that
I'm meeting myself asshole
good thing, good thing you've learned some manners
play some cards
keep it nice and good
you're New Yorkers boy
it's what we were running
keep it normal you would be in it boy
thank you
polite conversation is what we're having here
well let's pretend we're all fucking canooks
Uh-huh. What do you guys know about the finger the Finger Lakes up in New York?
Well, don't trigger him like that his uncle brother
Well, I mean it is the Finger Lakes in New York
Do you get lost up in the Finger Lakes?
Price my uncle got lost up somewhere in Chicago. You heard it. I'm not a I'm not a New Yorker
you know Alex
my uncle got lost somewhere in a fucking place
what do you know
I don't know nothing about finger legs bro
what the hell
are you saying finger legs or finger legs
you say like three different words at once
finger legs
what happened then
he's in the telescope
running
who
who I say
no
Bites nothing. Hmm. Interesting. Who gives a fuck about buying this on I don't know
Why are you talking about dickhead? He's not even here
But do you want by this son talking about crucible ghost on some panel? Like you use the crucible ghost. No, you know
The fucking heroin
you are the math pipe to actually know what you're brother
Cosum take a bless you
Cosum parents, look see on the train. Oh, that's you some tight salute. Salute. Salute
Salute, oh
That is Polish
No pollute Italian
No, the zoom type is German. Yes
No, we say that they say that shit. No, Salud is Spanish. What are you?
Salud all through South America when Thomas Meese is the Salute Salute is Italian
Well, then I guess when I guess I guess when Columbus came and raped the whole South
They adopted a couple things that's what happened
that's not what Columbus is came here with his boys
they started raping his way from Argentina all the way up to Columbus
he also started beating up fucking up
and that's why there's white Spanish people
still thinking they're made still boys
because they have Spanish blood and European blood because of
here we go
Christopher Columbus
lost cool debate from Alex
a lot of white skinned people in South America are descendants of Columbus
because he came here and raped the whole continent
Yeah
Most of the ocean continents are descendants of Genghis Khan because he not only
Population but he fucked he changed the fucking like he changed the fucking moves like the oxygen and the fucking weather
How many people he killed?
all I have I
Carbon footprint correct. Look it up. Oh, since you know everything
Columbia is named after Columbus
Columbia
Columbus Christopher Columbus look it up Wikipedia
Man that came here rate this way
from argentina all the way up and they got a statue of home in columbus squareman hand
there's a statue of the rapist i mean in columbus squareman hand i drive by every day and live
Like, wow, you raked like a whole continent.
And they got to have that.
Let's play a great game.
Great game for Columbus Day, my peeps.
Chicken's steep.
A nation got conquered, shocking, right?
Genghis Khan conquered how many nations?
Has it been not going on?
How long has that been going on, though?
Who are you making an argument for?
How long has that been going on?
Yeah, exactly. I'm saying all throughout history.
Who are we making argument for? Yeah, exactly. Oh, yeah, exact. I'm just saying it if it wasn't
Columbus, it would be
No, Lumbus, you know, somebody fucking else, you know
Everybody conquer shit all over. I get what you're trying to say there. Yeah, yeah
Americans native tribal people
patches Indians
Mayans all conquered other nations other god did battles fought for land territories blah blah blah blah whatever the fuck
It happens all throughout history
And you have to break that if you're gonna make that argument not you I'm talking about if you're gonna make the argument
You have to break it down far enough without making believe in that ship
You have to bring it down break it down far enough where you're not still in other people's land
Which you like to make the short-term argument, but you don't know how to actually make the argument
You don't know if you're talking about you're looking it up probably right now
and I go I'm literally on my phone talking to you like and I'll still get you uh definition of stealing land versus conquering
I think what what is the definition of conquering? I'd like to uh because I
I'd actually probably I'd probably disagree with that this honestly exact definition, but uh conquering and stealing are
I would say are very taking of ones. I mean if you take of one's property, are you not stealing of one's property by force?
No, it depends. Oh taking by force. Yeah, see that's why I asked and that's really important
There's a dependence and it is I mean stealing can be taking by force too, but conquering the same portion is
I'm not a great debater, but I don't know how you can, you know, I never claim to be the master debater.
Look at Pakistan conquered parts of India India took Pakistan parts back blah blah blah still wars going on over the shit
Look at the Middle East conquering each other's and it's it's all
history and semantics and bullshit it
To harp on one nation to you're the worst because you did this now fuck off
You're you're how did how did England start existing with the Anglo-Saxons and shit conquering fucking lands, right?
And who you know hates to hear this argument if you really is can I say it can I say the W word?
White Jones
Because Alex wants to talk about religion a lot. You remember the person that ate that non-diskind now
I don't know how why I've never heard Alex make a religious argument for it
I've known him for a while, but I also don't pay attention
I didn't make a religious argument, but we could do that too with it. I don't know crusades
jihad
All conquerings of land and conquerings of people and forced ideologies
Just as a couple
Hinduism
Yeah, all over the Taoism
Technically not religion, but still religion s. Yeah, it's yeah religion
Bringing up the the free what up Jay? How you doing up those?
Good brother. How you doing? What up Jay?
So how you doing? Oh Alex, I was gonna tell you this is the one we're still on the show. Oh
No, so just realized Brooklyn and crew and Brooklyn
Wait, were you asking what were you saying, Jay? Are you asking with Jay still in the show? No, no
I was not saying I was not trying like Jay's asking
Oh, yeah, he's I'm getting this up. You probably talk to him. He's probably listening
Yeah, yeah
You know
What's up? Yeah, I heard summer. It was J1. Yeah
I don't know what's up. I just came for the supermarket Alex
A group of any way it's a Brooklyn Brawler. What's up Brooklyn Brawler? Alex shut the fuck up Alex
All right, we're talking
I know you love your
Just coming your
Justin Boyle
He's a freak from out
Him and spunky or swingers
They're not different than Abstein and Giselle Maxwell.
Justin is Abstein and that bitch is Maxwell.
The same thing, they're not different.
They're swingers.
They're the devil.
Oh, they want his cock.
What do you want?
Did you get your fucking Oreo cookie?
I'm going to ban you on TPP, Alex.
I'm going to ban you on TPP.
It's my first time seeing a group of cops chase after white teenagers, Alex.
I
Know advice the dust
Love it put your hand up in the pool. Oh, the water's warm the wall. We got you surrounded
Are you from you from New York, Brooklyn? We got you surrounded
You ain't from Brooklyn from upstate yurt
No, Brooklyn BK
in the house for me.
You day one so what happened in the supermarket, bro?
These white teenagers were that this went in right and they started let's you know kicking stuff around and throwing stuff on the floor
Yeah, so then the cops came and they started running after them. I've never seen
No, yeah, the truth was white or black they were chasing the way vigilantes
We're makes they were mixed cops
Interest here about no, but
You know, did you hear about Epstein?
Fuckin we've heard about Alex. Wait, we're gonna we're gonna ride some rails here
And I don't want the us to all get kicked for it. So
You don't want to buy everything. No, you're gonna do no
I don't want psyche to start kicking people for it. Okay, okay
Top it just tells not to talk about it, dude
Oh, thank you to the background. He's gonna tell us not to talk. Yeah, we're not gonna talk about I will say it is bullshit with
Dan Bongino and shit going on, but it is all bullshit
They're enough. I know I know I know I would love to talk about it
But we have sensitivities like we can't talk about
the Middle East like
the two major nations
I'm gonna say the day
Psycho's moving people we're moving people right now
We're moving or moving people. I mean they're bringing them down. What's the word?
Alex was on the panel. He just disappeared and he does bring people down. Maybe you wouldn't kick them off
Maybe just put them back in the chat. No street. Oh
Hey, don't crucible. Oh, she did today. Good. How about you?
I was hot. He says
What did I heard? I heard a lot of people saying that it was hottest fucking day to that humidity though
Yeah, I was just like the leniest fuck man. You remember a couple years ago when Arizona it might still be that they had like a fire hazard
Couldn't let fireworks or anything, but it was so hot. There's a person that I know from high school
He lives in Arizona. He came over here and they literally like when it started raining
It was like like about eight o'clock in the evening. They don't went outside and fucking with dancing in the rain
This was a couple years back though
Yeah
Was it how you couldn't even you'd get in fucking major trouble even if you light a fire and you're fucking like even if you
Have like a farm home. You can't let it fire at all. Uh, it was so dry there
They didn't have fireworks like I don't know I have to look it up, but I think it was like years of some shit
My boys getting those bleeds and shit because of the heat
Those were the humidity. I don't know. I don't know what it was dried out. Maybe there was no humidity. It's fucking dried out, you know
Close house the temperature in West Virginia during the summer
It's like here in New York, nasty.
It's always good.
You got elevation, you go a little higher,
you go a little lower.
Nice and cool.
Okay, that's good.
No, no.
Well, yeah, nice and cool
if you get in the right spot, brother.
But even when that cold fucking water comes off that mound,
you laying that little creek, brother.
Hey, you keep your beers in that shit
and it's like a cooler.
Yeah, I want to I want to visit a
Those you're about there were shit like yellowstone and shit like they got like those like hot water so far
It's like a hot tub. I've never heard no shit like I heard about that cool water coming from top of the mountains coming down. I
Never heard a bundle of hot water. I never heard of that
Oh, I used to fucking I take my beer and I just fucking dig it into the sand a little bit
I'm not a little bit when it's out there that water runs across it
I think you could pull it for you might not be ice cold, but it'd be fucking it'd be definitely be ready to drink
You do for the mountain ears
It's a college team right the mountain ears. Yeah, man. Not anymore. I used to a lot used to be so big into that
I
I still like sports, but I'm getting older. I've been watching the UFC and Mike boxing the
Paranochal boxing the dirty boxing the slap the fucking you see that I've been into that shit a lot
Have you been to a USC event? I got I got my mom into it, dude
She like she watches that shit. Yeah, she watches that shit. She'd be stolen it. She ain't paying for it, but she'd be watching it
You getting them paper moves are free
Okay, okay, they're special like what that's 60 bucks
Yeah, yeah
Yeah
Oh
You don't watch rest not wrestling. That's not well. I know it's not real
But do you want to know but it's on it's on Netflix now. Well, what is it like the WD or whatever?
But now I don't watch that shit. Um, I watched Logan Paul a couple times, but I know I'm not into it
Logan Paul, yeah, Logan Paul they had a fight with a Mexican boxer
No, he had a fight with me brother
Logan Paul
had a fight with mayweather jake paul's little boxer brother which i would we'd have a whole debate because i actually think he's actually a fucking decent fucking boxer
but logan paul fought mayweather
even though they're like three fucking i wait dude different
oh i remembered i remembered that i ordered the pay-per-view
yeah jake paul's the jake paul's the boxer logan paul's the wrestler now
which was the one that's also in wrestling
Fake wrestling said the question we'd be Logan. That's the older one Jake. I think he's younger
He's the boxer. He's the one that knocked out all these like you know old-ass UFC guys and stuff
Which I got many debates about because he's a pretty good boxer
I mean all in all together
the
I
He got beat he got beat by J by our Jake Paul
And Conor McGregor like is a partner in the BKFC now and he's like well, you're never fight over here again
Obviously, they got to put their biggest star back and Conor's like the only reason you're here is because I let you but they're letting
Perry get another one in
Uh, of course, I can't watch female USC fighters. I just I can't you know why I feel sorry for them
They get beat up, you know, you get the the bruises they get bruised up. I
I'm being sexes, right? No, I can know I can watch it. I mean, maybe you're just being an old-school brother
I can watch it like that's too female. No, let me be clear if it's two females going to each other. I can watch it
But like I can sit there and I can sit there and watch two males like fucking sit there and get the elbow
Ate in their face like they're getting I can't watch that like, you know, it's kind of like hard
Yeah, it's just like a regular fight. They're sitting there throwing out knocking each other out like you're tapping each other out
I can't take the brutal beating of it. Then I feel I think that's our nature though as men
Yeah, we want to jump in there and like break it up like oh you she got her asshole, but it's over
It's over like we want to sit there and like yeah, you know, we got to protect
females I mean it's our nature yeah so there's nothing wrong against that but
uh they're setting their baying it out or they're fucking something they're like
going for like they're fucking just doing like yeah I'll watch it all day man I don't care but
like yeah there is what I'm saying is like
Baby, I don't know if you're taking too far. It's like you don't want them fighting
I don't care if they fight amongst themselves like as I get in a UFC bout
But I just can't take like the brutal beating. I think that's all me because
They could fight but I just you know and they get like because really brutal. I have to turn the TV off
Yeah, well as I was a man was a man you want to jump in there like hey, it's over or you want to break it up
Or you want to protect? You know, that's our natural thing to do though
Now close after watch a man beat up a woman
Now I'm okay with that now. I'm just joking. I'm just joking now. I'm just kidding
But I can watch a bitch get slapped though. She really really really really fucking deserved it and she got hit one time
I mean, I probably watch it
I mean, I'd probably be there, you know real close, but you know, I could see it
That's what I mean. Hey
If you shouldn't have been that close you got slapped. I mean, I'll but if you fall out like especially if you're you need clock the bitch
I mean
You get people don't know the under they don't understand the like the danger about fighting like when you hit that concrete
Or do you like get dropped like that? Like?
There's serious risk like that, you know like
But you're not gonna be okay ever again. You have a concrete certain way brother. It's over. Oh
Amanda come up Amanda Amanda watches you see to I didn't know that
I know, yeah, yeah, come up Amanda. Come come up. Yeah, I can't you know
Marcy was in her earlier. Oh Marcy
Yeah, well, she's near earlier. Oh
I think that was like an hour maybe
Uh, did they leave or did they get kicked out? I don't know. What happened to Alex and the other guy? They got kicked out
But it's psyche is psyche is still here. Well, you just kicked people out before you went to bed
Back stage oh backstage
It's backstage. Oh, Alexander's backstage
It goes I was kind of scary man there that the kids came in teenagers came inside a supermarket started tossing things around and
Yeah, we definitely don't want
Alex but the other dude seemed cool. Oh
You see what he's seen in chat. Yeah, we don't
Try to help you
Went full crash out on us. Oh, thank you
Oh, no Alex went full crash. I stormed the fucking back. I still on the jack on crash out. Oh the back track. Yeah
Yellow dude seemed all right
You say Yellowstone
But the TV show or the place. Oh, wait, I could feel wait Yellowstone. That's a place. I should know that
Oh, yeah, of course it is. I mean
It's like the biggest on of things like the biggest volcano, but yeah, it's a show. It's like a
It's that way they have the president the monuments of the different presidents
No, I don't know. I don't know if that's what that's the code. I actually don't know
Way off
I'm at her the other stone the TV show
I've never watched it
Saskatchewan, that's in Canada. Hey, Saskatchewan
It's just a show and are you are you Canada's right? Yeah
Got it got it got cool. Hey, you're the one that you said that you're you had a friend that played for them and then NHL
Yeah
Okay, he was a defenseman I believe
Josh Brown. Yes. Yes. I got to look him up. He likes to get down
Careful that mother he likes to throw them hands
Yeah, he does
Wait, so that's wrong. That was you in the kitchen, right? You was cooking. Yeah
cooking what sir
I just made sure you know it's back up cookin. What can that work sir? Yeah, let me see some hands
Turn on your camera. Let me see some hands
Stay check
Stay check. I always get confused with sticker
Let me see some hands, sir. I like Canadian bacon
me too
Little guilty pleasure of mine
Have you ever had smoked Canadian bacon? No, not me
Well, dude, once you get a small once you get a smoking man, I I
Two years ago why I smoke fucking everything I was a smoking, you know, I smoked cheese
Which is pretty fucking good by the way, but I smoke everything dude
I know you mean piehead. I don't mean that and I have a smoker. Oh, it's real
You say smoke around these New York's man, they like to smoke shit
You ever seen a man make a fucking bong out of the fish put cheese in it and then smoke pot out of it
Have you ever seen that? I've only seen it in New York. No, and I caught the fucking fish
Well, what what what part of New York the city or of state? I
Can just day was no we couldn't afford to go up there
Well, so we love we were looking over the river brother
So even to New York goes tell me what your experience you like you call that it. What does that call it?
Do you call that a river the Hudson River?
Our river okay, what size look down the west side. I'll be the Hudson River. Yeah
No, no, we stay on our side, brother
Oh
You're
You know I fuck it I'll put it on them you only put it on them
I'll put it on for them
It goes you gotta now I just see I I just see your crazy ass neighborhood whatever you want to call it
Yeah, I'd rather be in Chicago
safer in Chicago it is
Well, I know that I well motherfucker if you're running through a maze when you want to know what right and left is like you know
Where to go a grip around there. Yeah, I know where to go
It goes you got a you got a radio voice man. You should do radio. You should be on radio. I have a radio voice a face sir, so
But voice maybe
Yeah, you got a radio voicing and you never sound tired. You know, it doesn't matter what time it is
It would be four o'clock in the morning. You never saw you never
You bring it later and later and you bring up real points like
Yeah, I've been to your second city once but I've read being Chicago. I know where the fuck
I know what I know what's dumpster to lay down behind. I know how to dodge them. I go up there
I don't know where to go something pops off
It's like oh, this is the city. This is the city, but it can get real good. Let me use your word gritty as it called or is it
slimy
What you're making real crazy? That's my definition real crazy in a minute in a second you got nowhere to go
You got no which alley to run down
Cool, so you're talking to
You or all you New York people? Oh, yeah
Dude everybody in the chats New York by the way, I mean why won't say everyone but good fucking person just
I'm not familiar with these people in the trap. I mean states are it's from Jersey the same thing New Jersey, New York. Oh
Whoa, thank pretty sure you tell me it's from New York
No, you're sure. Oh, I'm not the option, right? Got him. Got him. Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
What people like pretend like they're from like New York, you're Chicago's pretty bad
I mean, let's be for it. Isn't that like I mean we can Google it. I wish someone works. I don't have it
Hey, yeah, so much from Chicago summer Barney rays. Yeah
And my friends were fucking my friends were in the suburbs. We were not
Yeah, we were part of the football we were part of the same football regimen
They're in suburb regimen here regimen cuz we weren't really
Tough spot rough rough area of Canada
Yeah, I guess yeah like like Drake
Yeah, it was disrespectful. I take that back. No, I think it's from Toronto, I believe
Right. Yeah
Drake is actually so he is from a very like wealthy neighborhood in
Toronto like Richmond area
But they grew up and hung around kids in Scarborough. So like
I mean, it doesn't make him gangster or anything, but yeah, that's the both worlds Hannah Montana looking at
Scarborough is not an easy place to be
And I wouldn't be the best place to be
Surrey Vancouver, it's like the Surrey of Toronto is Scarborough
Not a lot of white folks
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh
Let's go BPL big let's go BPL. Do you matter a big booty latinas do matter they shall stay
Okay, the fuck what your immigration laws the big booty latinas shall stay
They want you
No comment goes
They're gonna stay
I
That's what makes America great again, the big
I get a little emotional over my own
Oh, no
What's up, oh man, yeah, brother who you're on a journey nice to be out of jail with an around on like 600 acres
Let's go. Oh
I'm jealous. That sounds nice
Let's go rockin like an acre and a half here had a good day
Where do you go to argument brother?
Oh, man.
Sorry, but we should not really where'd you go, though? What were you doing?
Do you really want tell me?
If he was good, I presume he was looking at my cam, but I definitely did four pull-ups because that's about all I can do because I'm still fat
Four is better than zero you damn right
Well, I'm surprised they got through one to be completely fucking honest. It's been many years since I've done a fucking pull-up
What's that ladder dude?
That's exactly I
Can't it raises the ass cheeks and you stuff more fat behind it and it's a country boy BBO
Show me what it do. Hey ghost, show me what your peepee do
Don't the fuck you just say to me
His peepee what brings out the boys to the yeah, what's your peepee do?
Peepee things ask your mother
Ask your mother what my peepee do
Yeah
Hello
Because of the piano
No, I didn't
Why do I sit down people's conversations? I didn't send them people's conversation. I just let you talk for about a couple of hours
I think did I you said anything you wanted to say?
When I cut it off because I'm ready to take over the show. It's almost 11 p.m.
We're gonna be doing some reads and
Hope you had fun though
Oh
You you you start a show and you'll understand
Okay, well, you know, I don't want to see crash out I
Didn't say hi you saw me earlier
Anyway
Hi guys, Christian, are you okay? I saw the keyboard earlier
You're welcome Christian now
You should have been a mod hi as they have should have been a mod because
You were and then I
Forgotten and then I had you a whole verse in the song about how you were such a great mom
And I was like, oh my god
I'm sorry overlooked
Yeah
Okay, no, it's like do you think it's fine please guys
I was I try to let everything go like every you know some of the stuff
I didn't want to talk to that just because you know TOS early just because it's not like this topic of the show
But you know, I hope I gave everyone enough time. I think it's actually a few hours like now
Maybe like I've been on this is the six and a half hour stream. So
You know
Might want to take a little time for myself and just if anyone wants to do a reading and I'll do like I know we're so collective right now
I'm down what's up money for 20. Yeah, I don't know I should say I wanted to have the show open and stuff like that
You know, it's like it is, you know
You know, I just want to make sure I have time to do it. I want to say yeah
You know, yeah many money for 20 you guys, you know, he might have
I'll probably let you up. I
Let you up. I let everybody I don't care that I didn't let anybody up today. Let everyone up
So I'm not gonna be guilty
Okay, okay
Panel panel panel like
Should maybe be nice
No, no, I don't feel guilty. I'm not talking about you. Of course you don't feel guilty. I know you don't
I don't
Okay
Yeah
Got panel panel panel. Yeah, you guys
Panels are you know, you take a lot of it's like a lot of drama a lot of energy, which is good, but also I
Don't always feel like
being in some of these conversations, and I'm going to run this show like I want it to show,
but I do appreciate the panelists, but thank you so much for being on the panel.
I'll come back now, you're here. Okay. How's the chat doing? Is the chat having a good time?
I'm going to keep the panel closed for, I might open it.
I might open it
You know that feel like it
I'm not really feeling feeling it right now, but somebody comes up. I really want to talk to
Otherwise I'll do another collective from the chat
Oh, I don't know what kind of dry you you like talks, you know
Talk to me face-to-face like you do and with that like that like just that look okay
I was looking at like the thumbnail. It's like the mug looks on people
It's like it's the real smile that I'm on space
It's just mug can't stand it. Okay
This is a observation
Okay
There's something was supposed to be closed off like something was supposed to put you put to an end and it's like it's not ending
Thank you. It's like the world upside down. It's like the cycle is like still going if the doors still open
It looks like he's kind of like running, right? I don't know
Kind of looks like a little guy right there. It looks like he's like there's like still some kind of like or maybe you thought some doors closed
That's not close to you. Maybe there's still some kind of chance you have
I always believe in hope the last thing is Pandora's box, but the cycle is not over. I would say maybe it's a good thing
You know some because once cycles over is completion. It's like raid the test. Oh emperor. I mean to some of your power
the tigger, right? No, it's not tigger. It's
Here's a way to who's this one? I don't know. He's the Mufasa. There's not
Anyone know from the jungle book, I think, right?
Emperor really coming into all your power all your confidence
Maybe it's like, you know in time before the cycle closes that door closes. Let me see. I think that's enough
Okay, so let me see
Okay, I'm for maybe making a foreign decision about something okay nine of points okay nine of points
Abundance you got this abundance flowing. It's really good stuff. It's okay. You got the abundance flowing. Let's hope this you know
I hope that
This will continue to for all of us, right? There's just the abundance. It's a clear channel also the clear channel, right? It's all the way through
Yep, we need the poo
Just remember all the abundance you have around you and also the power I mean it's like even like, you know
You might not feel like an emperor. You might not feel like you you're
Because the all the abundance
But you if you like look kind of closely even if you think you're in a bad state
You probably are doing better off than you think you are or even like, you know
Okay, in this forecast in reverse, okay.
So this is forecast usually, you know,
forecast usually about, you know,
taking, don't take every offer, offer to you,
but I think there's like some kind of offer
that you're like not, you're like thinking,
ah, this is not gonna, there's some offer
you're like turning it down that you should like
consider maybe.
So it's saying don't be so quick to reject other options.
Okay, we got, oh, I got this seven of wands again.
It's like, you know, again, it's like, you know,
you got some kind of like long road ahead.
Oh, okay, you got to protect your stuff too, okay?
Make sure you're, everything is protected
because defenses may be down.
What's some advice for the chat?
I'm gonna have to do a couple cards of advice.
Okay.
Huh, wow, okay
Okay, well with these cuffs, okay
Like if I get out of your own mind
Get out of your mind about it and also like something like there's like you're confused about something
There's so many options. There's like a lot of options and it's like all of them look good
A couple of those are poison. A couple of those are
Yeah, they're put there like, you know
They're put there to entice maybe entice
There comes a bit ultimately empty look so it comes to all full too. They're full, but
They're full, but they're full because they're I mean everything's full of them there, right? Okay
Yeah
Might want to really um, watch your spending right now too, right? What's your spending and?
Make sure you give make sure you're
Giving to a worthy person the person that means it serves. Okay, my advice, okay
There you go, and you would like a card. Hey, Christina. Yeah, you were typing your type
You were talking in a chat. We all we're all we're talking to you
You weren't making
That much sense, but you know you're all talking. There's a seven cups of tea. Okay
Is it green tea or is good sleepy time?
Maybe
Camomile camomile
Okay, I thought I had a little bit no idea got the dish or the dryer going
Yeah, it's called it's called like I have you know, I can like produce a show. I was a little bit late
I was gonna end it may attempt 30 or the 1045. I
Was just listening to the conversation. I was like, huh time to wrap it up
Okay, don't don't be offended
Yo, yo, yo, I'm in the show I'm in the show I'm in the show
What is show mean psych?
It means that I'm creating content. I would like, you know, the most people to watch the content. I would like most people to be involved. I would like, you know,
people to be viewing the content, I would like people to be in the chat, supporting the chat, you know, supporting the show, participating. I don't know.
No reason what's going on? Hold on is it too loud? I was too loud
Okay, hold on. Okay. All right
See you
How I'm gonna go yo yo yo, I'm in the show yo
No, so proud doesn't mean to be in the show
It means to suck my dick. That's what it means. It means you're on the stage and everyone can see and hear you, and you know, you're on, uh, you're on stage. You're not, you're not in backstage, you're not in the audience, you're on the stage. You're basically partly opposed to the show in a way.
Alex, what does that mean to you?
Show, show, show.
I'm in the show. I know show me something really bad. I mean something very very
Let's not forget that site
Okay, because as so show as so sh implies like a secret
Train boy, he likes trains. So there's a show. Okay. So, you know, you know, you know, your show means, you know, a show meant
You know, you know, 1930s and I know something different than it means today
I just know about him. Okay, well me if something and I can literally
I can't talk to ghost he's insane. I can talk to psyche
Well, why you make no sense. That's why
I
Run it there's a debate you make no sense. You're meant to patient
You fat piece of shit.
Because I know you're fat and so you camped up mad times and you fucked up with your fat leg.
Hey, hey, Alex, go ahead.
Alex, stop.
Very nice of you, by the way.
I mean, you're insane, Alex.
Very nice. That was a very good debate style.
No, you just like you can't think what you can't know. It's like well, you got a very close veins. That's how fat you are
You don't the fuck you're talking about remind me of my grandmother's leg and your logic reminds me of a all-timer
Like you're all you're literally like there's something wrong with you and I feel bad for actually debating at this point
If there is something wrong with you, brother
And I you know, I think you got very cool. I can't say the word you're fat boy. Shut up your legs
Okay, that's a good comeback if you knew what the come back
I'll give you the screenshot of you
You want me to pull it up?
We're just talking about brother
About the screenshot of your face and your fat legs
He's came up you need to come up to get me
That's my legs make sense brother. He's a different person
He's not Tony
Go stay em. See suck a dick loser. Oh
This is the first time I've actually your goal shut the fuck up
All right, why are you crazy? Why?
Why why should I have a master computer shut the fuck up? You think I don't know it's you
This is the allied master. This is ghost AMC and crucible ghost psyche master
Can I find your time you mean do you want me to tell you what you actually met you?
You said master computer is that what I am?
Yeah, you're the loser
You're the master you call me and you couldn't do it
You couldn't do it bro
You call me the master you lose
You lose
Okay, how?
Suck my dick
Crucible goes
Okay, cool
How do I lose?
You can't answer can you
Yo shut the fuck up like you're fucking muted you try to take psyche down and you failed how
They one time I ever tried to take him down go ahead
Where to prove that I'm not through whoever you thought I was how did I try to bring him down go ahead
You're gonna sit there
Have this conversation again Alex. We have it every time
It's always the same. It's always the same. Let's say I'm not even I don't care if he is or not
If he's two personalities, at least he's like nice on this personality. So
Though you should
You should care
Don't care
Next to you and you knew it was me you would say I don't care
Yeah
Man I don't care
Punch that maybe somebody
Jesus Christ
Punch their face
Maybe you killed them
I tried to judge you a little bit
Reincarge that person you were telling me about
Take a photo
Don't you fucking comment logic
But they get down we heard enough of it your shit in the chat. I don't know but really it's kind of disgusting
That's not
Fucking reading you remember Jesus the Bible. There was Judas remember remember Judas remember
For money
Try to kill you like and yet you're on the cruise saying forgive them. I got money for district
I am doing no way so I got 30 gold 30 silver
Yeah
But I don't
But you did you just unalived himself to he hung himself in a tree. Yeah, but a ghost wouldn't do that because he couldn't live with the
Gilt because that was actually his friend. It means like it was never friends
Yeah, so he wouldn't be guilty, but he didn't do anything anyway. Go. I mean, I was sorry, but he's fine
This is a little harm. He's like a friendly ghost. He's like, you know what you actually you know what fucking I did it
I did it for 30 silver coins. That's what I did it for. I thought my god
I fucking I did it forever. Yeah, those 30 silver folks so good to me
Everybody got fuck. I flagged everybody basically 30 cents for 30 cents for 30 cents 30 dimes 30 silver coin 30
So 30 dimes. Okay. Well, that's dimes are still there. That's some real silver in them. Yeah
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't
100%
Tony shut the fuck up like we don't know you're gold if you're gonna call me Tony call me Tony
My Tony is so last name. You're a little choo-choo train slender dog
Tell me Tony much. If you're gonna call me Tony. Tell me Tony much in a year. You failed you failed my friend
Times and now you're here suckin
Perfect, you're not Tony Montana you're Tony. I am Tony. It's who's the boss
And now you're sucking our cock
What cock in my sucking on sir psyche's in mine
the same
you would have to consider Alice more than you did me though
that's really a soul sandwich
Ray won, you can't bring your little friend into this
what do you think Ray won is going to help you
shut the fuck up Ray won
hey hey hey
you can't bring your little rat brain into these fights
you guys lose
you
Your crucible goes good. Oh, yeah, what's up, brother?
Go suck a dick motherfucker. I
Own you. That's what I do. Yeah. Nah, you do nothing. You do nothing
Coastal emcee you do nothing but suck my dick. That's the only thing you do
the
Psyche's a winner
He's a winner. I know you don't like
Motherfucker remember that
We're gonna do one argument at a time. Yeah, whatever. You lost there. So you lost that you lost you lose you lose
Thank you. Isn't what exactly like he wins you lose
And the story oh, yeah, no, it's not in the story you gotta explain like he wins and you lose
Your fat ass, your fat decrepit ass, loses while Psyche's beautiful, super-model ass
wanes.
And people love him, nobody loves you, you loser, nobody's coming to you, nobody cares
about you, but everybody loves Psyche, you lose motherfucker, you lose.
You lose motherfucker. You fat piece of shit
Sike is gonna take off. He's gonna have 10k soon. What are you gonna do then go?
He's gonna bury you motherfucker and you're gonna die you understand you fuck fuck
With him you piece of shit
You understand you can't do nothing psyche wins
You in the YouTube funeral
You understand boy
So I'm gonna be in a psyche stick. You see how you're under me right now motherfucker. You see me
Running the show you're not gonna run the show
Me and Pat run the show, motherfuckers.
You don't run shit.
So I could dig.
I run you right now.
Okay.
I run you.
And I always run you.
Go ahead.
Always.
Run me.
Always run you.
You can pull up all you want.
We're just gonna grow and grow.
Run me right now.
Shit, crap.
Fuck.
You're too stupid.
You crap.
You piece of shit.
Take hold of what's the argument? You're too stupid to have that you're glad and you run nothing. It means psych on you
That's the argument. Okay. I own you. I own you motherfuckers. How do you own you?
I own you. Nobody wants to be a dirty fat fella. Shut the fuck up
What? I'm not a little hate. Shut up. Yeah, you are
I have computers in front of me that tell me who everyone is you're gonna tell me you're an Alexa one
Say it again. I dare you. I'm asking you. I dare you. I dare you you tell me
Right one you're an Alexa one. Shut up. Shut up nigga. And I know where you are right now
on the map
I see
It's like I don't even care. I don't like you're been yelling at him for half an hour. Yes. Thank you psych. Thank you psych
I can't get a word in with that guy. Oh my god. Thank you
You're welcome
No, i'm sorry. I know I was just like I was getting my like I just had like some stuff delivered just now
So I was busy and I uh, but yeah, he was just going on and on
Anyway
Alex, you know, we love you, but that's when the delivery room exploded with the stuff. Oh, come on. Come on
Come on. There's no way that there's no way that guy's a cop in a no way. Oh, he's me
I mean, he's maybe the multi-curry
But it doesn't matter. It doesn't matter. He's you know, he's the nice person
Let's just
Let's just forgive Alex for the night. Okay, me and guy just got a lap dance. Oh
Hold on to stay turn. Okay. Oh, that's okay. You're both single. All right
This guy on the Simpsons. Yeah, hold on. No, I think he was on the Beverly Hillbillies. He played a fleet of
I'm just
You know, you know, I clean this I love your accent actually very sunny
Yeah, you mean jet jet clamp it. Oh dead clamp it. Yeah
And in a nice way, he's cute. He was actually a very good looking guy
Um, let's see are you insulted? Please don't be insulted. Oh, it's just
You've heard that before ha you've heard that before no
Okay, I'm really sorry you're mad. Okay. I'm so sorry. I guess don't be mad. Don't be angry. Come on. Oh
It was okay. Let's kidding. I was kidding. Okay. It is him
Yeah
Clubs or cleats up where it was on a sense. Oh, yeah, Cleetus was on a sense of the Simpsons
Give it back at us more like this. He's not smaller. Hey, what's your name? He dig? Oh
No, we've got to get 30 kids in the I don't know some sort of really bad. He's got his name was Cleetus though. I
Can't do this. Oh, hold my laundry. Hold on a second. Hi babies
Okay
Okay guys
Okay, okay. Okay. I know it's been really stressful lately
But in the middle of summer it always gets a little bit. Oh, I was a little bit hot around here a little bit
So, okay, so I don't my glasses were my glasses. I'm blind. Okay
It's wrong. That's the whole thing. It usually does get hotter during the summer
Well, I know but it's again I'm saying like that's kind of coincides with like, you know every every summer kind of like
like the heat kind of
Turns up in a metaphorical way too. It's like there's a lot of you know, what's that song? It's a cruel cruel cruel summer
Leaving me here on my own. Yep. May I know the song? Yeah, and so it's kind of like that. I don't know if I explained it right
That's the best I can do.
Where are my fucking glasses?
I can't see without my glasses.
I put them down.
So what's that woman's name that sings that song?
I think it's Banana Ramma, but I'm not mistaken.
I'm not sure their actual names,
but the band is Banana Ramma.
I think it was probably in the 1980s,
the early 80s or something.
That's what I'm thinking about.
Um
You know that song though actually Taylor Swift the cover of it, too, but I'm not sure. I don't know if it's very good
What else guys anybody know
Dang no, it's the same woman that sings the teenagers in America
Teen
Is the same you think so I don't know I think that's like more like it is that like Tiffany or something I don't know
Oh, yes, that that that's our Tiffany doesn't sing cool summer though
That's not Tiffany that things that Tiffany sings
Like I think we're alone now. That doesn't seem to be anyone around
Persian just said it came while it's Kim Wilde. Oh, okay. Yeah, so we were both wrong. Oh shit. Well
There we go. Kim Wilde
Okay, guys
Doing my laundry. Wow. I got a lot of laundry to do tonight. Okay. Oh
Oh, it feels good to clean I'm gonna clean my kitchen tonight. Oh
Left all day. Yeah, can't Kim Wilde song the best version of
Cool summer. She really did
Leaving me here on my own
It's the crew
Okay, hold on
I think I'm going to get some stuff picked up.
Ah.
How's the chat doing?
Is it having fun?
Hope so.
Just putting stuff in the washer.
Got to do my dishes.
My clothes in the hallway.
Oh my God, there's so many dirty clothes.
Okay.
Excuse me, excuse me.
Huh? What's up? What's up? Sorry
Hello
No, what are you doing?
If you live alone, why don't you just use paper plates? Why don't you just use paper plates and plastic forks?
Mean really yeah, I have a dishwasher and so it's like I might as well like you know
But I really don't like I usually do eat out of the cartons or the cake. I don't really use that many
that many
Whatever they're called, you know utensils or paper plates or stuff, but it's just like I haven't done my dishes
I just got they got so they got like a big plastic thing that you could get from targets and
It's got like 40 forks
40 spoons and 40 plastic knives
Okay from target. They're plastic. They'll be rare. Hold on. I've never heard this. No, they do a target home
That's a good deal. I don't know you go to target like yeah from
I'll have his whole foods targets too far to walk is like two miles away. We
But yeah, that's a good idea. I mean I can get him probably at the place too, you know, but uh, yeah. Oh, what's in here? Oh?
Somebody brought this detergent over and it's okay
Okay, my god, it's will to rant, but what are you doing here will to rant?
Who is that?
Hello?
So, the whole thing is this
Wilderant guy,
he used the...
Okay, so you know
who Rusty is?
Yeah, she's a nice
woman. Very, very sweet.
That that is her ex-boyfriend. That was Rusty's ex-boyfriend. Oh, really? He's here. He's here now in your room
Hi, Rusty's ex-boyfriend. How are you?
Welcome to the show
What brings you the what brings you to these here parts?
Sorry, that was racist. Hey, what's wrong?
Let me clean up a little bit.
Oh, yes.
Okay, let me draw.
Who said female just came up?
Um, does a female just came up? Who's that? Let me see.
Is there she in the back chat?
Are you talking about in the panel or the back chat?
Hello, I thought I heard someone on the chat
No, no, no, no, okay. I'll go back. Oh, we're never matter
Guys are you hearing are you hearing a female voices you I think are you lonely array? Are you lonely? I'm just kidding
Hi, sir
You're that who is that? I sort of female voice my wife who oh my god
I don't want to hear who just said who just said that who just said who just did that
Who just said that said what?
Hi, okay, the cat meowing me. Who just are you who did oh
Well, yeah, it's your your woman's voice you heard a woman's voice guys
Sometimes when I'm on the phone, I'll say hello and they'll say oh hi ma'am and they'll say the thing
I'm a woman sometimes, but I don't think I like sound that much
No, you got you got yours. You got your sister in there. What you have something?
No, no one's here.
My sister
And
This is about her own life. She's not gonna be sneaking around my apartment in the middle of the night
vanilla slice with Matt
No, I'm gonna go back in the um chat
Oh, so I'm the one you're calling Sly Scotty. Oh, okay. Let me just think of all the things you said about Sly. Oh, no
Okay, okay, so anyway, I can't find my my glasses, so I'll be squinting for a little bit
Your back hurts
Don't you have a boyfriend or four that was to stretch out your back
Not stretch out break not break crack. I don't know. Yeah, chiropractor
Morphine power after it gets really bad, you know
Okay
Look, okay, so Delray your wife. This is huge vagina. Okay. Okay
Is oh, she was her name giant labia because we did have giant labia in the in the chat before but they haven't been here for a while
Have you seen giant? Is anyone seeing giant labia around? Has anyone seen giant labia? Is there a giant labia in the house, right?
No, okay. Oh, here she is. Hold on. Hello giant labia
Yeah, it's not maybe it's me dickhead. Oh, where you glad to say so I can't find them. I'm looking we'll find them
That's the only thing that matters. You're gonna give up your eyesight over fucking
Labia and me you better find those shit right now dick. I can't find them
Without my glasses how I supposed to see I can't see my glasses without my glasses
We'll find them bro. That's my whole point nobody cares
you'll be blind as a bad nobody cares well interesting so you don't care about yourself
so how can i care about you if you don't care about you i do
they're on your head dick they're on your head
They're on your head you retort
They're on
My god
I'm out. Thank you. That happens to me all the time, bro. I swear to God that happened me the day
I'm like with my sunglasses. I was wearing them
My job is done. Oh
Well, I love you up. Oh, he left. He said his job. That was really that was all he just was waiting for the woman relationship
Right by my glasses, and then he just leave
That makes sense. Okay. Yeah. Yeah guys. This is my life. You know, that's how it goes usually
What time is over there?
Well, there's play live in 24 Pacific. It's a
11 12 12 224 Eastern
Central that now
No, Mr. Mr. Coldplay wins back to England. Okay
Mandy
I was many the one with the large vagina
That's kind of doxy over this that you live or you do live on the east or the west coast
Is that too specific for anybody? There's only eighty eight four million people in the United States. Anyway. Yeah. Hey, Ray
How are you right here? Ray
Ray Ray are you there?
Hello, I think we lost them. Hey, uh-oh Damien's calling me a loser guys
Yeah, I do feel like a loser because I haven't gotten any donations or
For memberships, you know today one today, maybe I don't think so. I do feel like I'm a loser. Yeah
There was hey, so it was upside
What's up? No people are just saying I'm a loser the loser podcast people are just like saying horrible things about me
Let's see. Oh
No, it's okay. You're not a loser. You got you got one of the best you got one of the best new channel of psych
You got one of the best new channels. That's true
Well, now, yeah, thank you
But now it's I mean it's been around for like, you know almost a year now
So it's like now I'm not now I'm supposed to be now
It's like I'm supposed to be like on a good upswing and now it's like it seems like everyone's like turning on me
So that's his life Coldplay and I are boring. Everyone knows it. Oh coldplay is yeah
Pat, let me tell you Pat somebody's useful at the screen door on a submarine
Nobody seems to get less done is a disaster. Everyone's talking about it. He just can't deliver sad. Believe me. Who are you you bitch?
What are you talking about get out of here? I don't need to hear your crap
Go stuck on a dick
Lee
Okay, anyway
As long as you're talking to me right if you're not I'm so so sorry. I'm so sorry
But if you were talking to me, go fuck yourself. Okay. Anyway
Yeah
You know what we use full a submarine door on your screen door on your submarine Mandi. That's what I want
That's what I hope for you. Okay
Anyway
Guys, I'll get sassy. I'll get sassy. Yeah, we'll go
We'll go guys. I mean, we don't wield the rat. What are you waiting for money for 20 wheels around there waiting for you leave me the fuck alone
I don't know so so psych psych so the whole thing is psych
What was the deal with that pit that you posted last night?
With the what the pick
The wet what I post last night yeah that pick on your community page
Okay, yeah, that was yeah on your community page. Yeah, that's me
Yeah
you like it so so that's that did you
Did you did you meet will the rat before you posted that?
No, who's will the rat that somebody I look like this like me
Hello
Hello, who's will the rat?
Hello, I don't think you just asked about him
I know I'm yeah, no, whatever. I'm just saying. Oh, is that Rusty's boyfriend?
Rusty's ex-boyfriend, you mean? Yeah, that's Rusty's boyfriend. Why did you post him a pic?
Why did you post Rusty's boyfriend a pic? Why would you think I posted him the pic?
Well, you surely, well, you surely did. What did it say?
How did I say wills or ants?
This is what the pick is for who did I say that I didn't say that
Okay, go ahead. Oh, no, okay. What wait a second just wait a second. Yeah
I'm clicking in the car. I'm clicking the comments right now
That's
Okay, I mean you got you got a bunch of losers in your comments
I know looking for a cat
Well, what'd she say?
What does it say?
Oh, here's Will. This is Will Durant in the chat right now. Hi, Will. See, I'm not, that's not me.
Oh, so Will, are you, um, are you Rusty's, his boyfriend?
Hello.
it's a little like that
Guys
Hello
Will the rant will the rant has his mother-in-law as his pick
Okay, well you're not giving me
You're gonna let him promote it. Are you gonna let are you gonna let him promote in your room?
He just he just now said live in ten
I don't care. I mean, I don't even know who this person is. He can go fuck himself. I don't care really
I mean, it's like go ahead and go to Will Durant's room. Please. I think leave me alone. Okay
Anyway
What your cousin okay, so I don't know who think that I mean it's like I don't get it
You're not explaining why that you said something I posted something last night
About it. I didn't I didn't I just posted a picture of myself or you
You'd like me here with Miss Vita and the psychies to call play mr. Easy mr. James in the suite and others for peace
Yes, well will who are you? I can choose to right?
Explain please
What you owe me you owe me apology Ryan, and you really do
Person you're telling me
Okay, so please are you gonna explain?
Hello, no, okay. Well, it's like it's too difficult to like
To like, you know get out any answer. I keep asking just to go ahead explain it
It would just take two seconds to say oh, I meant I thought this I thought it's like no
He'll he's just silent. Hello. He's not like it. He's not like an extra on King of the Hill
Okay
Here you really got he can shed some light on this. I mean someone someone comes gonna make
What do you want to know?
What is he talking about? He's like saying I posted something about the will go around answer me. It's got me. What about him?
We got we got a grown up here now. We got got here. What's what's the problem up here now?
There's no problem. He's going live in ten minutes. He said well, so what man was like what does that have to do with me?
Like why why is not people come over and say hi and that was it?
Okay, well, I mean, I'm doing my show right now. I mean, he can post his link or like have a mod post this thing
I'm gonna be happy to promote. I just think I don't know
Oh shit, but people are just like talking like tell me all these things. I don't know. I don't know what you want
No, no, he's not a threat. He doesn't do tarot
Okay, I'm not saying I bet it's like but why is it like now? I'm being like people are like
Wild Iran is not a threat
Will Durant is gay as fuck. He's obviously here for you. I mean, I'm just saying
Okay, well, I mean, I think he has his mother-in-law's photo. I don't okay. No, no problem. Well, I mean
He's married so he's how gay is he if he's married with a mother-in-law that makes sense
So I guess he used to so will used to be will used to be straight he obviously went gay now
He went gay
It's okay. Well, you know, I have enough going on. That's why he's here psych. It's why he's here
Well, you're just an endating. I don't know. I need to see your real photo. You know, I don't think
I don't know what's going on, you know, I don't know what's going on either.
I'm just confused as much as you are.
It's a bit of bullshit.
If I need to, I'll just end up, I'll stop doing panels, I'll just do like, you know,
I'll just do live shows and everyone will eventually lose interest in me and then it'll be over.
Great, what are you doing?
People went the attention so bad on my panel.
Like, why is it my panel?
It's like, you know, there's so many shows.
I'm up here all alone, God.
I'm up here all alone.
I'm up here all along God. Are you guys kicked me from the discord?
If you're gonna be like that, I'm gonna leave no, I'm a fucking cry about it all night and you know, it's the truth
Okay
Well, anyway, so okay, so anyway, okay, I guess we got that right. Okay. Well, that answers that now. Thank goodness that's resolved
Anyway, yeah, I don't even go to discord anymore guy. There was just a it's gotten too ridiculous
I sometimes I answer messages from there, but I don't go my discord anymore. It's like it's so full of
Primal investigations and you know, please report and fake police reports then it's just like it's just going it's gotten too messy
And so, but you know, but you did it's so psyched
Do you see that eraser rain character down there? Oh, yeah
That is an American terrorist that is an American
No, she's not she is not Italian that is a Mexican terrorist she only means harm to gringos
Eraser rain means harm to gringos. That's what I mean
What does she's married or isn't she dating the guy at H.E. or something? I'm gonna be confused. I'm sorry, right?
Is it you? No, I'm telling you eraser rain
Eraser rain means harm to gringos and what language does that mean that what language?
Hello, I mean it's like Hunter Green. Do you know what a gringo? Do you know what a gringo is like a white person?
Yes
Okay, she's dating a white guy though
JT is not a white have you do you have you seen a picture of him?
What what is he I
Don't know what the fuck that guy is. Do you?
Don't know. I mean he looks kind of I mean, you know, I just found out that I say is black
And so I don't even know what what's white or black anymore. You know, I mean
He's a white
I am not sure JT is an earthling
Look at this guy. How about that guy looking how white he is?
Ronald McDonald evil evil Ron McDonald. Isn't Ron McDonald's a regular one evil. So it wouldn't be the good wrong. I don't know
I'm just confused for it. Okay
Say Ray you're an insta with your mother. Well, no, why are you mad? Well, Ray? Do you have a girlfriend or a wife?
She should be hate, you know, you should be
Kind of like having sex with the right now. No, so but because you raise a rain kicked me from discord
Okay, now it all makes sense. Well, it's what okay. What's the point? What's the point?
No, he's good. He's a good role my dog, but the whole thing is I don't care. I really don't care
Okay
About what?
No about nothing I don't care about nothing
Well, that's not a very good way to live, you know, you don't care about anything, but so yeah, but okay
So if you're gonna teach me what do you care about psych? What do you care about?
What do you care about well first of all?
You could care about your own life, you know, you have this ability if it's life your own life you're protecting
No, I don't I really don't care if I die. I don't okay. Well, no, you mean you will die
I mean we all will die. That's the point is like it's not like life is not promised like, you know
Guarantee a second longer, right? We were just it's a gift, right? And so
So just treat it like a gift instead of like a no
Eternal eternal no no no eternal life is a gift not this life
Hmm. Well, it's like think about the things you get to experience in this life. I mean in spirit the spirit worlds you get to
You know walk around you get to have like your own your own
human being to be do your own
You know worlds to live in and the beauty and like the people that love you and the people you talk to you and visit in the
Relationships then yeah, but but the whole thing is this world is under a curse
You believe that?
Well, this world is maybe under a curse, but also maybe it's a counterfeit world
It's like, you know, this is kind of a copy of like, you know copy of the kingdom, but it's not the kingdom, right?
And so it's yeah, and I I agree. I agree 100 percent. This is a simulation
You're right. I agree
Okay, yeah, I'm saying there's there is something real and this is a copy of it. This is kind of like a copy of it
it's like a
And we don't know if it's a creation God God made this in them
Like six days or something like six days or something
Well, God no God created the yeah, well, I don't know if I got rid of the earth in six days or whatever
But it's like, you know, whatever Lucifer is the ruler of this earth not not God, but yeah, you're right
You hit it on the head again site
Ah, the devil is to God the devil is to God of this world
You did it again site. I
Mean it's just bingo. Bingo. This doesn't mean it doesn't make sense to me. Yeah, I just figured I understand
I understand a concept because because that's what Lucifer's sin was was pride
He wanted he wanted to be God he wanted to run his own world
Yeah, and that's why you and that's why you and so many people and in the Catholics are so blind
I'm blind. What are you talking about? I just I just told you who the whole whole rules of earth is
I'm blind. What are you talking about? Who's blind? Tell me
explain explain
No, I know so so I got okay. I got to go P
One extra one. Why don't you go fuck your little black bitch?
Bronze versus. Oh my god. Oh my god
Don't fuck up with your bullshit man. Everything that comes out of your mouth is bullshit your ex out one
Are you?
I don't sound anything like that!
Bitch in the background!
I don't say anything like that country. It's it's too guys. It's getting too confusing
I don't I don't want to think everyone's everyone else. It's too confusing
I don't care guys. I mean, I'll say we're all like human beings
But it's like when you're saying oh this person is this person and then it's like well
It gets you know, so side side side side come about I gotta get up and go pee
You tell me your thoughts on reality
Okay, yeah
It goes row row row your boat gently down the stream
Merrily, merrily, merrily, merrily, life is but a dream. That's my sense on reality
It's just a dream
Okay, um whole actor tonight is a set because he was kicked from the discord. Okay
I'm a very sick discord discord sucks
You know discord is really like a bunch of like hackers and really bad intention people you're lucky
You get to kick off there just do you just run run run for the hills
Okay, not a good place. No, I like I like I like this chord. I like this chord, but
Right erase rain kicked me
Rain why do you why would you do that? This guy's this guy's so so sweet. Come on
He's a nice this guy from the south. I've ever even talked in my life. You better let him back in
Okay, I tried I told her I told her she didn't listen to me though
She never listens to me. She always says, oh, I don't like you. She's like, you're an idiot. It's like you
go away
She's never listened to me. No one listens to me. I have a good advice though. No, no, no. I know that's that's JT
E-rape, E-rape Serene is JT's girlfriend
And she's a total butt. She is a she's a real jerk
Thanks to Tom. Thanks Tom. I smoke crack with your mama. Okay. How about that? Okay?
Okay, so Alex, would you want to come back?
I'm talking about just talking to the guy in the chat. It was saying some stupid shit. Okay
Yeah, oh
Thank you, you've a raw McDonald's you've a raw McDonald's the chat fucking endorsement
Okay, okay, but you know you came out. Hey, you're supposed to crack under a bridge, dude. Yeah. Yeah
It's been a minute. Yeah, rain kicked him here read into if you control. Oh, so are you a troll? Um, Ray
Are you trolling me? Is this your real accent? Or you are you but you're a black guy, right?
It's like a deep very white voice and you just talking this this accent. So like
cool people. Hello, I
Think I got it guys
So
Okay, we lost them. Okay. Well, I guess it's time to add another song. Let's shoot the song now. Let's do the next song
Let's do it. Let's write a cool song. Let's see
Hmm
He's a grandfather shul
Let me just look at the chat right it's gonna go take care of a little business in chat. Oh, oh
He has oh he's gone he left
Hello
Hello, hey, hey, how are you? Hey? Hey?
Hi, hi. Hey, how are you? How are you tonight? Hey? Hey?
Hi, I don't suck dick. I'm not gay, but hey sure. Okay, okay? Sure. What did take he doesn't believe me?
He thinks I'm gay you think I suck cock
Say say I do that. No. No. No, I only I suck yours
You you say it's you say it's too gay to do it to me
So you won't you refuse but I I do a bunch of them, bro
I love pussy and tits and ass. I love it. The face is so
You know your faces vary from pretty ugly
But they're all the tits the ass and the legs and the pussy. They're basically the same thing
So well separates women is their face and how pretty they are and carry themselves
Because every girl has a tits and ass and a pussy. So that doesn't make you special
Every woman listen up to this what makes you special is your face
You're either ugly half ugly or pretty or beautiful and naturally
Super beautiful. There's some girls out there that are just so
Amazingly beautiful naturally. They're like, you know other girls hate on
Because there's a lot of ugly bitches out there a lot of girls are ugly
90% of the women are ugly. They gotta put makeup and do all this shit to look like half decent
They gotta turn into clowns
but there's a few girls out there. They're just naturally so beautiful
That is scary and those are the ones I love
That's the one I want next to me
I don't want some of you pig that's to wake up and turn into a clown to look beautiful
Name your name your mom. I'm
Cristiano, you know Ronaldo that soccer player
Yeah, yeah, his wife. That's what I'm extra. I'm sorry miss you like to hear what's up a little Christian. I don't run out those wife
That's one of those kind of girls
Okay, that you want yeah, that's what the wife I want next to me
Um
So like a 10%
the
They don't got to put makeup. They can wake up, you know, you know any they can put up any clothes. They can wear anything. They're just
Naturally beautiful some girls have to
Do things to get to like half of that stage
Like I'm so ugly and weird like I gotta do all this shit to look something normal
But some girls just we got a bed like complete super miles
Beautiful lips face cheeks eyes hair legs body
Don't got to do a thing
And every guy just wants them like wow that is one hot girl
Some girls have that power and some men do too by the way
Some guys just wake out of bed, and they're just super models and every girl just wants them some guys got a work
Gotta do that. Hey, they gotta die. They gotta you rest this way work out
Some guys do the same shit like me
I'm one of those
Sweet up
And everybody wants you it's just not your beauty that cannot be duplicated in any shape way of form
All the people know what I'm talking about psyche knows
Psych is not one of those he's a nerd. He's he's got a psyche has to work for people to like like
He's got a good head. He's got a you know, my
There's some guys that hold a lot of bed and this girl's lined up ten blocks
Okay, I don't need women line of ten blocks or a guy. I just need
I love that
Alex someone's asking if you ever
What if you're caught a squirt in your face right in the face Amanda wants to know a squirt
Yeah
I mean pushy squirt
I don't know. What do you mean Amanda a pussy sport or like a jizz sport?
I've seen the scorey persons
The first time I seen a girl shit fucking fire hose water out of pussy. Oh, it's like wow
Yes, I'm gonna squirt shit
Is it pee
Don't know supposedly whatever it is. I bathed in that shit that bitch was squirting
I was fucking as she was coming in when they come they squirt it doesn't smell. It's just like water. It's not pee
Don't know what it is, bro. It's just some liquid shit that comes out of the pussies when they come and I love it
I baited in that shit. I was like, yeah
Yeah, I love squatters. I'm off my end of squatters, man
That shit turns me on when I'm fucking you and the fucking waters popping out of your pussy while you're coming
That's hot
You know what's even hotter site? I fucked a girl on her period
And yo, it looked like a crime scene.
The whole bed was covered in blood.
What? What?
I don't know what to say.
That's not TOS.
I don't want to hear that.
You don't want to hear it?
It's the TOS of my mind.
It's the greatest day of my life.
I guess that's TOS of my mind.
Bro, I was fucking the shit out on her period,
and the whole bedroom was covered in blood.
The blanket's me and her, right?
I will put the whole...
Mean I asked him to stop and he just wouldn't I mean, it's like right
Terrible hopefully this reminds me to wash my curtains
Why kick you I don't know I mean did I kick you I don't remember kicking you
Did I?
Maybe there's a reason I don't know were you annoying me? Are you being nice? I?
Don't know
Oh
Guys a little bit a little bit too much a little bit too much
Beep beep beep beep beep, okay
This is hold on. Oh, is this a man's boyfriend right now? Is there about him right now?
That Ray Ray
Yeah, this is Rikers or than Rikers. That's like the boyfriend Ray Ray. I don't know. I'm just guessing
Hello
Hi, Yumi. Hi, Mr. Psyche. How are you? Good. How are you?
Oh, great. Okay. Good. Good.
I'm good too.
Oh, yeah, my food is ready. I'm gonna I'm having some uh,
let's see. What is it? It's a macaroni cheese and it's a uh
What else is there? There's a salisbury steak. Ah, shit.
Okay, hot, hot, okay.
I'm ready to go. Okay, here we go. Okay. Oh
How, what do you have for dinner tonight? Oh shit. Yeah
It's still the end in the afternoon. Oh, oh my god. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. What do you have for lunch?
It's in the afternoon. Oh my gosh. Yeah
Okay, Amanda, so now Amanda are you just that you're just that you're just that guy the taxi guy of reincarnated, right?
And it's like right. I don't like him either
So go eat poo similar. I'm not sure about it. I don't know. I don't know. I think these people are mental
It's mental
Okay, guys
It's like a salary sick. I'll show you one
You never eat rice or something for dinner, right rice for dinner for dinner only in my sushi
Wow
That's delicious
Yeah, enjoy it
Dopers
So far is delicious
Okay, well
Tell it to nobody Amanda because you are now
Okay, so you mean you like my song that was I was making for people
You like a song for Miss Peter
Oh, you like that one?
Yeah, I think that was cute
Yeah, that was cute. That was really cute
Yeah, I want to make another song you but yeah, they're fun. I mean there's like, you know, it's AI music
But I I do I do like put the prompt prompting. Hey gonzo the great gonzo. Let me tell you, okay
So now we have oh my gosh, we have Amanda
I can just tell like the energy of the person, right? And so so now gonzo I mean
Amads, can you please just say so you'll see that person, right? Just to leave them
Just hide them
Goodbye. Goodbye
Hidden
Gone gone forever into the ether your words never never read your joke never landed
your lame
Your lame you are a muppet
I can't understand about this people behavior. I mean, I don't know why they
They they really don't know to be a human being
Not for judging someone, you know
Not right. It's also it's all and it's also like a lot of the most judgmental people are the people that they have some stuff to be judged
About yeah, not necessarily to pull up. I'm trying to say anything, but it's like, yeah
Some of the people that are judging me like you know look in the mirror, okay?
Look in the mirror before you start judging. They don't have it but said they don't have it. They don't have any
Mirror to see their reflection, I guess I think that's why they non-stop like a judging A to Z about someone
I know it's it's unfortunate. It's kind of I feel I feel so pity about the ball, you know, yeah
Well, let's just pray that they you know
Mm-hmm. They don't end up in a mental. Yeah, they cannot share
Positivity even just for one day with you or something get you know, like a screaming
Hating
So I'm doing or something
Yeah, it's it's yeah, it's horrible really really horrible. I don't know what's wrong with people
It's like you know what?
You know what? Yeah, I'm just gonna
Whatever they went they went whatever they want to say and just they can say yeah make it 21 all right 21 else
Yeah, it'll continue to I know I know this person who was it that Darth Vader that's a Vader guy
I mean, it's like he probably did form bomb me. I just think I don't have the patience to
To deal with it all day
I mean, I'm just trying to be nice. I'm trying to be I'm trying to be nice and try to have fun
And I'm and I'm appreciated and thank you
Oh, you're always nice too. Thank you. Thank you. I love you. I love you too. Love you, Yumi. Thank you.
I love you and your cat too.
You gave me a smile tonight.
Yeah, Yumi.
Now you're just making me starving.
That's good.
Yeah, it's like, oh, it's like, they, they hate you. They hate what you did on your panel. But, and then why they keep talking on your channel is talking on your, your panel when they hating you. Stop. Go make something else out there. Do not force.
I know, I wish they, isn't it not just logical though, I mean, oh shit, they did that, they
seem to lack a little bit of logic, they're, they seem to be like, hey, let's just like
gang up on this person.
I step away, I step away from these people, you mean, creating the trauma using Stream
Yard, the trauma using YouTube, I, I, I step away from last year.
step away I yeah I yeah it's better I focus about myself focus about my real
life and my family that's it focus about people who can respect me as a
human being you know has a friend a new friend from Asia like that you know
don't listen to them mr. Sipy you just you you be you that's you
Thank you.
Don't listen to them.
I know Alexo.
I wish I can bring Alexo and James to join to your panel,
but they are busy because they are young boys from Italy
and from the Africa, San Francisco, I think,
from James Africa.
Who is?
Alex?
Yeah, Alexo.
Alexo and James.
Oh, Alexo.
Alexo, OK.
Yeah, because I am.
He's a cute boy
Okay, yeah, yeah, it's still yeah, it's like a 22 I think 22 years old. Yeah, I'll accept
Yeah, I used to be I'm a friend I'm a friend with it talking about will Durant
I'm sure he's talking right now
Stuck in me on your panel
Will Durant I used to call him as my YouTube brother
But something something worse happened, and then I step away from him. It's like I
Talked to him like the almost like a year. I think
Mm-hmm. Yeah, I don't yeah
Yeah, I don't have it in my time about that
Sometimes it happens with like, you know friends and it's like, you know, you'll make your friends and then it's like
They won't like you for some reason and you know what you just have to wish them the best and send them love, but you know
Not everyone's gonna be
There for us, right? We've got to be there for ourselves. We're all we're growing up people. We are growing up people
Do positive things do not creating the trauma. That's it
I got it. I gotta go. I gotta go. Talk to you. Okay, sweetie. Thank you so much. Love you. Bye. Bye. Love you. Bye
You have a great day. Thank you. You me. Yes. That's a sweet person. I said she has a good heart
That's what it's about. It's not about
All these people trying to get it to get attention
Thinking like that they're being so funny
There's really rude
Not
You'll have to make your own inferences, inferences.
Yes.
So I guess I blocked my entire chat, and it's OK.
I will read some more about the narcissistic personalities
and go through some of that again.
Real cool, huh?
Everything she said was a lie.
Oh, god, come on.
Shit I was a nice person so that's a lie, right?
So so funny so funny
So funny I forgot to laugh, right?
Okay guys, I just updated my about me with my reading for my, if you'd like to get a
private reading, you can look through SC if you'd prefer, or you can do one over the phone,
contact me and we can do the kind of reading you want, no matter what the listing says.
published. Okay. Okay. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
I'm always in a block here. I love a block here
You can do it all night I can do it all night
Thank you. Yeah
And if people bother you in chat guys because sometimes the chat is being I kind of like you know
Metabolize based on people you just go ahead and block them or let me know if it's bad too bad
Thank you ma's you're on it. Got you. Thank you
Got it got is a good got you, okay
God he has my back
Appreciate that
I'm going to write a song.
Hi Amanda
Names and controls
Let's see
Okay, I'm trying. I tried to write a song. I don't know if it's any good
See what you've checked you can use things
Okay
That's not working.
Okay.
Oh, here it is.
Okay, here it is. They wrote it.
That's the last one.
Okay, they wrote it. It's funny, edgy, and chaotic. Okay
Emily I'm a little emo too, but here comes. Oh, okay, and it says Joe it says it's genre trap cabaret all pop
It says think doja cat means rocky or picture show. Okay
Let's try that one
I like doja cat and rocky or picture show
Oh, fuck, I just like, fuck down.
Did it?
Oh, okay.
Copy.
Okay.
Hi guys, here we go.
AI.
AI, it's a generator.
Okay.
And what do they say?
Doja Cat means Rocky Horror Picture Show.
I'll go musical and then hip hop.
I'll go hip hop musical.
That sound good?
I'll try that.
Okay.
Okay, so it'll be musical
And hip hop
There we go generating, okay
Yo, I can't wait to hear this one
Yeah, I think I think I pushed you in this one, but no I don't consider you a troll
I consider you like a friend, but if I put you in I just just because I want you to give your shot
Anyway, they're all awesome
Yeah, I
Hear my beat as long it was really good to you. You heard my beat as long earlier. I did I heard a couple
You heard a couple. Okay. Yeah, we need a Christine summer boxy by her side
Yeah
I heard a moment
Yeah, Paige
You still want the songs from yesterday, okay, I'll put them on my arm. I'll put them on my desk
That's the number one hit
Everyone loves that one over all of them
The one with the
Madness
Yeah, Michael Lingweenie getting gonged
It was the funniest shit. What'd you say like Michael?
Later gonged Alex making a joke send into the night
Oh
Perfecto like Michael wants to talk later Alex
Crazy
So funny perfect. It was actually like perfect
They're really cool I
Mean I cannot write music. I can't write the lyrics very well, but I can prompt sure I can
Hmm I've got ideas wants to joke boom send them to the night
I'll put them on discord. I haven't put them up yet. I'll put them on just I will put them on my discord
Like yeah, um, I
Do have links to them. Maybe I'll put them in my description
God you it's not hitting a link to me page is not having a link. I don't know
I'm not gonna I mean it's like I will only kick you off the show if you I never kicked the page off, right?
I've kicked you up a million
Hmm. Hmm. No, why would you keep page? She doesn't get out of line
You keep me I have violated rules page doesn't violate the rules
Yep, she doesn't page is very she doesn't
I'm sympathy for you for people because
Because I would everything that was a joke a lot. Oh, I'm gonna wake up from here. Yeah, you can outline you get kicked
Okie-dokie or the Chokey page. I always say okie-dokie by the way
That's my line okie-dokie
That's weird
I was just taking a little while
I don't know when they'll be ready. I think in the meantime play our shit the number one. Hey
Awesome, well me pulling you off something I got this one. Oh, you're jumping. How are you eating? You're jumping away
I'm psyching in a speedo stars and stripes flash flash turning into tacos with the side of whiplash fish guts on the mic
That salsa in my eye, I'm dancin' on the table like conspiracy's, don't die!
Be the sippin' wine, cryin' bout her ex, top's gone flyin', it's a certified mess
She's spillin' all the tea, now the chat's on fire, Doc's buyin' cat and her fart's gone viral
Welcome to the panel, ain't no rules to this, if you're sayin' turn back, you will not be missed
Sims in the DMs, chaos in the chat, this show's more crack than a TikTok
That's the funniest thing I learned
Oh my god, a public breakdown!
It's in a speedo!
One more drink and someone's on the floor
Drama, delusion, thirst, traps, and cloud
It's a digital madhouse, cream it out loud
The last poster of the show
A digital madhouse!
Say a prayer, come to the panel
We're all gonna regret this
400%
Ha ha ha ha!
Who do you think ever made?
Fish
Okay, okay, the new song is ready. Okay, I just need to do it on one second
Well, that's amazing, bro
We're all gonna regret this
Yeah, yeah, it's gonna come back to bite you in your ass
Who you?
Let's be good people, and not a reservation issue.
Hold on.
I just need to put this on real quick.
Shit.
Cancel.
I'm just a fish taco in a world on fire.
Oh, how's the chat doing? Okay. Okay. Cancel. Oh, where do you feel the con?
Okay, sorry, my pad was a little bit wonky. Okay.
Enter studio.
I didn't want to believe you did, but you're right.
Yeah.
OK, here we go.
Here we go.
But God, do you think you should say the N word in that comment?
One second.
I'm having a minute with you.
What's up?
OK.
True.
There's two psycharones
Yeah, yeah, who for the price of one?
Yeah, two for the price. Okay, so the song is almost ready. It'll be ready in one second
We can hear the premiere of the troll song. Okay here. It's ready. Okay
The premiere the troll song. I mean, yeah, I mean, yeah, yes, you are
Where is my picture of my music trolls behind me, oh pretty go
Oh
Oh, yeah, it's right here. Okay, I'll play it. Here we go. I mean it was a troll song
They came in loud they came in wrong but baby I made them part of my song
They pop and rude with the same old script
Tryna porn bomb the show like I'm gonna trip
Saying wow shit, flexin' hate and fear
But I got glitter nails and a crystal sphere
Doug D talkin' like it's 1952
Racist rents, yeah I banned you to view
But every troll that clicks my stream
Just feeds the fire in this mystic queen
Trolls make-
with the tarot pack
Duh out of pocket, out of touch
Your trauma dumb, don't trigger much
Yeah, keep watchin', keep that frown
Cause trolls make the world go round, down
JT and Reigns, devilishly hot
If Lucifer had a twitch, they'd co-host the spot
Cross these vibes
Then there's Alice yelling you're all the same
Dudes got more clones than a bad video game
I mute, I boot, I laugh so hard
While I shuffle my deck and pull your card
Tony's got a crush for a baby boy
Dropping porn like he's trying to destroy
But guess what?
Psyche don't fold
You're just another name in the block
You're the ones who yell, who shame, who storm the chat.
You try to break me, but baby, I'm the storm, you can't survive.
And see you next stream, suckers, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
And see you next stream, suckers.
Whoa, that was good. Whoa, that was amazing
After that, I believe that was made in like five minutes to it was like so perfect. Thank you guys for listening and
I hope you appreciate the message and I know I know most people here are not trolls and even if they are true
They're friendly trolls usually
Not trying to be harmful, but you know
I don't like the form bombing stuff, but otherwise you guys are all right. Okay
Eight hour streams so far. Wow. Oh, okay. This is over there eating the rest of my my food
You guys like this dog. I don't know. You see it. You're on the top chat. Wow. God. You got on the top chat. Finally
Finally
I
Okay, guys
I did like the song, is that a kind of like,
some kind of like Jimmy, Jim Iroquois or something?
Who's that guy named Jim Iroquois?
From like the 90s, kind of sounds like that a little bit.
Or a, that black guy, not Lenny Kravitz, I'm not sure.
Who's the guy with the big hat and the black and white
video and he was like walking all over the room?
Remember that video?
You're not a troll, you got character, well good.
Also, even if you're most people most people have a little bit of troll blood, but you know, there are some full-fledged trolls
I just named a few of them assigned. I'm gonna like get anybody too mad
Doug D. Alex
Rain and rain and J.T. You got it now
I
Said I said they're pretty I said they're I said rainy JT or so. I said they're they're a cute couple, but you know
It's huge for hell and so they put the whole thing about Lucifer in there is pretty good because there's a devil
There's a devil. I get it. Yeah. Yeah, the devil
Ellie said nothing about the devil, but at least demons
Demons, yes, I'm the devil and he comes Alex you gotta go back and listen to the song
Yeah, I'm the devil in this whole scenario
Well, you're not really
You're not tempting me that you're like trying to be the voice of reason, right the temperatures
Oh, I'm the voice of reason. We're in trouble
But how about the accusers like the accusers, you know
Accusery is like satan is the accuser. That's what it means in the Bible like satan is the accuser. There's no one that's accusing
It's almost like a deck Marjorie bitch. She's the voice of reason. She wants the Epstein flowers dropped
Margie green
When she's the voice of reason we're fucked
Well, I mean Margie I think it's a tie-up and so just look at her name and it's gonna be all
It's gonna be a clue other clue. It's just another clue down the rabbit hole
I mean come on. Hey, are we guys really we guys really believe someone blue?
I have seen was not operating alone
For a morning guy trafficking kids by himself for 14 year old for his so they go to the school
They pick up these 14 year old 14 year old white girls from this Florida's high school
Okay, and then they fly them over to an island. Okay to be a massage therapist. No one figures it out for months
Okay, like maybe six months through a year until someone someone said after at a hundred girls
Can girls keep secrets like this? I mean, maybe they can but with from each other. No
It's impossible. Okay, so guys it's fake
Good, I just want to wake you up to something like the world
It's for I mean, what do you mean? It's a ring. It's not even real. It's just a big it's like a it's like a ditty thing
It's just the it's the
Don't say that